<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RN_Ration_Caviar.label>Caviar</RN_Ration_Caviar.label>
  <RN_Ration_Caviar.description>A canned caviar, from its packaging it seems to mimic an ancient Fairview brand though it's freshly produced. Caviar is a food consisting of salt-cured roe. A canned delicacy, manufactured for survival use. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside.</RN_Ration_Caviar.description>
  <RH_AestheticShaper.label>super seducer implant</RH_AestheticShaper.label>
  <RH_AestheticShaper.description>A highly sophisticated modification of the Aesthetic Shaper, a package of hormonal and mechanite influences shapes the muscles and fat on the body, adding non-functional aesthetic tissue where needed to achieve a desired appearance. This implant can be configured to form various body shapes according to the user’s taste - or that of their partner.\n\nThis implant was produced by the infamous Dr. La Ruina, who made off with insurmountable wealth for the invention of this implant. He is hunted for multiple counts of unethical human experimentation, and being involved with human traffickers that use these implants for slaves.</RH_AestheticShaper.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicSpine.label>voidtech spine</RH_VOIDBionicSpine.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicSpine.description>An advanced artificial spine, resembling a natural spine in appearance and its feeling. A biogel nerve bundle runs down an articulated plasteel core, surrounded by a lattice-dust healing system. It matches the performance of a biological spine.\n\nThis bionic part is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicSpine.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicHeart.label>voidtech heart</RH_VOIDBionicHeart.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicHeart.description>An advanced artificial heart resembling a natural heart in appearance and its feeling. It has synthetic muscle fibers for a realistic heartbeat, plus a high-flow pump for rapid circulation during high stress. It is better than a biological heart in almost every way.\n\nThis bionic organ is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicHeart.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicStomach.label>voidtech stomach</RH_VOIDBionicStomach.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicStomach.description>An advanced artificial stomach, resembling a natural stomach in appearance and its feeling. An advanced chemical processing system breaks down nutrients the body could normally never use, leading to increased efficiency. It is better than a biological stomach in almost every way.\n\nThis bionic organ is custom made by VOID for their members. It is an improvement from the reprossesor stomach design.</RH_VOIDBionicStomach.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicEar.label>voidtech ear</RH_VOIDBionicEar.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicEar.description>An advanced artificial ear implant, resembling a natural ear in appearance and its feeling. A collection of invisible subdermal microphones capture sound and transmit it to a biogel nerve interface that links directly with the auditory nerve. It's sensitive enough to hear a cat before you see it, can't be damaged by loud noise, and automatically tunes itself to pick out meaningful sounds in noisy environments.\n\nThis bionic part is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicEar.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicLung.label>voidtech lung</RH_VOIDBionicLung.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicLung.description>A highly advanced artificial lung, resembling a natural lung in appearance and its feeling. Capable of converting most impurities into oxygen and increase the capacity for breathing. A pair of these form the core of the human respiratory system.\n\nThis bionic organ is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicLung.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicKidney.label>voidtech kidney</RH_VOIDBionicKidney.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicKidney.description>An advanced artificial kidney, resembling a natural kidney in appearance and its feeling. Filters and removes waste products from the blood with more efficiency.\n\nThis bionic organ is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicKidney.description>
  <RH_VOIDBionicLiver.label>voidtech liver</RH_VOIDBionicLiver.label>
  <RH_VOIDBionicLiver.description>An advanced artificial liver, resembling a natural liver in appearance and its feeling. Plays an important role in a more efficient metabolism.\n\nThis bionic organ is custom made by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDBionicLiver.description>
  <RH_VOIDSocialImplant.label>impromptu implant</RH_VOIDSocialImplant.label>
  <RH_VOIDSocialImplant.description>A custom made non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with social interactions, designed for social engineering to assist the user with persuasion, deception and performance.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</RH_VOIDSocialImplant.description>
  <RH_VOIDCircadianHalfCycler.label>voidtech half-cycler</RH_VOIDCircadianHalfCycler.label>
  <RH_VOIDCircadianHalfCycler.description>A custom made signal redirector which isolates half of the brain, allowing the other half to sleep while the user remains outwardly awake. By alternating brain halves, the user never needs to sleep. Unfortunately, two hemispheres are better than one - working with half a brain causes a reduction in consciousness.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members, it is an improvement from the design of the circadian half-cycler with its EMP damage protection to prevent brain shock.</RH_VOIDCircadianHalfCycler.description>
  <VOIDCombat_Implant.label>destruction implant</VOIDCombat_Implant.label>
  <VOIDCombat_Implant.description>A custom made non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with combat, improving aim speed and accuracy.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</VOIDCombat_Implant.description>
  <VOIDMeleeCombat_Implant.label>violence implant</VOIDMeleeCombat_Implant.label>
  <VOIDMeleeCombat_Implant.description>A custom made non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with melee combat increasing reaction speed, dodge reflexes and helps the user land hits on the enemy with real-time analysis.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</VOIDMeleeCombat_Implant.description>
  <VOIDBrain_Implant.label>genius implant</VOIDBrain_Implant.label>
  <VOIDBrain_Implant.description>A custom made non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with learning, memory and calculation, like a calculator and notepad embedded in the brain.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</VOIDBrain_Implant.description>
  <VOIDHealing_Implant.label>nerotonin-V implant</VOIDHealing_Implant.label>
  <VOIDHealing_Implant.description>A custom made implant that uses nanomachines to improves the user's natural healing factor, boost immunity gain speed and reduce blood loss in the same way coagulators do.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</VOIDHealing_Implant.description>
  <VOIDArmorskin_Implant.label>behemoth implant</VOIDArmorskin_Implant.label>
  <VOIDArmorskin_Implant.description>This custom implant releases chemicals and nanomachines that toughen the skin to mimic the "Behemoth" gene, one of the extreme variants that resulted from the N-4 mutation. This makes the user more resistant to damage across their whole body and be extremely aversive towards heat.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members.</VOIDArmorskin_Implant.description>
  <RH_VOIDAestheticNose.label>voidtech nose</RH_VOIDAestheticNose.label>
  <RH_VOIDAestheticNose.description>A custom made advanced artificial nose, shaped to the user’s desired form, matching prevalent beauty standards and enhancing physical impressions. It also enhances the user's sense of smell and is able to filter out strong stenches when desired, some features are derived from the gastro-analyzer to aid with cooking.\n\nThis implant is produced by VOID for their members</RH_VOIDAestheticNose.description>
  <RH_RedWine.label>red wine</RH_RedWine.label>
  <RH_RedWine.description>Red wine is a type of wine made from dark-colored grape varieties. Wine can taste good, but its main effect is intoxication. Excessive consumption can lead to alcohol blackouts and, over time, addiction.</RH_RedWine.description>
  <RH_RedWine.ingestible.ingestCommandString>Drink {0}</RH_RedWine.ingestible.ingestCommandString>
  <RH_RedWine.ingestible.ingestReportString>Drinking {0}.</RH_RedWine.ingestible.ingestReportString>
  <RH_RedWine.tools.0.label>bottle</RH_RedWine.tools.0.label>
  <RH_RedWine.tools.1.label>neck</RH_RedWine.tools.1.label>
  <RH_Nerotonin8B.label>nerotonin-8B</RH_Nerotonin8B.label>
  <RH_Nerotonin8B.description>A Nerotonin-8B (N-8B) pill that can heal health conditions rapidly. It was discovered in an abandoned secronom building years after the outbreak, the secronom corporation who was held responsible for the outbreak of the N-4 virus did not have documents or files regarding this mysterious pill. It was the cure they failed to release, which only worked on those that have not yet succumbed to the N-4 infection or to death itself.\n\nAfter being returned to Fort Pastor, research began almost immediately to allow surviving scientists to reproduce this long forgotten medicine.</RH_Nerotonin8B.description>
  <RH_Nerotonin8B.comps.0.useLabel>Use nerotonin-8B</RH_Nerotonin8B.comps.0.useLabel>
  <RH_DF_Titan.label>titan</RH_DF_Titan.label>
  <RH_DF_Titan.description>A weaponized Titan, a mutant infected with a modified strain of the N-4 virus.\n\nOne hit is often all it takes for the Titan's mighty arms to kill anyone unfortunate enough to be within reach. The virus, mixed with a rare gene, changed this former human being's bones into something stronger than a concrete wall. This effectively makes the Titan a living tank, capable of taking many punishing hits before it goes down. In Greek mythology, its namesakes waged war with the Greek gods, and almost won. Your colonists, unfortunately, are not gods.\n\nDue to how the N-4 virus strain works, this creature is immune to heat damage, though the creature is still vulnerable to heatstrokes.</RH_DF_Titan.description>
  <RH_DF_Titan.tools.0.label>left fist</RH_DF_Titan.tools.0.label>
  <RH_DF_Titan.tools.1.label>right fist</RH_DF_Titan.tools.1.label>
  <RH_DF_Titan.tools.2.label>head</RH_DF_Titan.tools.2.label>
  <RH_DF_Wraith.label>Wraith</RH_DF_Wraith.label>
  <RH_DF_Wraith.description>A weaponized Wraith, a mutant infected with a modified strain of the N-4 virus.\n\nThe Wraith's tentacles are capable of penetrating most armours known to man, including ones that are of spacer origin. The Wraith is also known as "The Destroying Angel," they are the archetype of all female N-4 mutants. Wraiths are perhaps the least mentally affected by the mutations of Nerotonin-4, allowing them to retain their premortem mental acuity. Known back in their world as an eerie reminder of humanity’s best.\n\nDue to how the N-4 virus strain works, this creature is immune to heat damage, though the creature is still vulnerable to heatstrokes.</RH_DF_Wraith.description>
  <RH_DF_Wraith.tools.0.label>tentacles</RH_DF_Wraith.tools.0.label>
  <RH_DF_Wraith.tools.1.label>tentacles</RH_DF_Wraith.tools.1.label>
  <RH_DF_Wraith.tools.2.label>head</RH_DF_Wraith.tools.2.label>
  <RH_DF_GiantSpider.label>giant spider</RH_DF_GiantSpider.label>
  <RH_DF_GiantSpider.description>A weaponized Giant Spider, a mutant infected with a modified strain of the N-4 virus.\n\nBack in a city known as Fairview came some N-4 mutations known as the "Spider" which causes the infected to grow an extra set of 4 arms. It is not clear how they could have grown so exponentially. It is hypothesized that the N4 virus mutated the pituitary gland to excrete vast amounts of HGH (Human Growth Hormone), the same mutation that might be found in Titans and Wraiths. This creature's intelligence is about the same as its predecessor, a disadvantage that allows it to be trapped with ease.\n\nDue to how the N-4 virus strain works, this creature is immune to heat damage, though the creature is still vulnerable to heatstrokes.</RH_DF_GiantSpider.description>
  <RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.0.label>left claw</RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.0.label>
  <RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.1.label>right claw</RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.1.label>
  <RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.2.label>teeth</RH_DF_GiantSpider.tools.2.label>
  <RNApparel_VOIDReactive.label>VOID reactive</RNApparel_VOIDReactive.label>
  <RNApparel_VOIDReactive.description>An ancient suit of powered armor. The "VOID Reactive" crafted by a worldhopper nicknamed "Admin" for VOID members only. He has never made armors for anyone ever since the fall of VOID from grace.\n\nThe armor was modeled after how N-4 mutant genes reacted to extreme heat, high resistance to fire and high temperatures.</RNApparel_VOIDReactive.description>
  <RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOID.label>VOID helmet</RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOID.label>
  <RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOID.description>An ancient powered armor helmet, The VOID helmet has a built-in status computer compatible with various VOID brain implants. Without the implants one cannot access the HUD within this helmet.\n\nThe VOID helmet protects the user from psychic attacks and toxic fallouts, improvements of which were a part of a promise to VOID made by a worldhopper known only as "Admin". The promise no longer applied to them when they abandoned Fairview. The armor was modeled after how N-4 mutant genes reacted to extreme heat, high resistance to fire and high temperatures.</RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOID.description>
  <RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOIDCloaked.label>VOID helmet (cloak)</RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOIDCloaked.label>
  <RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOIDCloaked.description>An ancient powered armor helmet, The VOID helmet has a built-in status computer compatible with various VOID brain implants. Without the implants one cannot access the HUD within this helmet. This version comes with a wasteland cloak hood, makes the helmet slightly flammable. \n\nThe VOID helmet protects the user from psychic attacks and toxic fallouts, improvements of which were a part of a promise to VOID made by a worldhopper known only as "Admin". The promise no longer applied to them when they abandoned Fairview. The armor was modeled after how N-4 mutant genes reacted to extreme heat, high resistance to fire and high temperatures.</RNApparel_ReactiveHelmet_VOIDCloaked.description>
  <RNApparel_SpeedSkin_VOID.description>A speed skin that utilizes nano technology. It allows the user to perform actions almost as fast as they think them, with the skin suit preventing burnout, acid buildup and other issued to allow the wearer's body to move freely at meta human speeds.\n\nIt was something "borrowed" by VOID from Glitterworlds during their early stages of venturing through the stars.</RNApparel_SpeedSkin_VOID.description>
  <RNApparel_SpeedSkin_VOID.label>VOID speed skin</RNApparel_SpeedSkin_VOID.label>
  <RHApparel_DFCloak_Black.label>Cloak (wasteland black)</RHApparel_DFCloak_Black.label>
  <RHApparel_DFCloak_Black.description>A windproof cloak, worn-out from it's years of use but keeps on going. It seems to be something wasteland survivors are too sentimental to let go of, before their time of using power armors. Maybe its just whats fashionable among their social circles.</RHApparel_DFCloak_Black.description>
  <RNApparel_BuisnessSuit_VOID.description>A custom tailor business suit for VOID executives, or for the average member's use outside of combat. It is taken from Glitterworld technology, bullet resistant and keeps the temperature within warm despite its lightweight feel, as if the user is using a parka.\n\nEven though the color scheme of this suit seems to be for evil organizations, it's so sleek and smart in appearance that its wearer can just about persuade you to surrender and let them use you for human experiments.</RNApparel_BuisnessSuit_VOID.description>
  <RNApparel_BuisnessSuit_VOID.label>business suit VOID</RNApparel_BuisnessSuit_VOID.label>
  <RHApparel_RangedShieldBelt_VOID.label>VOID shield belt</RHApparel_RangedShieldBelt_VOID.label>
  <RHApparel_RangedShieldBelt_VOID.description>A custom single-person energy shield device. It will attempt to stop any rapidly-moving projectile or energy attack that comes from a distance. It does nothing against melee attacks or shots from point-blank range.\n\nThis advanced version allows the wearer to fire outward, but the increased energy expenditure makes it weaker and slower to recharge. It's large pouches allow the wearer to carry extra items.</RHApparel_RangedShieldBelt_VOID.description>
  <RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.label>dusk razor</RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.label>
  <RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.description>The Dusk Razor is a strange and powerful falchion-like blade. This rare blade is forged specifically for only the most dedicated survivors in its home world. It is earned by enduring a week long blood sport among other survivors, competing for the top place among the elite.\n\nThis weapon is a part of the Dusk set, crafted by a peculiar worldhopper who awards access only to his brutal competition's winners.</RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.description>
  <RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.tools.0.label>point</RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.tools.0.label>
  <RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.tools.1.label>serrated blade</RHMelee_DFDuskBlade.tools.1.label>
  <RHMelee_DFAmputator.label>amputator</RHMelee_DFAmputator.label>
  <RHMelee_DFAmputator.description>A strange, scythe-like blade. Earned its nickname through years of use from wherever world it came from, against creatures that can endure losing limbs.</RHMelee_DFAmputator.description>
  <RHMelee_DFAmputator.tools.0.label>point</RHMelee_DFAmputator.tools.0.label>
  <RHMelee_DFAmputator.tools.1.label>serrated blade</RHMelee_DFAmputator.tools.1.label>
  <RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.label>grinder</RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.label>
  <RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.description>The Grinder, a chainsaw with a mysterious origin. Upon close inspection, the word "ASH" is written on the side in crimson letters. Rumors say that the souls of slain enemies are what runs the high power engine of this chainsaw.</RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.description>
  <RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.tools.0.label>point</RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.tools.0.label>
  <RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.tools.1.label>blade</RHMelee_DFGrinder_Chainsaw.tools.1.label>
  <RN_BallisticKnife_Blade.label>ballistic knife blade</RN_BallisticKnife_Blade.label>
  <RNBullet_40SW_Pistol.label>.40 SW bullet</RNBullet_40SW_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45ACP_Pistol.label>.45 ACP bullet</RNBullet_45ACP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45ACPAP_Pistol.label>.45 ACP AP bullet</RNBullet_45ACPAP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MM_Pistol.label>9x19mm Parabellum bullet</RNBullet_9MM_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MMMakarov_Pistol.label>9x18mm Makarov bullet</RNBullet_9MMMakarov_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MMAP_Pistol.label>9x19mm Parabellum AP bullet</RNBullet_9MMAP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_46x30_Pistol.label>4.6x30mm bullet</RNBullet_46x30_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_57_Pistol.label>5.7x28mm bullet</RNBullet_57_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_50_Pistol.label>.50 bullet</RNBullet_50_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_762Tokarev_Pistol.label>7.62x25mm Tokarev Parabellum bullet</RNBullet_762Tokarev_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_762_Revolver.label>7.62x38mmR bullet</RNBullet_762_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_454_Revolver.label>.454 bullet</RNBullet_454_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_44Magnum_Pistol.label>.44 Magnum bullet</RNBullet_44Magnum_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45Colt_Pistol.label>.45 Colt bullet</RNBullet_45Colt_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_38Special_Pistol.label>.38 bullet</RNBullet_38Special_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_357_Revolver.label>.357 bullet</RNBullet_357_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_545x39_Rifle.label>5.45x39mm bullet</RNBullet_545x39_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_AACBlackout_PDW.label>AAC blackout bullet</RNBullet_AACBlackout_PDW.label>
  <RNBullet_380_SMG.label>.380 bullet</RNBullet_380_SMG.label>
  <RNBullet_32ACP_Pistol.label>.32 ACP bullet</RNBullet_32ACP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_12Gauge_Shotgun.label>shotgun blast</RNBullet_12Gauge_Shotgun.label>
  <RNBullet_23x75mmR_Shotgun.label>23x75mmR blast</RNBullet_23x75mmR_Shotgun.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_LMG.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_LMG.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_LMG.label>7.62x51mm NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_LMG.label>
  <RNBullet_762x39_Rifle.label>7.62x39R bullet</RNBullet_762x39_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_556x45_Rifle.label>5.56x45mm bullet</RNBullet_556x45_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_303British_Rifle.label> .303 British bullet</RNBullet_303British_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_Rifle.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_792x57Mauser_Rifle.label>8mm Mauser bullet</RNBullet_792x57Mauser_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_9x39mmSP6_DMR.label>9x39mm SP-6 bullet</RNBullet_9x39mmSP6_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_58x42mm_DMR.label>5.8x42mm bullet</RNBullet_58x42mm_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x39_DMR.label>7.62x39R bullet</RNBullet_762x39_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_DMR.label>7.62 NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_DMR.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_792x57Mauser_DMR.label>8mm Mauser bullet</RNBullet_792x57Mauser_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_308Winchester_DMR.label>.308 Winchester bullet</RNBullet_308Winchester_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_Sniper.label>7.62 NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_308Winchester_Sniper.label>.308 Winchester bullet</RNBullet_308Winchester_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_338Lapua_Sniper.label>.338 Lapua Magnum bullet</RNBullet_338Lapua_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_Sniper.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_408Cheyenne_Sniper.label>.408 Cheyenne bullet</RNBullet_408Cheyenne_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_50BMG_Sniper.label>.50 BMG bullet</RNBullet_50BMG_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_127x108_Sniper.label>12.7x108mm bullet</RNBullet_127x108_Sniper.label>
  <RHBullet_50CalFMJ_HMG.label>.50 BMG bullet</RHBullet_50CalFMJ_HMG.label>
  <RNBullet_10Gauge_Shotgun.label>shotgun blast</RNBullet_10Gauge_Shotgun.label>
  <RNBullet_DF_GAUSSRifle.label>GAUSS rifle</RNBullet_DF_GAUSSRifle.label>
  <RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.label>GAU-19</RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.label>
  <RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.description>The GAU-19/A is designed to accept standard NATO .50 caliber M9-linked ammunition. The rate of fire is selectable to be either 1,000 or 2,000 rounds per minute. The Humvee armament kit version fires at 1,300 rounds per minute. The average recoil force when firing is 1.7kN, 2.2kN or 2.8kN depending on firing rate.</RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.description>
  <RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.tools.0.label>barrels</RNGun_GAU19_Minigun.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DuskMAG.label>Dusk MAG</RNGun_DuskMAG.label>
  <RNGun_DuskMAG.description>The Dusk MAG, a portable heavy machinegun chambered in 12.7x99mm. This rare weapon system is crafted specifically for only the most dedicated survivors in its home world. It is earned by enduring a week long blood sport among other survivors, competing for the top place among the elite. \n\nThis weapon is a part of the Dusk set, crafted by a peculiar worldhopper who awards access only to his brutal competition's winners.</RNGun_DuskMAG.description>
  <RNGun_DuskMAG.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_DuskMAG.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DuskMAG.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_DuskMAG.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.label>corpse blaster</RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.description>A mysterious semi automatic shotgun, crafted from the preserved remains of the N-4 "undead". It uses 10 gauge shells. Rumors among survivors who have witnessed this weapon perform, are that cries of a hellhound can be heard while firing this weapon.</RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.description>
  <RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_CorpseBlasterS.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_DuskStrikerS.label>dusk striker</RNGun_DuskStrikerS.label>
  <RNGun_DuskStrikerS.description>The Dusk Striker, a fully automatic shotgun chambered in 10 gauge shells. This rare shotgun is crafted specifically for only the most dedicated survivors in its home world. It is earned by enduring a week long blood sport among other survivors, competing for the top place among the elite. \n\nThis weapon is a part of the Dusk set, crafted by a peculiar worldhopper who awards access only to his brutal competition's winners.</RNGun_DuskStrikerS.description>
  <RNGun_DuskStrikerS.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_DuskStrikerS.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DuskStrikerS.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_DuskStrikerS.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_DuskEnforcer.label>dusk enforcer</RNGun_DuskEnforcer.label>
  <RNGun_DuskEnforcer.description>The Dusk Enforcer, a puzzling semi automatic pistol. This sidearm has unlimited ammunition, yet when it is disassembled to extract rounds, none can be found. It is unkown how this technology is accomplished, though it is known that its bullet resembles .50 caliber hangun ammo in terms of size and damage. This enigma of a sidearm is crafted specifically for only the most dedicated survivors in its home world. It is earned by enduring a week long blood sport among other survivors, competing for the top place among the elite. \n\nThis weapon is a part of the Dusk set, crafted by a peculiar worldhopper who awards access only to his brutal competition's winners.</RNGun_DuskEnforcer.description>
  <RNGun_DuskEnforcer.tools.0.label>grip</RNGun_DuskEnforcer.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DuskEnforcer.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_DuskEnforcer.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.label>corpse destroyer</RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.description>Destructive and mysterious, no one knows how this weapon was created, who actually designed and built it, or where it even came from. It is a general purpose machine gun chambered in 7.62x51mm. It is crafted from preserved remains of N-4 "undead", rumored to have a mind of its own and cries of the infected still heard while firing this weapon.</RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.description>
  <RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_CorpseDestroyer.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_DuskCarbine.label>dusk carbine</RNGun_DuskCarbine.label>
  <RNGun_DuskCarbine.description>The Dusk Carbine, an early "X" variant which is chambered in 12.7x99mm. This rare rifle is crafted specifically for only the most dedicated survivors in its home world. It is earned by enduring a week long blood sport among other survivors, competing for the top place among the elite. \n\nThis weapon is a part of the Dusk set, crafted by a peculiar worldhopper who awards access only to his brutal competition's winners.</RNGun_DuskCarbine.description>
  <RNGun_DuskCarbine.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_DuskCarbine.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DuskCarbine.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_DuskCarbine.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.label>GAUSS rifle</RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.label>
  <RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.description>A rifle that was custom made for one individual known as "Reznorock", who discovered a means to mass produce it for other VOID members. Legend has it that its parts were discovered in the lost city of Fairview, an odd thing to find in a fallen Midworld where spacer tech weapons are nothing but fairy tales. Reznorock returned this to an outpost, gathering the others to ask if anyone knew the value of these parts. One worldhopper that didn't belong there told him all he needed to know. The worldhopper took pity on Reznorock, wearing his ragged clothes and blood covered bandages.\n\nThis GAUSS rifle is now among the many custom tools the mysterious worldhopper created for VOID. A man who is partly responsible for raising them to be the monsters they are now.</RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.description>
  <RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_DFGAUSSrifle.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>