<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFE_FactoryBasics.label>factory basics</VFE_FactoryBasics.label>
  <VFE_FactoryBasics.description>Gain a basic fundamental understanding of factory utilization and unlock factory hoppers and terrain capable of supporting heavy machinery.</VFE_FactoryBasics.description>
  <VFE_ElectronicsFabricationFactory.label>electronics fabrication factory</VFE_ElectronicsFabricationFactory.label>
  <VFE_ElectronicsFabricationFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically harness small amounts of steel from loose rock chunks and forge them into both simple mechanical components and higher tech electronic components.</VFE_ElectronicsFabricationFactory.description>
  <VFE_MasonryandMetallicsFactory.label>masonry and metallics factory</VFE_MasonryandMetallicsFactory.label>
  <VFE_MasonryandMetallicsFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically mine surface-level rock chunks as well as process them into bricks and further refine them into an advanced material indistinguishable from plasteel.</VFE_MasonryandMetallicsFactory.description>
  <VFE_MunitionsandArmamentsFactory.label>munitions and armaments factory</VFE_MunitionsandArmamentsFactory.label>
  <VFE_MunitionsandArmamentsFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically refine and clarify chemfuel from organic matter as well as process it further into weaponry and large-scale mortar shells.</VFE_MunitionsandArmamentsFactory.description>
  <VFE_WearablesandTextilesFactory.label>wearables and textiles factory</VFE_WearablesandTextilesFactory.label>
  <VFE_WearablesandTextilesFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically recycle old apparel into salvaged scrap as well as assemble new apparel from the aforementioned scraps. Additionally unlocks a machine capable of molecularly reconfiguring apparel to mimic the properties of synthread.</VFE_WearablesandTextilesFactory.description>
  <VFE_ProvisionsPackagingFactory.label>provisions packaging factory</VFE_ProvisionsPackagingFactory.label>
  <VFE_ProvisionsPackagingFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically and efficiently harvest animal meat trimmings, cook, and package them into a variety of survival meals, kibble, and canned goods.</VFE_ProvisionsPackagingFactory.description>
  <VFE_MedicinalCompoundingFactory.label>medicinal compounding factory</VFE_MedicinalCompoundingFactory.label>
  <VFE_MedicinalCompoundingFactory.description>Research a series of machines that grant the ability to automatically refine a thick glycerol extremely similar to that of neutroamine, also allows the further refining into a variety of medicines or illicit drugs.</VFE_MedicinalCompoundingFactory.description>
  <VFE_BasicDroneAssembly.label>basic drone assembly</VFE_BasicDroneAssembly.label>
  <VFE_BasicDroneAssembly.description>Research a machine that allows the assembly of rudimentary automated rechargeable drones capable of hauling, mining, and cleaning.</VFE_BasicDroneAssembly.description>
  <VFE_AutomatedDefensiveMeasures.label>automated defensive measures</VFE_AutomatedDefensiveMeasures.label>
  <VFE_AutomatedDefensiveMeasures.description>Research the ability to weaponize automated drones for a variety of purposes including mobile turret platforms, mortars, riot control and other defensive countermeasures.</VFE_AutomatedDefensiveMeasures.description>
  <VFE_IndustrialRoasting.label>industrial roasting</VFE_IndustrialRoasting.label>
  <VFE_IndustrialRoasting.description>Research an industrial-sized oven that deeply roasts coffee beans before dispensing them to a quern that grinds them into grounds. Boiling water is then forced and filtered through the grounds into a mass amount of coffee. Nearby hoppers can also hold other products for processing a number of coffee-related drinks.</VFE_IndustrialRoasting.description>
  <VFE_CheeseMaking.label>industrial cheesemaking</VFE_CheeseMaking.label>
  <VFE_CheeseMaking.description>Research a tank capable of rapidly heating milk until curds begin to form, then automatically straining and pressing them into multiple wheels of cheese at once. Nearby hoppers can hold enough milk to make several wheels and finished wheels will automatically be dispensed.</VFE_CheeseMaking.description>
  <VFE_IndustrialSoups.label>industrial soups</VFE_IndustrialSoups.label>
  <VFE_IndustrialSoups.description>Research a very large vat with a series of mounted, spinning blades towards the top. Attached hoppers can be filled with a variety of raw food products. Thereafter they are vacuumed through the top, sliced and simmered deeply into a variety of soups. Finished soups will be dispensed to an opposing hopper without the need of processing steps. Input and output both are done en masse and require much less management than traditional slow cooking.</VFE_IndustrialSoups.description>
  <VFE_Aquaponics.label>aquaponics</VFE_Aquaponics.label>
  <VFE_Aquaponics.description>Research a deep water filled basin capable of processing vegetable matter into an algae-like paste for continuous feeding of fish living within. Fish within live in optimal water conditions and temperature and therefore breed quite quickly. Matured fish will occasionally be deposited to a nearby output hopper.</VFE_Aquaponics.description>
</LanguageData>