<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <BorealForest.label>boreal forest</BorealForest.label>
  <BorealForest.description>Forests of coniferous trees. Despite the harsh winters, boreal forests sustain a diverse population of small and large animals, and have warm summers.</BorealForest.description>
  <Tundra.label>tundra</Tundra.label>
  <Tundra.description>These mostly-frozen plains bear almost no trees and little vegetation. There are a few small animals interspersed with large herds of migratory grazers and their predators.</Tundra.description>
  <ColdBog.label>cold bog</ColdBog.label>
  <ColdBog.description>A wetland packed with trees and vines. Much of the marshy land here can't support heavy structures, moving around is slow due to choking vegetation. Disease is endemic in this dense, wet ecosystem.</ColdBog.description>
  <IceSheet.label>ice sheet</IceSheet.label>
  <IceSheet.description>Sheets of ice which can be kilometers thick. There is no soil for plants to grow in. The only animals here are migrating to somewhere else - or badly lost.</IceSheet.description>
  <SeaIce.label>sea ice</SeaIce.label>
  <SeaIce.description>Permanent ice sheets floating on water. There is no soil for plants to grow, no minerals to mine, and almost no animal life.</SeaIce.description>
  <TemperateForest.label>temperate forest</TemperateForest.label>
  <TemperateForest.description>Forests of deciduous trees interspersed with fertile clearings. Many species of animals move around among the trees and on the plains.</TemperateForest.description>
  <TemperateSwamp.label>temperate swamp</TemperateSwamp.label>
  <TemperateSwamp.description>Wetlands choked with vegetation and disease. Dense overgrowth makes it hard to move around, and clearing areas for building takes a long time. Much of the terrain is too marshy to support heavy structures.</TemperateSwamp.description>
  <TropicalRainforest.label>tropical rainforest</TropicalRainforest.label>
  <TropicalRainforest.description>A thick, moist jungle, buzzing with animal life and infested with disease. Despite its visual beauty, this is a very dangerous biome. Choking overgrowth, aggressive animals, and constant sickness are why some explorers call this the "green hell".</TropicalRainforest.description>
  <TropicalSwamp.label>tropical swamp</TropicalSwamp.label>
  <TropicalSwamp.description>A plant-choked, steamy swamp seething with parasites and pathogens. Much of the land is too marshy to build on. Difficult movement, aggressive animals, and rampant disease make living here a nightmare.</TropicalSwamp.description>
  <AridShrubland.label>arid shrubland</AridShrubland.label>
  <AridShrubland.description>A dry region, but not dry enough to become a true desert. Open plains with grasses and bushes give way to scattered groves of trees. Plants are hardy and there is a moderate density of animals, but arable soil is hard to find.</AridShrubland.description>
  <Desert.label>desert</Desert.label>
  <Desert.description>A very dry area which supports little life. There is very little arable land, and animal life is very sparse. Deserts can be hot, or quite cold.</Desert.description>
  <ExtremeDesert.label>extreme desert</ExtremeDesert.label>
  <ExtremeDesert.description>An extremely hot, dry area, devoid of almost all life. Searing heat and a near total lack of arable land make it very difficult to survive here.</ExtremeDesert.description>
  <Ocean.label>ocean</Ocean.label>
  <Ocean.description>Open ocean. Great for fish. Not so great for you.</Ocean.description>
  <Lake.label>lake</Lake.label>
  <Lake.description>A large lake. Beautiful to live next to. Not so beautiful to live in.</Lake.description>
</LanguageData>