<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RoyaltyTips.TitleMilitaryAid>Some title permits allow the holder to call for military aid. This can save you in a tough moment.</RoyaltyTips.TitleMilitaryAid>
  <RoyaltyTips.NoblesDemandPrivileges>Nobles from the Empire will demand all the privileges of their title. Your own titled colonists will be more flexible, unless they are greedy or jealous.</RoyaltyTips.NoblesDemandPrivileges>
  <RoyaltyTips.RoyalArmor>Prestige armor and eltex apparel will also satisfy the apparel requirements of royal titles.</RoyaltyTips.RoyalArmor>
  <RoyaltyTips.TitleInheritance>If a title holder dies, their title goes to their chosen heir.</RoyaltyTips.TitleInheritance>
  <RoyaltyTips.ChangeHeir>You can change the heir of a title holder through the comms console. However, this requires completing a ritual.</RoyaltyTips.ChangeHeir>
  <RoyaltyTips.FreePsychicAmplifier>The Empire bestows a free level of psylink upon anyone who earns the title required to use it.</RoyaltyTips.FreePsychicAmplifier>
  <RoyaltyTips.IllegalImplantUse>Psylink neuroformers can be acquired through quests. These items can give a person psychic powers.</RoyaltyTips.IllegalImplantUse>
  <RoyaltyTips.InstallingPsychicAmplifier>Gaining a new level of psylink grants knowledge of one random psychic power.</RoyaltyTips.InstallingPsychicAmplifier>
  <RoyaltyTips.PsycastAdvantage>Psychic powers can give you significant advantage in combat.</RoyaltyTips.PsycastAdvantage>
  <RoyaltyTips.PsycastFactionRelations>Using a psychic power on an ally will harm faction relations - but only if it has negative effects.</RoyaltyTips.PsycastFactionRelations>
  <RoyaltyTips.PsycastInvisibility>Psychic invisibility doesn't wear off when you attack.</RoyaltyTips.PsycastInvisibility>
  <RoyaltyTips.PsychicEntropyLimit>Going over your neural heat limit can save you in a desperate situation - but the psychic breakdown can last a while.</RoyaltyTips.PsychicEntropyLimit>
  <RoyaltyTips.PsycastSensitivity>Creatures with higher psychic sensitivity are affected more by psychics.</RoyaltyTips.PsycastSensitivity>
  <RoyaltyTips.EltexGear>Dressing your psycasters in eltex gear will increase their neural heat limit and dissipation rate.</RoyaltyTips.EltexGear>
  <RoyaltyTips.MechClusterPowercell>When fighting a mech cluster, try shooting their power cells. They explode, dealing heavy damage to surrounding creatures and structures.</RoyaltyTips.MechClusterPowercell>
  <RoyaltyTips.MechClusterDormant>Some mech clusters remain dormant until disturbed. Use that time to prepare your attack.</RoyaltyTips.MechClusterDormant>
  <RoyaltyTips.RoyalTributeCollector>The Imperial royal tribute collector arrives twice per year, and accepts prisoners and gold in exchange for honor.</RoyaltyTips.RoyalTributeCollector>
  <RoyaltyTips.MechClusterDormantTrigger>You can safely walk right past a dormant mech cluster, as long as you don't attack it or trigger a proximity activator.</RoyaltyTips.MechClusterDormantTrigger>
  <RoyaltyTips.SkipPsycastsMultiuse>The psychic skip power works on self, allies, enemies, and even items. The tactical possibilities are endless.</RoyaltyTips.SkipPsycastsMultiuse>
  <RoyaltyTips.JumpPackRescue>You can carry a downed ally while using the jump pack. Aerial rescues save lives.</RoyaltyTips.JumpPackRescue>
</LanguageData>