<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <EJC_Tempura.label>tempura</EJC_Tempura.label>
  <EJC_Tempura.description>An assortment of vegetables and meat fried with a light, crispy batter. Best eaten hot!</EJC_Tempura.description>
  <EJC_Onigiri.label>onigiri</EJC_Onigiri.label>
  <EJC_Onigiri.description>A simple meal consisting of sticky rice packed into easy-to-hold triangles. There's a topping and filling for everyone's tastes!</EJC_Onigiri.description>
  <EJC_Katsudon.label>katsudon</EJC_Katsudon.label>
  <EJC_Katsudon.description>A cut of meat fried to crispy perfection and served atop a bowl of rice and other toppings. Spacers often eat this meal for luck before landing planetside, but no one remembers why this dish is supposed to be lucky.</EJC_Katsudon.description>
  <EJC_Ramen.label>ramen</EJC_Ramen.label>
  <EJC_Ramen.description>Noodles and a variety of toppings in a broth. Quite variable! Tastiest when slurped while piping hot.</EJC_Ramen.description>
  <EJC_Udon.label>udon</EJC_Udon.label>
  <EJC_Udon.description>Thick chewy noodles in a broth. The dough to make the noodles is so thick, it's been known to be used as a punching bag to relieve stress during the kneading process.</EJC_Udon.description>
  <EJC_Yakisoba.label>yakisoba</EJC_Yakisoba.label>
  <EJC_Yakisoba.description>Stir-fried noodles with a variety of other ingredients. A common entertainment is watching the cook fry them right in front of you, and some cooks even pull fancy tricks while doing so.</EJC_Yakisoba.description>
  <EJC_CurryRice.label>curryrice</EJC_CurryRice.label>
  <EJC_CurryRice.description>An age-old blend of spices forms the base of curry, carried from Old Terra since ancient times. This particular style of curry was popular on an island nation, with meat and veggies stewed in the curry sauce and served alongside rice.  Mild and tasty to eat.</EJC_CurryRice.description>
  <EJC_Zarusoba.label>zarusoba</EJC_Zarusoba.label>
  <EJC_Zarusoba.description>A light dish of chilled noodles served on a bamboo draining mat with a dipping sauce. The cool noodles and salty sauce make a refreshing meal in the hot summer months.</EJC_Zarusoba.description>
  <EJC_Unajuu.label>unajuu</EJC_Unajuu.label>
  <EJC_Unajuu.description>Glazed and barbecued eel fillets on top of rice, served in a lacquer box. Hearty and packed with plenty of stamina to go all day - and night - long.</EJC_Unajuu.description>
  <EJC_InstantRamen.label>instant ramen</EJC_InstantRamen.label>
  <EJC_InstantRamen.description>Dried noodles and mild seasoning in a convenient cup. Just add hot water for a tasty snack! Warning: no responsibility taken for excessive consumption.</EJC_InstantRamen.description>
</LanguageData>