<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <BilliardsTable.label>billiards table</BilliardsTable.label>
  <BilliardsTable.description>A soft-topped bounded table for playing a variety of billiards-type games. It trains shooting ability.</BilliardsTable.description>
  
  <ChessTable.label>chess table</ChessTable.label>
  <ChessTable.description>The ancient game of kings. Fun for a few hours here and there, even playing alone. It trains intellectual skills.\n\nThis building requires adjacent chairs or stools to use.</ChessTable.description>
  
  <FlatscreenTelevision.label>flatscreen television</FlatscreenTelevision.label>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>A high-tech flat-screen television with crystal-clear image and rich color. Picks up transmissions from ancient satellites and ubiquitous data cards.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  
  <GameOfUrBoard.label>Game-of-Ur board</GameOfUrBoard.label>
  <GameOfUrBoard.description>Dating from 2500BC, this exciting yet infuriating board game can be played by one or two people. It trains intellectual skills.</GameOfUrBoard.description>
  
  <HoopstoneRing.label>hoopstone ring</HoopstoneRing.label>
  <HoopstoneRing.description>A simple ancient game played with stones and a large ring in the ground. Players try to toss stones through the ring from a distance. It's relaxing, and trains shooting skills.</HoopstoneRing.description>
  
  <HorseshoesPin.label>horseshoes pin</HorseshoesPin.label>
  <HorseshoesPin.description>A simple ancient game played with a horseshoes and a large pin in the ground. Players toss horseshoes to try to get them to land on the pin. It's relaxing, and trains shooting skills.</HorseshoesPin.description>
  
  <MegascreenTelevision.label>megascreen television</MegascreenTelevision.label>
  <MegascreenTelevision.description>A huge, high-tech television. Gigantic, hyper-vibrant images almost leap out of the screen. Very entertaining. Picks up transmissions from ancient satellites and ubiquitous data cards.</MegascreenTelevision.description>
  
  <PokerTable.label>poker table</PokerTable.label>
  <PokerTable.description>A table designed for playing gambling card games like poker. A great way to test your strategic skills and a bit of luck.\n\nThis building requires adjacent chairs or stools to use.</PokerTable.description>
  
  <Telescope.label>telescope</Telescope.label>
  <Telescope.description>A telescope for doing amateur astronomy. It's a relaxing hobby for a certain kind of person. Can only be used outdoors.</Telescope.description>
  
  <TubeTelevision.label>tube television</TubeTelevision.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>A cathode ray tube display for showing moving pictures with sound. Even on the rimworlds, there is often an old transmitter running something at least marginally interesting.</TubeTelevision.description>
</LanguageData>