<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Battery.label>battery</Battery.label>
  <Battery.description>Stores electricity for later use. Charged batteries explode when exposed to rain or fire.</Battery.description>
  
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>chemfuel powered generator</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming chemfuel. Must be periodically refueled by hand.</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>
  
  <GeothermalGenerator.label>geothermal generator</GeothermalGenerator.label>
  <GeothermalGenerator.description>Produces electricity from geothermal steam geysers. Must be placed on a steam geyser.</GeothermalGenerator.description>
  
  <HiddenConduit.label>hidden conduit</HiddenConduit.label>
  <HiddenConduit.description>Hidden electrical cables for moving power around. They're tougher than regular conduits, but also slower to build and more expensive.</HiddenConduit.description>
  
  <PowerConduit.label>power conduit</PowerConduit.label>
  <PowerConduit.description>A bundle of electrical cables for moving power around. Can be placed under walls and other buildings.</PowerConduit.description>
  
  <PowerSwitch.label>power switch</PowerSwitch.label>
  <PowerSwitch.description>Switches power on/off.</PowerSwitch.description>
  
  <SolarGenerator.label>solar generator</SolarGenerator.label>
  <SolarGenerator.description>Produces electricity from sunlight. Does not work in the dark or under artificial light.</SolarGenerator.description>
  
  <WatermillGenerator.label>watermill generator</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>Produces electricity from a river. Must be placed with its wheel in moving water. If watermills are placed too close together, the turbulence they generate will interfere and reduce power generation.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  
  <WaterproofConduit.label>waterproof conduit</WaterproofConduit.label>
  <WaterproofConduit.description>Insulated electrical cables for transmitting power under shallow water.</WaterproofConduit.description>
  
  <WindTurbine.label>wind turbine</WindTurbine.label>
  <WindTurbine.description>A wind-powered electrical generator. Requires a large clear space in front and behind for optimal air flow.</WindTurbine.description>
  
  <WoodFiredGenerator.label>wood-fired generator</WoodFiredGenerator.label>
  <WoodFiredGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming wood. Must be periodically loaded with wood fuel by hand.</WoodFiredGenerator.description>
</LanguageData>