<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Alpaca.label>alpaca</Alpaca.label>
  <Alpaca.description>A medium-sized ungulate closely related to the llama, the alpaca is usually raised for its remarkably soft and insulating wool. Alpacas have also been used as pack animals since they hauled cargo on the rugged mountain trails of ancient South America.</Alpaca.description>
  <Alpaca.tools.left_hoof.label>left hoof</Alpaca.tools.left_hoof.label>
  <Alpaca.tools.right_hoof.label>right hoof</Alpaca.tools.right_hoof.label>
  <Alpaca.tools.head.label>head</Alpaca.tools.head.label>
  
  <Capybara.label>capybara</Capybara.label>
  <Capybara.description>The largest natural rodent, the capybara is well-adapted for steaming jungle environments.</Capybara.description>
  <Capybara.tools.left_claw.label>left claw</Capybara.tools.left_claw.label>
  <Capybara.tools.right_claw.label>right claw</Capybara.tools.right_claw.label>
  <Capybara.tools.head.label>head</Capybara.tools.head.label>
  
  <Megasloth.label>megasloth</Megasloth.label>
  <Megasloth.description>A giant, solitary herbivore with two giant claws for warding off threats. Long extinct after being wiped out by the natives of Earth's American continent, the megasloth was later brought back using advanced cloning and artificial gestators. Its thick hide is exceptionally strong and insulating, and makes a great leather for cold-weather clothing. It is peaceful if left alone, but will shred anyone who disturbs it with its giant claws.</Megasloth.description>
  <Megasloth.tools.left_claw.label>left claw</Megasloth.tools.left_claw.label>
  <Megasloth.tools.right_claw.label>right claw</Megasloth.tools.right_claw.label>
  <Megasloth.tools.head.label>head</Megasloth.tools.head.label>
  
  <Sheep.label>sheep</Sheep.label>
  <Sheep.description>Sheep husbandry is practised throughout the majority of the inhabited worlds, however only recently it has been introduced to the rimworlds. Domestic sheep are relatively small herbivores, usually with yellowish wool and medium sized horns.</Sheep.description>
  <Sheep.tools.head.label>head</Sheep.tools.head.label>
  <Sheep.tools.left_hoof.label>left hoof</Sheep.tools.left_hoof.label>
  <Sheep.tools.right_hoof.label>right hoof</Sheep.tools.right_hoof.label>
</LanguageData>