<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <REN7_DarkChannelProjectile.label>dark channel</REN7_DarkChannelProjectile.label>
  <REN7_CarnageProjectile.label>high plasma projectile</REN7_CarnageProjectile.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyHelmet.label>N7 heavy helmet</REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyHelmet.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyHelmet.description>A heavy helmet with high armor.</REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyHelmet.description>
  <RE_Apparel_N7AdeptMask.label>N7 adept mask</RE_Apparel_N7AdeptMask.label>
  <RE_Apparel_N7AdeptMask.description>A mask with a hood. Greatly increases biotic energy regeneration rate.</RE_Apparel_N7AdeptMask.description>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7Helmet.label>N7 helmet</REN7_Apparel_N7Helmet.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7Helmet.description>A helmet with decent armor. Makes the wearer completely resistant to toxins.</REN7_Apparel_N7Helmet.description>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyArmor.label>N7 heavy armor</REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyArmor.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyArmor.description>A suit of incredibly damage-resistant powered armor, with a powerful overshield. It slows down the user when equipped, but provides best in class protection. Driven by eezo-assisted actuators, the N7 Destroyer soldiers carry heavy weapons onto the battlefield that no one else can match.</REN7_Apparel_N7HeavyArmor.description>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7AdeptSuit.label>N7 adept suit</REN7_Apparel_N7AdeptSuit.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7AdeptSuit.description>A full-body jumpsuit. The Fury suit greatly increases the biotic energy reserves of the user. \n\nThe N7 Furies are a terrifying and unpredictable sight on the battlefield. These operatives wind an unpredictable path on the battlefield, moving in and out of combat before returning to unleash a sweeping biotic attack on their unsuspecting targets.</REN7_Apparel_N7AdeptSuit.description>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7Armor.label>N7 armor</REN7_Apparel_N7Armor.label>
  <REN7_Apparel_N7Armor.description>A suit of powered armor with a powerful overshield. Armor ratings are decent. It also increases pain shock threshold and mental break threshold. \n\nThe bulwark of the N7 special forces, the N7 Paladin Sentinels are a welcome sight by all members of the alliance military. One of them on the battlefield can hold the line against all comers, and drastically reduces friendly casualty statistics.</REN7_Apparel_N7Armor.description>
  <REN7_Omnishield.tools.0.label>base</REN7_Omnishield.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Omnishield.tools.1.label>centre</REN7_Omnishield.tools.1.label>
  <REN7_Omnishield.label>omni shield</REN7_Omnishield.label>
  <REN7_Omnishield.description>An omni shield capable of intercepting a majority of ranged and melee attacks.</REN7_Omnishield.description>
  <REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.label>N7 blade</REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.label>
  <REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.description>A light monomolecular sword with high attack speed and armor penetration. \n\nThe favored weapon of the fearsome N7 Shadow Infiltrators. These blades are devastating in their hands, as they hide and then strike from the shadows in extreme close range.</REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.description>
  <REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.0.label>handle</REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.1.label>point</REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.1.label>
  <REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.2.label>edge</REN7_MeleeWeapon_N7Blade.tools.2.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7BattleRifle.label>accelerated shot</REN7_Bullet_N7BattleRifle.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.label>N7 battle rifle</REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.description>A mass accelerator battle rifle. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Valkyrie is a two-burst assault rifle with extreme range and good accuracy, but longer cooldown between shots. It is highly prized on the black market for it’s balance and effectiveness.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.tools.0.label>stock</REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.tools.1.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7BattleRifle.tools.1.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7LMG.label>accelerated shot</REN7_Bullet_N7LMG.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7LMG.label>N7 LMG</REN7_Gun_N7LMG.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7LMG.description>A mass accelerator heavy LMG. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Typhoon is an incredibly high penetration LMG that also applies a 10% chance to deflect any shot.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7LMG.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7LMG.tools.0.label>stock</REN7_Gun_N7LMG.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7LMG.tools.1.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7LMG.tools.1.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7Shotgun.label>accelerated blast</REN7_Bullet_N7Shotgun.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.label>N7 shotgun</REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.description>A mass accelerator heavy shotgun. Firing a spray of pellets lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles further shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Crusader shotgun sacrifices close range damage for the ability to fire at targets much farther away with effectiveness.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.tools.0.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7DMR.label>accelerated sniper shot</REN7_Bullet_N7DMR.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7DMR.label>N7 DMR</REN7_Gun_N7DMR.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7DMR.description>A mass accelerator designated marksman rifle. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Valiant is a 3 round burst rifle sacrificing some damage for extreme range.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7DMR.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7DMR.tools.0.label>stock</REN7_Gun_N7DMR.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7DMR.tools.1.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7DMR.tools.1.label>
  <RE_Bullet_N7Pistol.label>accelerated shot</RE_Bullet_N7Pistol.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7SMG.label>N7 SMG</REN7_Gun_N7SMG.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7SMG.description>A mass accelerator submachine gun. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Hurricane rapid-firing 4 burst SMG, one of the fastest-firing weapons ever produced. While some militaries find it to be too inaccurate, the N7 SpecOps soldiers prize it for its overwhelming amount of suppressive fire.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7SMG.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7SMG.tools.0.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7SMG.tools.0.label>
  <RE_Gun_N7Pistol.label>N7 pistol</RE_Gun_N7Pistol.label>
  <RE_Gun_N7Pistol.description>A mass accelerator autopistol. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Eagle is a fully automatic 3-burst pistol. While it is named after the famed Desert Eagle, its strengths lie not in its single-shot firepower, but in its ability to provide sustained automatic fire.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</RE_Gun_N7Pistol.description>
  <RE_Gun_N7Pistol.tools.0.label>barrel</RE_Gun_N7Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7AntimaterielRifle.label>accelerated anti-materiel shot</REN7_Bullet_N7AntimaterielRifle.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.label>N7 anti-materiel rifle</REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.description>A mass accelerator anti-materiel rifle. Firing slugs lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Black Widow is a very powerful armor piercing sniper rifle. A modified version of the Alliance Antimateriel Rifle with slightly less damage and shorter cooldown.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.tools.0.label>stock</REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.tools.1.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7AntimaterielRifle.tools.1.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.label>N7 black hole generator</REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.description>A single shot black hole gun. Creating an extremely powerful but unstable mass effect field, the rapidly-increasing gravity near the singularity's event horizon rips objects apart. \n\nThe M-490 Blackstorm fires a single slow projectile, but it draws all enemies into it, dealing heavy damage, and then explodes when it reaches its maximum distance. Absolutely devastating to groups of enemies.</REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.tools.0.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7BlackHoleGenerator.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Rocket_BlackHole.label>mini black hole</REN7_Rocket_BlackHole.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.label>N7 chain shotgun</REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.label>
  <REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.description>A mass accelerator light shotgun. Firing spray of pellets lightened by mass effect fields using precision electromagnetism, its projectiles shatter on impact to increase the damage to the target. \n\nThe Piranha is a powerful 2-burst shotgun with low cooldown but extremely short range. Designed for use by weaker soldiers who couldn’t handle the heavy recoil of other shotguns.\n\nThis weapon has a 10% chance to deal double damage.</REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.description>
  <REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.tools.0.label>barrel</REN7_Gun_N7ChainShotgun.tools.0.label>
  <REN7_Bullet_N7ChainShotgun.label>accelerated blast</REN7_Bullet_N7ChainShotgun.label>
</LanguageData>