<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AlpacaMorph.label>alpacamorph</AlpacaMorph.label>
  <AlpacaMorph.description>Alpacamorphs are rather woolly herbivorous humanoids who often have hooves. They produce good amounts of soft wool, which they can shave off themselves... and they don't need your help, thank you.</AlpacaMorph.description>
  <BearMorph.description>Bearmorphs are combat experts. Usually equipped with large claws, paws and maws, they are devastatingly dangerous up close. But they have a tender heart, and a soft spot for plush toys of the ursine variety.</BearMorph.description>
  <BearMorph.label>bearmorph</BearMorph.label>
  <PolarBearMorph.description>Bearmorphs are combat experts. Usually equipped with large claws, paws and maws, they are devastatingly dangerous up close. But they have a tender heart, and a soft spot for plush toys of the ursine variety.</PolarBearMorph.description>
  <PolarBearMorph.label>bearmorph</PolarBearMorph.label>
  <BoarMorph.label>boarmorph</BoarMorph.label>
  <BoarMorph.description>A humanoid with many boar like characteristics resulting when a human is exposed to boar specific mutagens. Usually found with thick hide and large tusks making them dangerous combatants.</BoarMorph.description>
  <BoomalopeMorph.label>boomamorph</BoomalopeMorph.label>
  <BoomalopeMorph.description>A humanoid sharing many characteristics with boomalopes, due to heavy mutagen exposure. They usually have thick hide, and an urge to seek out chemfuel.</BoomalopeMorph.description>
  <CatMorph.label>catmorph</CatMorph.label>
  <CatMorph.description>A human variant with many cat features. Uusually defined by a short whiskered muzzle, a long, thin tail and sharp clawed hands. They are faster and more dextrous than regular humans, and they have an advantage in melee.</CatMorph.description>
  <ChaocowMorph.description>A human variant with a large number of random mutations. With such a mish-mash of changes there is no easy way to categorize them, but based on key features like the ability to produce morph-milk, this one can be considered a "chaocow".</ChaocowMorph.description>
  <ChaocowMorph.label>chaocow morph</ChaocowMorph.label>
  <ChaoboomMorph.description>A human variant with a large number of random mutations. With such a mish-mash of changes there is no easy way to categorize them, but based on key features like the ability to produce chemfuel, this one can be considered a "chaoboom".</ChaoboomMorph.description>
  <ChaoboomMorph.label>ChaoboomMorph</ChaoboomMorph.label>
  <ChaofoxMorph.label>chaofox morph</ChaofoxMorph.label>
  <ChaofoxMorph.description>A human variant with a large number of random mutations. With such a mish-mash of changes there is no easy way to categorize them, but based on key features such as a swathes of fur and a vulpine snout, this one can be considered a "chaofox".</ChaofoxMorph.description>
  <ChaodinoMorph.description>A human variant with a large number of random mutations. With such a mish-mash of changes there is no easy way to categorize them, but based on key features like the ability to lay morph-eggs, this one can be considered a "chaodino".</ChaodinoMorph.description>
  <ChaodinoMorph.label>chaodino morph</ChaodinoMorph.label>
  <ChookMorph.label>chookmorph</ChookMorph.label>
  <ChookMorph.description>A human who now shares many features with chickens due to exposure to mechanite mutagens. Usually found covered in feathers, and arms more resembling wings. For odd reasons, both genders are capable of producing eggs.</ChookMorph.description>
  <SnakeMorph.label>cobramorph</SnakeMorph.label>
  <SnakeMorph.description>A large, muscular morph whose head and lower body are that of a snake. They have a venomous bite, so be mindful not to get on their bad side.</SnakeMorph.description>
  <PM_HellhoundMorph.label>hellhoundmorph</PM_HellhoundMorph.label>
  <PM_HellhoundMorph.description>A large, heavily mutated canid morph resembling a warg morph but significantly larger and usually with additional mutations.</PM_HellhoundMorph.description>
  <CougarMorph.label>cougarmorph</CougarMorph.label>
  <CougarMorph.description>!!!CougarMorph needs a description!!!</CougarMorph.description>
  <CowMorph.label>cowmorph</CowMorph.label>
  <CowMorph.description>A bovine humanoid resulting when a human is exposed to cow specific mutagens. Usually capable of producing milk.</CowMorph.description>
  <DeerMorph.label>deermorph</DeerMorph.label>
  <DeerMorph.description>A humanoid with many deer-like characteristics resulting from exposure to deer specific mutagens. They are often uncomfortable without others like them around.</DeerMorph.description>
  <DonkeyMorph.label>donkeymorph</DonkeyMorph.label>
  <DonkeyMorph.description>Donkeymorphs are strong pack morphs that often have hoofed feet and a broad snout that snorts when they get upset. They're very good haulers, but often rather stubborn.</DonkeyMorph.description>
  <ElephantMorph.label>elephantmorph</ElephantMorph.label>
  <ElephantMorph.description>A large human that has been exposed to large amounts of elephant specific mutagens. They usually have much in common with their feral counterparts like thick hide and large tusks, making them very dangerous in combat.</ElephantMorph.description>
  <ArcticFoxMorph.description>A somewhat smaller fox-like humanoid, often the result of exposure to the associated mutagens. In addition to physical changes, these humanoids now share many traits with their feral counterparts like their keen hunting instincts, especially towards chickens.</ArcticFoxMorph.description>
  <ArcticFoxMorph.label>foxmorph</ArcticFoxMorph.label>
  <FennecFoxMorph.description>A somewhat smaller fox-like humanoid, often the result of exposure to the associated mutagens. In addition to physical changes, these humanoids now share many traits with their feral counterparts like their keen hunting instincts, especially towards chickens.</FennecFoxMorph.description>
  <FennecFoxMorph.label>foxmorph</FennecFoxMorph.label>
  <FoxMorph.description>A somewhat smaller fox-like humanoid, often the result of exposure to the associated mutagens. In addition to physical changes, these humanoids now share many traits with their feral counterparts like their keen hunting instincts, especially towards chickens.</FoxMorph.description>
  <FoxMorph.label>foxmorph</FoxMorph.label>
  <HareMorph.description>The result of a mad scientist's attempt to take over the world, these docile creatures were designed to breed an army. Unfortunately for the morphs, they proved too timid to serve as proper militia and were abandoned soon after.</HareMorph.description>
  <HareMorph.label>haremorph</HareMorph.label>
  <SnowhareMorph.description>The result of a mad scientist's attempt to take over the world, these docile creatures were designed to breed an army. Unfortunately for the morphs, they proved too timid to serve as proper militia and were abandoned soon after.</SnowhareMorph.description>
  <SnowhareMorph.label>snowharemorph</SnowhareMorph.label>
  <HorseMorph.label>horsemorph</HorseMorph.label>
  <HorseMorph.description>Horsemorphs are strong pack morphs that often have hoofed feet and a broad snout that snorts when they get upset. They are quite fast, and useful for hauling.</HorseMorph.description>
  <HuskyMorph.label>huskymorph</HuskyMorph.label>
  <HuskyMorph.description>A large humanoid canine resembling a husky. These former humans now share many mental traits with their animal counterparts, such as pack-mindedness and keen hunting instincts.</HuskyMorph.description>
  <IguanaMorph.label>iguanamorph</IguanaMorph.label>
  <IguanaMorph.description>A scaly reptile morph with traits similar to that of an iguana.</IguanaMorph.description>
  <LynxMorph.label>lynxmorph</LynxMorph.label>
  <LynxMorph.description>!!!LynxMorph needs a description!!!</LynxMorph.description>
  <MegaslothMorph.label>slothmorph</MegaslothMorph.label>
  <MegaslothMorph.description>Slothmorphs are massive herbivorous humanoids covered in fluff. Their fur is very insulating, and can be shaved to make clothing, bedrolls and other fluffy stuff. And no, they won't be your pillow, so don't ask them (it's rude).</MegaslothMorph.description>
  <MonkeyMorph.label>monkeymorph</MonkeyMorph.label>
  <MonkeyMorph.description>A fun-loving morph type, Monkeymorphs tend to like playing pranks on their friends.</MonkeyMorph.description>
  <PantherMorph.label>panthermorph</PantherMorph.label>
  <PantherMorph.description>A large catlike morph covered in a sleek black fur. They are natural predators, and have the agility and killing power to prove it.</PantherMorph.description>
  <PigMorph.label>pigmorph</PigMorph.label>
  <PigMorph.description>A humanoid race resulting from a human being exposed to pig specific mutagens. They are often fond of looking through dirt and grass to find edible mushrooms.</PigMorph.description>
  <RaccoonMorph.label>raccoonmorph</RaccoonMorph.label>
  <RaccoonMorph.description>!!!RaccoonMorph needs a description!!!</RaccoonMorph.description>
  <RatMorph.label>ratmorph</RatMorph.label>
  <RatMorph.description>A smaller, ratlike humanoid. These former humans share many characteristics with rats, usually making them fragile in combat, but their dextrous paws make them good crafters and artists.</RatMorph.description>
  <RhinocerosMorph.label>rhinomorph</RhinocerosMorph.label>
  <RhinocerosMorph.description>!!!RhinocerosMorph needs a description!!!</RhinocerosMorph.description>
  <SheepMorph.label>sheepmorph</SheepMorph.label>
  <SheepMorph.description>With cute, fluffy wool and cuboid pupils, sheepmorphs are a 'farm'-type morph who can be shorn for wool. They often have hooves and are covered in wool that makes them useful in cold biomes.</SheepMorph.description>
  <SquirrelMorph.label>squirrelmorph</SquirrelMorph.label>
  <SquirrelMorph.description>A smaller, squirrel-like humanoid. These former humans share many characteristics with squirrels, usually making them fragile in combat, but their dextrous paws make them good crafters and artists.</SquirrelMorph.description>
  <ThrumboMorph.label>thrumbomorph</ThrumboMorph.label>
  <ThrumboMorph.description>A large humanoid often resembling a bipedal thrumbo, usually sporting the characteristic horn. Much like feral thrumbos they are exceptionally dangerous in combat, and enjoy eating trees.</ThrumboMorph.description>
  <TortoiseMorph.label>tortoisemorph</TortoiseMorph.label>
  <TortoiseMorph.description>Tortoisemorphs are defensive morphs characterised by their hard shell. While a shell does generally make them slower, conventional tortoises are slow due to energy conservation -- which is not necessarily an issue with morphs.</TortoiseMorph.description>
  <WargMorph.label>wargmorph</WargMorph.label>
  <WargMorph.description>A large humanoid canine resulting from a human that has been exposed to warg specific mutagens. Much like feral wargs, they are exceptionally dangerous in combat, and easily upset if there aren't other canines around.</WargMorph.description>
  <ArcticWolfMorph.description>Wolfmorphs usually stand on their paws and possess keen nose seeking prey, with grey or brown fur covering them. They make excellent fighters.</ArcticWolfMorph.description>
  <ArcticWolfMorph.label>arcticwolfmorph</ArcticWolfMorph.label>
  <WolfMorph.description>Wolfmorphs usually stand on their paws and possess keen nose seeking prey, with grey or brown fur covering them. They make excellent fighters.</WolfMorph.description>
  <WolfMorph.label>timberwolfmorph</WolfMorph.label>
</LanguageData>