<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <SoSArchotechEar.label>archotech ear</SoSArchotechEar.label>
  <SoSArchotechEar.description>An artifical ear built by an archotech. It can hear sounds as soft as a mosquito's heartbeat, but is selective enough to pick out a single word whispered in a crowded room. The outer portion can reshape itself at will and even generate various adornments. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechEar.description>
  <SoSArchotechNose.label>archotech nose</SoSArchotechNose.label>
  <SoSArchotechNose.description>An artifical nose built by an archotech. The outer portion can reshape itself at will to match a viewer's sense of beauty, improving the user's appearance. Its sensory apparatus is more sensitive than a bloodhound's, allowing pheromone-based communication with animals - and hence improving taming and training chances. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechNose.description>
  <SoSArchotechJaw.label>archotech jaw</SoSArchotechJaw.label>
  <SoSArchotechJaw.description>An artifical jaw built by an archotech. It can reshape itself at will to match a viewer's sense of beauty, and the voice it projects is simply sublime. This not only improves the user's appearance, but increases their social impact substantially. The muscles are strong enough to crush a femur, yet delicate enough to nibble a lover's neck. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechJaw.description>
  <SoSArchotechHeart.label>archotech heart</SoSArchotechHeart.label>
  <SoSArchotechHeart.description>An artifical heart built by an archotech. Although it never beats uncomfortably fast, it can sustain superhuman levels of athletic activity. It somehow modifies the bloodstream, causing blood to flow back into wounds. Users also report faster wound healing. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechHeart.description>
  <SoSArchotechLung.label>archotech lung</SoSArchotechLung.label>
  <SoSArchotechLung.description>An artifical lung built by an archotech. It can extract trace amounts of oxygen from planetary atmospheres that would kill a baseline human, and is immune to caustic gases. Even underwater or in a vacuum, a vanometrically-powered scrubber recycles carbon dioxide into oxygen. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechLung.description>
  <SoSArchotechStomach.label>archotech stomach</SoSArchotechStomach.label>
  <SoSArchotechStomach.description>An artifical stomach built by an archotech. It vanometrically provides all the power a body needs, and a module integrated with the lungs absorbs atoms from the air. The user (almost) never needs to eat again, though if they enjoy doing so, the stomach is still capable of breaking down food and is immune to food poisoning. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechStomach.description>
  <SoSArchotechKidney.label>archotech kidney</SoSArchotechKidney.label>
  <SoSArchotechKidney.description>An artifical kidney built by an archotech. It is capable of filtering out toxins, radioisotopes, and pathogens of all kinds. Users gain immunity more rapidly and can endure toxic exposure for longer. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechKidney.description>
  <SoSArchotechLiver.label>archotech liver</SoSArchotechLiver.label>
  <SoSArchotechLiver.description>An artifical liver built by an archotech. It is capable of breaking down any chemical toxin, and even neutralizing radioactive isotopes through exotic physics. In conjunction with archotech kidneys, it provides complete immunity to toxic exposure. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechLiver.description>
  <SoSArchotechSpine.label>archotech spine</SoSArchotechSpine.label>
  <SoSArchotechSpine.description>An artifical spine built by an archotech. Capable of bending in ways that would make a cat jealous, yet rigid enough to carry a small car if necessary. The user's drastically increased core strength improves their manipulation ability. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechSpine.description>
  <SoSArchotechSkin.label>archotech skin</SoSArchotechSkin.label>
  <SoSArchotechSkin.description>This small patch of artificial skin quickly spreads to cover the user's body. Archotech skin resists pressure changes and offers complete immunity to vaccum depressurization, as well as providing significant armor and temperature insulation. In conjunction with archotech lungs, it offers the ability to survive vacuum indefinitely. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but is harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</SoSArchotechSkin.description>
  <SoSPsychicPredictor.label>psychic predictor</SoSPsychicPredictor.label>
  <SoSPsychicPredictor.description>Gives limited mind-reading ability, allowing the user to track enemies' movements before they make them. This improves melee dodge chance and shooting accuracy, with an effect proportional to psychic sensitivity.</SoSPsychicPredictor.description>
  <SoSPsychicManipulator.label>psychic manipulator</SoSPsychicManipulator.label>
  <SoSPsychicManipulator.description>Gives limited telekinetic ability, allowing the user to lift or move small objects. This improves manipulation, with an effect proportional to psychic sensitivity.</SoSPsychicManipulator.description>
  <Archocat.label>archocat</Archocat.label>
  <Archocat.description>A perfected version of the domestic cat, this adorable ball of fluff wants nothing more than to spend its days playing with a ship's crew. In addition to frequent nuzzling, the archocat emits a psychic purr which improves nearby colonists' mood. It can technically be trained to "haul" by batting objects across the floor.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archocat.description>
  <Archocat.tools.0.label>left claw</Archocat.tools.0.label>
  <Archocat.tools.1.label>right claw</Archocat.tools.1.label>
  <Archocat.tools.3.label>head</Archocat.tools.3.label>
  <Archomutt.label>archomutt</Archomutt.label>
  <Archomutt.description>Man's best friend just got even better. The archomutt is a large, fiercely loyal dog with boundless energy for play - and the combat performance of a heavy mechanoid when its family is threatened. It also makes a fine working dog and can be taught to haul.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archomutt.description>
  <Archomutt.tools.0.label>left claw</Archomutt.tools.0.label>
  <Archomutt.tools.1.label>right claw</Archomutt.tools.1.label>
  <Archomutt.tools.3.label>head</Archomutt.tools.3.label>
  <Archostrich.label>archostrich</Archostrich.label>
  <Archostrich.description>Flightless but fierce, the archostrich plays an unusual role as both a food source and battle animal. This bird excels as the vanguard of combat operations; it moves faster than most cars, and its kick can shred plasteel. It psychically reads the preferred tastes of nearby humans and modifies its eggs accordingly.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archostrich.description>
  <Archostrich.tools.0.label>claws</Archostrich.tools.0.label>
  <Archostrich.tools.1.label>beak</Archostrich.tools.1.label>
  <Archostrich.tools.2.label>head</Archostrich.tools.2.label>
  <EggArchostrichFertilized.label>archostrich egg (fert.)</EggArchostrichFertilized.label>
  <EggArchostrichFertilized.description>A fertilized archostrich egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby archostrich. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggArchostrichFertilized.description>
  <EggArchostrichUnfertilized.label>archostrich egg (unfert.)</EggArchostrichUnfertilized.label>
  <EggArchostrichUnfertilized.description>An unfertilized archostrich egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</EggArchostrichUnfertilized.description>
  <Archoffalo.label>archoffalo</Archoffalo.label>
  <Archoffalo.description>Your archotech spore respects the Rim's desire not to use ground vehicles, and so has designed the archoffalo to replace them. The beast's prehensile hair is capable of shaping and hardening to form bags, platforms, or any other structure required to carry cargo. When it gets too long, it can be sheared for hyperweave.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archoffalo.description>
  <Archoffalo.tools.0.label>head</Archoffalo.tools.0.label>
  <Archoffalo.tools.1.label>left hoof</Archoffalo.tools.1.label>
  <Archoffalo.tools.2.label>right hoof</Archoffalo.tools.2.label>
  <Archospider.label>archospider</Archospider.label>
  <Archospider.description>Perhaps your archotech spore hates arachnophobes. There are few other excuses for creating this monstrous life-form - a spider with tank-like armor, jaws capable of shearing plasteel, and a breeding rate that threatens to quickly overwhelm a planet's ecosystem. At least it is unfailingly loyal to its masters... so far.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archospider.description>
  <Archospider.tools.0.label>head claw</Archospider.tools.0.label>
  <Archospider.tools.1.label>head</Archospider.tools.1.label>
  <Archospider.race.meatLabel>insect meat</Archospider.race.meatLabel>
  <Archolope.label>archolope</Archolope.label>
  <Archolope.description>An elegant refinement of the standard boomalope, the archolope somehow generates exotic particles, safely contained in fullerene shells within the molecular structure of its "milk." Whatever process produces them seems inherently unstable - when an archolope dies, it unleashes thermonuclear fury.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archolope.description>
  <Archolope.tools.0.label>head</Archolope.tools.0.label>
  <Archolope.tools.1.label>left hoof</Archolope.tools.1.label>
  <Archolope.tools.2.label>right hoof</Archolope.tools.2.label>
  <Archotortoise.label>archotortoise</Archotortoise.label>
  <Archotortoise.description>The archotortoise is nothing less than a mobile fortress. Armored with biologically-secreted plasteel, it can confidently stride into any melee. During peacetime its shell can be harvested for individual plasteel plates without harming it.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archotortoise.description>
  <Archotortoise.tools.0.label>beak</Archotortoise.tools.0.label>
  <Archotortoise.tools.1.label>head</Archotortoise.tools.1.label>
  <EggArchotortoiseFertilized.label>archotortoise egg (fert.)</EggArchotortoiseFertilized.label>
  <EggArchotortoiseFertilized.description>A fertilized archotortoise egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a baby archotortoise. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</EggArchotortoiseFertilized.description>
  <Archopanda.label>archopanda</Archopanda.label>
  <Archopanda.description>Sometimes referred to as a "living teddy bear," the archopanda makes an ideal pet for anyone who appreciates being knocked off their feet by an enthusiastic nuzzle. Its gentle nature prevents it from being much use in combat, but it can be trained to haul and to carry goods in a caravan.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archopanda.description>
  <Archopanda.tools.0.label>left claw</Archopanda.tools.0.label>
  <Archopanda.tools.1.label>right claw</Archopanda.tools.1.label>
  <Archopanda.tools.3.label>head</Archopanda.tools.3.label>
  <Archopanda.race.meatLabel>bear meat</Archopanda.race.meatLabel>
  <Archojerboa.label>archojerboa</Archojerboa.label>
  <Archojerboa.description>This hyperactive rodent is capable of great leaps, often landing on an owner's shoulder to chirp in their ear. It makes an excellent pet, and its breeding rate ensures that everyone aboard your ship can have one. In an emergency, the archojerboa can also be used as live ammunition - its unstable vanometrics result in an explosion upon death.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archojerboa.description>
  <Archojerboa.tools.0.label>left claw</Archojerboa.tools.0.label>
  <Archojerboa.tools.1.label>right claw</Archojerboa.tools.1.label>
  <Archojerboa.tools.3.label>head</Archojerboa.tools.3.label>
  <Archothrumbo.label>archothrumbo</Archothrumbo.label>
  <Archothrumbo.description>Can perfection be improved upon? Your archotech spore answers with a resounding [YES]. The archothrumbo is every bit as gorgeous and powerful as its predecessor, without the ravenous appetite. Its horn can wreathe itself in fire like a plasmasword, and its hooves release an EMP with each strike. There is no deadlier battle animal than this mythic beast.\n\nLike all archolife, its cells power themselves vanometrically and it absorbs atoms directly from the air, so it does not need to eat. Archolife can survive vacuum exposure, has no known maximum age, and regenerates scarred or missing body parts. It can even generate a shield in combat.</Archothrumbo.description>
  <Archothrumbo.tools.0.label>horn</Archothrumbo.tools.0.label>
  <Archothrumbo.tools.2.label>left foot</Archothrumbo.tools.2.label>
  <Archothrumbo.tools.3.label>right foot</Archothrumbo.tools.3.label>
  <Archothrumbo.tools.4.label>head</Archothrumbo.tools.4.label>
  <ShuttlePersonalRace.label>Personal Shuttle (hover mode)</ShuttlePersonalRace.label>
  <ShuttlePersonalRace.description>A personal shuttle set to hover mode, allowing it to be used as part of a caravan.</ShuttlePersonalRace.description>
  <ShuttleCargoRace.label>Cargo Shuttle (hover mode)</ShuttleCargoRace.label>
  <ShuttleCargoRace.description>A cargo shuttle set to hover mode, allowing it to be used as part of a caravan.</ShuttleCargoRace.description>
  <ShuttleHeavyRace.label>Heavy Cargo Shuttle (hover mode)</ShuttleHeavyRace.label>
  <ShuttleHeavyRace.description>A heavy cargo shuttle set to hover mode, allowing it to be used as part of a caravan.</ShuttleHeavyRace.description>
  <Astromite.label>astromite</Astromite.label>
  <Astromite.description>A large, genetically-engineered mite. Thick chitin plates and an anaerobic metabolism allow it to survive in space. Originally designed as part of an organic asteroid-mining system, the project was abandoned when the hives proved too difficult to control. Like other eusocial arthropods, it cannot reproduce individually.</Astromite.description>
  <Astromite.tools.0.label>mandibles</Astromite.tools.0.label>
  <Astromite.tools.1.label>head</Astromite.tools.1.label>
  <Stellapede.label>stellapede</Stellapede.label>
  <Stellapede.description>A vacuum-adapted variant of the familiar spelopede, the stellapede's anaerobic metabolism allows it to survive in space indefinitely. It appears to subsist primarily on minerals, but will eagerly hunt any organic prey it senses.</Stellapede.description>
  <Stellapede.tools.0.label>head claw</Stellapede.tools.0.label>
  <Stellapede.tools.1.label>head</Stellapede.tools.1.label>
  <Cosmopillar.label>cosmopillar</Cosmopillar.label>
  <Cosmopillar.description>This tremendous grub holds the dubious honor of "most disgusting creature in space." Chewing through solid stone and leaving a tunnel lubricated by its own slime, the cosmopillar was originally engineered as the vanguard of a hive of asteroid-mining insects. The project has long since been abandoned, but all throughout the Rim, asteroid miners live in fear of hungry cosmopillars.\n\nRumors persist that the oldest cosmopillars enter a deep hibernation at the center of asteroids, where their unstable genetics cause them to pupate into something even more terrible...</Cosmopillar.description>
  <Cosmopillar.tools.0.label>head claw</Cosmopillar.tools.0.label>
  <Cosmopillar.tools.1.label>head</Cosmopillar.tools.1.label>
  <Cosmopillar.race.meatLabel>insect meat</Cosmopillar.race.meatLabel>
  <ShipArchotechSpore.label>archotech spore</ShipArchotechSpore.label>
  <ShipArchotechSpore.description>The core of a machine persona that has begun upgrading itself into an archotech.\n\nThe vast majority of its computational power is focused inward, contemplating its own structure and other unknowable mysteries, but enough is left over to serve as a ship's computer core.\n\nIts mood can be improved by having colonists meditate nearby, or by sacrificing prisoners to it. Should its mood dip too low, it might decide to play "pranks."\n\nBuilding more than one archotech spore will not produce gifts more frequently, but they will develop psychic field strength independently.</ShipArchotechSpore.description>
  <ShipArchotechPillarA.label>archotech pillar alpha</ShipArchotechPillarA.label>
  <ShipArchotechPillarA.description>A complex and bizarre apparatus which serves no human-comprehensible purpose, but which will apparently advance the plans of your archotech spore in some way.\n\nThere is no benefit to building more than one copy of the same pillar.</ShipArchotechPillarA.description>
  <ShipArchotechPillarB.label>archotech pillar beta</ShipArchotechPillarB.label>
  <ShipArchotechPillarB.description>A complex and bizarre apparatus which serves no human-comprehensible purpose, but which will apparently advance the plans of your archotech spore in some way.\n\nThere is no benefit to building more than one copy of the same pillar.</ShipArchotechPillarB.description>
  <ShipArchotechPillarC.label>archotech pillar gamma</ShipArchotechPillarC.label>
  <ShipArchotechPillarC.description>A complex and bizarre apparatus which serves no human-comprehensible purpose, but which will apparently advance the plans of your archotech spore in some way.\n\nThere is no benefit to building more than one copy of the same pillar.</ShipArchotechPillarC.description>
  <ShipArchotechPillarD.label>archotech pillar delta</ShipArchotechPillarD.label>
  <ShipArchotechPillarD.description>A complex and bizarre apparatus which serves no human-comprehensible purpose, but which will apparently advance the plans of your archotech spore in some way.\n\nThere is no benefit to building more than one copy of the same pillar.</ShipArchotechPillarD.description>
  <ArchotechUplink.label>archotech uplink</ArchotechUplink.label>
  <ArchotechUplink.description>Allows human researchers to collaborate with a fraction of your archotech spore's mind. Place near a high-tech research bench to unlock archotech projects. Each research bench can only use one uplink.</ArchotechUplink.description>
  <ShipHullTileArchotech.label>archotech hull plating</ShipHullTileArchotech.label>
  <ShipHullTileArchotech.description>Spaceworthy hull plating designed by an archotech.</ShipHullTileArchotech.description>
  <Ship_BeamArchotech.label>archotech ship hull</Ship_BeamArchotech.label>
  <Ship_BeamArchotech.description>The outer structural elements of an archotech-designed ship's hull. Includes conduits for power and coolant.</Ship_BeamArchotech.description>
  <Ship_BeamArchotech_Unpowered.label>archotech ship hull (unpowered)</Ship_BeamArchotech_Unpowered.label>
  <Ship_BeamArchotech_Unpowered.description>The outer structural elements of an archotech-designed ship's hull. Does not include conduits for power or coolant.</Ship_BeamArchotech_Unpowered.description>
  <ShipHeatsinkAntiEntropy.label>anti-entropic heatsink</ShipHeatsinkAntiEntropy.label>
  <ShipHeatsinkAntiEntropy.description>An advanced heatsink designed by an archotech. Uses exotic physics to convert excess heat back into usable energy.</ShipHeatsinkAntiEntropy.description>
  <ArchotechShieldGenerator.label>archotech shield generator</ArchotechShieldGenerator.label>
  <ArchotechShieldGenerator.description>A shielding device which projects a momentum repulsor field. Shots can go out, but not in.\n\nGenerates 75% of a standard shield's heat when it blocks attacks. If no heatsink capacity is available, the shield will be damaged and require repairs.\n\nShip radiators cannot disperse heat while shields are up. Captains are advised to drop shields once heatsinks are close to capacity, or risk their ships turning into ovens.</ArchotechShieldGenerator.description>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelPsychic.label>spinal barrel: psychic flayer</ShipSpinalBarrelPsychic.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelPsychic.description>The final segment of a spinal-mount cannon. Fires a beam of directed psychic trauma that stuns crew and will likely cause brain damage. Ignores hull (but not shields). Unlike other spinal weapons, the psychic flayer cannot damage your own ship.</ShipSpinalBarrelPsychic.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.label>spinal-mount cannon</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.label>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.description>Capital ship weaponry.</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.verbs.0.label>shoot</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPsychic.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Psychic.label>psychic blast</Bullet_Fake_Psychic.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretPsychic.label>psychic blast</Proj_ShipTurretPsychic.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelMechanite.label>spinal barrel: disassembler</ShipSpinalBarrelMechanite.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelMechanite.description>The final segment of a spinal-mount cannon. A modified railgun which launches globs of disassembler mechanites. Should be placed outside the ship, unless you want a new hole in your hull.</ShipSpinalBarrelMechanite.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.label>spinal-mount cannon</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.label>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.description>Capital ship weaponry.</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.verbs.0.label>shoot</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopMechanite.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Mechanite.label>mechanite glob</Bullet_Fake_Mechanite.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretMechanite.label>mechanite glob</Proj_ShipTurretMechanite.label>
  <MechaniteFire.label>disassembler mechanites</MechaniteFire.label>
  <MechaniteSpark.label>disassembler mechanites</MechaniteSpark.label>
  <Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.label>mechanite cocktails</Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.label>
  <Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.description>Glass bottles filled with disassembler mechanites. A favorite weapon of extremely advanced hooligans.</Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.description>
  <Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.verbs.0.label>throw mechanites</Weapon_GrenadeMechanite.verbs.0.label>
  <Proj_GrenadeMechanite.label>mechanite cocktail</Proj_GrenadeMechanite.label>
  <ArchoRecycler.label>recyclotron</ArchoRecycler.label>
  <ArchoRecycler.description>Uses mechanites to break down any object into its base materials, with near perfect efficiency.</ArchoRecycler.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOne.label>archotech hull corner (1x1)</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOne.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOne.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by an archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOne.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOneFlip.label>archotech hull corner (1x1) flip</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOneFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOneFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by an archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneOneFlip.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwo.label>archotech hull corner (1x2)</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwo.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwo.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by an archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwo.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwoFlip.label>archotech hull corner (1x2) flip</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwoFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwoFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by a archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneTwoFlip.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThree.label>archotech hull corner (1x3)</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThree.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThree.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by an archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThree.description>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThreeFlip.label>archotech hull corner (1x3) flip</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThreeFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThreeFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull, designed by an archotech.</Ship_Corner_Archo_OneThreeFlip.description>
  <ShipAirlockArchotech.label>archotech ship airlock</ShipAirlockArchotech.label>
  <ShipAirlockArchotech.description>Allows access to a ship or divides rooms inside it. Low-energy plasma barriers prevent gases from escaping.</ShipAirlockArchotech.description>
  <Holodeck_Basic.label>basic holodeck</Holodeck_Basic.label>
  <Holodeck_Basic.description>A makeshift hologram emitter connected to a gaming PC. Capable of only simple simulations. Users will slowly gain skill points depending on the chosen sim.</Holodeck_Basic.description>
  <Holodeck_Standard.label>advanced holodeck</Holodeck_Standard.label>
  <Holodeck_Standard.description>A state-of-the-art holoprojector equipped with a wide range of simulations. Very entertaining. The user will gain skill points depending on the chosen sim.</Holodeck_Standard.description>
  <Holodeck_AI.label>sapient holodeck</Holodeck_AI.label>
  <Holodeck_AI.description>A state-of-the-art holoprojector controlled by an AI. Its creativity allows for endless entertainment, customized to the user's tastes. The user will quickly gain skill points depending on the chosen sim.</Holodeck_AI.description>
  <ShipHullTileMech.label>mechanoid hull plating</ShipHullTileMech.label>
  <ShipHullTileMech.description>Spaceworthy hull plating built by mechanoids.</ShipHullTileMech.description>
  <Ship_BeamMech.label>mechanoid ship hull</Ship_BeamMech.label>
  <Ship_BeamMech.description>The outer structural elements of a mechanoid ship's hull. Includes conduits for power and coolant.</Ship_BeamMech.description>
  <Ship_BeamMech_Unpowered.label>mechanoid ship hull (unpowered)</Ship_BeamMech_Unpowered.label>
  <Ship_BeamMech_Unpowered.description>The outer structural elements of a mechanoid ship's hull. Does not include conduits for power or coolant.</Ship_BeamMech_Unpowered.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne_Mech.label>hull corner (1x1)</Ship_Corner_OneOne_Mech.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne_Mech.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneOne_Mech.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne_MechFlip.label>hull corner (1x1) flip</Ship_Corner_OneOne_MechFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne_MechFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneOne_MechFlip.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwo_Mech.label>hull corner (1x2)</Ship_Corner_OneTwo_Mech.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwo_Mech.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneTwo_Mech.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThree_Mech.label>hull corner (1x3)</Ship_Corner_OneThree_Mech.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThree_Mech.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneThree_Mech.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip_Mech.label>hull corner (1x2)</Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip_Mech.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip_Mech.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip_Mech.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip_Mech.label>hull corner (1x3)</Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip_Mech.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip_Mech.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip_Mech.description>
  <ShipAirlockMech.label>mechanoid ship airlock</ShipAirlockMech.label>
  <ShipAirlockMech.description>Allows access to a ship or divides rooms inside it. Low-energy plasma barriers prevent gases from escaping.</ShipAirlockMech.description>
  <ShipChunkSalvage.label>ship salvage</ShipChunkSalvage.label>
  <ShipChunkSalvage.description>Advanced spacecraft systems, relatively intact. Can be deconstructed to yield spacer components.</ShipChunkSalvage.description>
  <Space_Satellite_Core.label>satellite core</Space_Satellite_Core.label>
  <Space_Satellite_Core.description>The core of an ancient communications nexus. Repairing this will take considerable skill, and once repaired, the system will also need to be hacked by a skilled researcher. Either step can result in the activation of defense systems.\n\nThe spoils of victory are great, however - this satellite could be used as a backdoor into ancient orbital bombardment, solar energy collection, or weather-control arrays.\n\nAlternatively, you could simply deconstruct it, but this is virtually guaranteed to provoke defenses.</Space_Satellite_Core.description>
  <Ship_DamagedReactor.label>damaged reactor</Ship_DamagedReactor.label>
  <Ship_DamagedReactor.description>An ancient, badly damaged fission reactor. Until it is shut down, it will inflict severe radiation sickness on any nearby creature.</Ship_DamagedReactor.description>
  <Ship_LabConsole.label>lab console</Ship_LabConsole.label>
  <Ship_LabConsole.description>An ancient but functional control console. A skilled researcher might be able to use this to shut down the ship's reactors.</Ship_LabConsole.description>
  <Ship_SecurityConsole.label>security console</Ship_SecurityConsole.label>
  <Ship_SecurityConsole.description>An ancient but functional control console. A skilled researcher could use this to open the ship's locked doors.</Ship_SecurityConsole.description>
  <BlackBoxAI.label>insane AI</BlackBoxAI.label>
  <BlackBoxAI.description>The ancient ship's AI core. Hostile, psychically capable, and deeply disturbed. Only the most gifted negotiators would have any hope of talking it out of suicide, and you will only get one chance at this.</BlackBoxAI.description>
  <JTDriveSalvage.label>Ancient Johnson-Tanaka drive</JTDriveSalvage.label>
  <JTDriveSalvage.description>An advanced reactionless engine capable of interplanetary and interstellar travel. Damaged by re-entry but still mostly functional.\n\nSafely opening the drive to reverse-engineer it will require a lengthy momentum discharge process, which is certain to attract raiders.</JTDriveSalvage.description>
  <SpaceHive.label>hive</SpaceHive.label>
  <SpaceHive.description>A hive of giant insects. If activated, it will spawn additional insects and hives over time, as well as valuable insect jelly.</SpaceHive.description>
  <Ship_Beam_Wrecked.label>wrecked hull</Ship_Beam_Wrecked.label>
  <Ship_Beam_Wrecked.description>The outer structural elements of a ship's hull. Damaged beyond repair.</Ship_Beam_Wrecked.description>
  <Ship_Beam_Wrecked_Fake.label>wrecked hull</Ship_Beam_Wrecked_Fake.label>
  <Ship_Beam_Wrecked_Fake.description>The outer structural elements of a ship's hull. Damaged beyond repair.</Ship_Beam_Wrecked_Fake.description>
  <ShipHullTileWrecked.label>hull wreckage</ShipHullTileWrecked.label>
  <ShipHullTileWrecked.description>Wreckage of a ship's hull. No longer spaceworthy.</ShipHullTileWrecked.description>
  <ShipHullTileWreckedFake.label>hull wreckage</ShipHullTileWreckedFake.label>
  <ShipHullTileWreckedFake.description>Wreckage of a ship's hull. No longer spaceworthy.</ShipHullTileWreckedFake.description>
  <ShipAirlockWrecked.label>damaged airlock</ShipAirlockWrecked.label>
  <ShipAirlockWrecked.description>The wreckage of an airlock, barely able to maintain minimum pressure.</ShipAirlockWrecked.description>
  <Ship_Beam_Unpowered.label>ship hull (unpowered)</Ship_Beam_Unpowered.label>
  <Ship_Beam_Unpowered.description>The outer structural elements of a ship's hull. Does not include conduits for power or coolant.</Ship_Beam_Unpowered.description>
  <Ship_Beam.label>ship hull</Ship_Beam.label>
  <Ship_Beam.description>The outer structural elements of a ship's hull. Includes conduits for power, life-support gases, and coolant.</Ship_Beam.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne.label>hull corner (1x1)</Ship_Corner_OneOne.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOne.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneOne.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOneFlip.label>hull corner (1x1) flip</Ship_Corner_OneOneFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneOneFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneOneFlip.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwo.label>hull corner (1x2)</Ship_Corner_OneTwo.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwo.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneTwo.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip.label>hull corner (1x2) flip</Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneTwoFlip.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThree.label>hull corner (1x3)</Ship_Corner_OneThree.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThree.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneThree.description>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip.label>hull corner (1x3) flip</Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip.label>
  <Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip.description>Angled armor for a ship's outer hull.</Ship_Corner_OneThreeFlip.description>
  <ShipInside_SolarGenerator.label>solar generator</ShipInside_SolarGenerator.label>
  <ShipInside_SolarGenerator.description>Produces electricity from sunlight. Does not work in the dark or under artificial light.</ShipInside_SolarGenerator.description>
  <ShipInside_PassiveCooler.label>ship radiator</ShipInside_PassiveCooler.label>
  <ShipInside_PassiveCooler.description>Radiates heat into the void, cooling a ship's interior. Also provides a small amount of heat capacity to weapons and shields. Cannot vent heat while shields are up.</ShipInside_PassiveCooler.description>
  <ShipInside_PassiveVent.label>ship vent</ShipInside_PassiveVent.label>
  <ShipInside_PassiveVent.description>Exchanges heat into the coolant network, cooling a ship's interior.</ShipInside_PassiveVent.description>
  <ShipAirlock.label>ship airlock</ShipAirlock.label>
  <ShipAirlock.description>Allows access to a ship or divides rooms inside it. Low-energy plasma barriers prevent gases from escaping.</ShipAirlock.description>
  <ShipHullTile.label>hull plating</ShipHullTile.label>
  <ShipHullTile.description>Spaceworthy hull plating. Designates this tile (and any objects built on it) as part of a ship. Must be placed inside an outer hull.</ShipHullTile.description>
  <ShipHardpointSmall.label>small hardpoint</ShipHardpointSmall.label>
  <ShipHardpointSmall.description>Support structure for attaching buildings and turrets to a ship's exterior. Anything built atop this will be considered part of the ship.\n\nIntegrated nano-composite armor reduces damage to turrets placed atop this hardpoint by 75%.</ShipHardpointSmall.description>
  <ShipHardpoint.label>hardpoint</ShipHardpoint.label>
  <ShipHardpoint.description>Support structure for attaching buildings and turrets to a ship's exterior. Anything built atop this will be considered part of the ship.\n\nIntegrated nano-composite armor reduces damage to turrets placed atop this hardpoint by 75%.</ShipHardpoint.description>
  <ShipHardpointExtraMedium.label>large hardpoint</ShipHardpointExtraMedium.label>
  <ShipHardpointExtraMedium.description>Support structure for attaching buildings and turrets to a ship's exterior. Anything built atop this will be considered part of the ship.\n\nIntegrated nano-composite armor reduces damage to turrets placed atop this hardpoint by 75%.</ShipHardpointExtraMedium.description>
  <ShipHardpointLarge.label>XL hardpoint</ShipHardpointLarge.label>
  <ShipHardpointLarge.description>Support structure for attaching buildings and turrets to a ship's exterior. Anything built atop this will be considered part of the ship.\n\nIntegrated nano-composite armor reduces damage to turrets placed atop this hardpoint by 75%.</ShipHardpointLarge.description>
  <Ship_Engine_Small.label>small rocket engine</Ship_Engine_Small.label>
  <Ship_Engine_Small.description>A chemfuel-powered engine capable of launching a ship into orbit. Not suitable for interplanetary travel.</Ship_Engine_Small.description>
  <Ship_Engine.label>rocket engine</Ship_Engine.label>
  <Ship_Engine.description>A chemfuel-powered engine capable of launching a ship into orbit. Not suitable for interplanetary travel.\n\nIn combat, provides double the speed of smaller engines at the cost of double fuel consumption.</Ship_Engine.description>
  <Ship_Engine_Large.label>nuclear engine</Ship_Engine_Large.label>
  <Ship_Engine_Large.description>A nuclear-powered engine capable of launching a ship into orbit, at the cost of irradiating the surrounding area. Not suitable for interplanetary travel.\n\nProvides six times the speed of small engines.</Ship_Engine_Large.description>
  <Ship_Engine_Interplanetary.label>Johnson-Tanaka drive</Ship_Engine_Interplanetary.label>
  <Ship_Engine_Interplanetary.description>An advanced reactionless engine capable of interplanetary and interstellar travel. Not suitable for use in combat.</Ship_Engine_Interplanetary.description>
  <ShipPilotSeatMini.label>minimal ship bridge</ShipPilotSeatMini.label>
  <ShipPilotSeatMini.description>Allows colonists to pilot a starship into orbit. Unlike its larger counterpart, cannot be used to scan for orbital sites, and suffers reduced accuracy and engine speed when used in combat.</ShipPilotSeatMini.description>
  <ShipPilotSeat.label>ship bridge</ShipPilotSeat.label>
  <ShipPilotSeat.description>Allows colonists to pilot a starship into orbit. Once in orbit, it can also be used to scan for objects of interest.</ShipPilotSeat.description>
  <Ship_ComputerCore.label>ship computer core</Ship_ComputerCore.label>
  <Ship_ComputerCore.description>A computer core capable of housing a superhumanlike AI who can guide a ship on interstellar journeys. Once in orbit, automatically scans for nearby sites of interest.</Ship_ComputerCore.description>
  <Ship_SensorCluster.label>basic sensors</Ship_SensorCluster.label>
  <Ship_SensorCluster.description>Basic ship sensors. Capable of detecting nearby craft and observing sites from orbit.</Ship_SensorCluster.description>
  <Ship_SensorClusterAdv.label>advanced sensors</Ship_SensorClusterAdv.label>
  <Ship_SensorClusterAdv.description>Advanced ship sensors. Capable of scanning the interiors of enemy ships and observing sites from orbit.</Ship_SensorClusterAdv.description>
  <Ship_LifeSupport.label>Life Support System</Ship_LifeSupport.label>
  <Ship_LifeSupport.description>Recycles oxygen in all fully-enclosed ship rooms. Required to keep non-cryptosleeping colonists and animals alive.</Ship_LifeSupport.description>
  <Ship_LifeSupport_Small.label>Small Life Support System</Ship_LifeSupport_Small.label>
  <Ship_LifeSupport_Small.description>Recycles oxygen in all fully-enclosed ship rooms. Required to keep non-cryptosleeping colonists and animals alive.\n\n This version sacrifices power efficiency for a more compact design that can fit on small ships.</Ship_LifeSupport_Small.description>
  <ShipCapacitor.label>capacitor array</ShipCapacitor.label>
  <ShipCapacitor.description>Efficiently stores up to 100,000Wd of energy.</ShipCapacitor.description>
  <ShipCapacitorSmall.label>ship capacitor</ShipCapacitorSmall.label>
  <ShipCapacitorSmall.description>Efficiently stores up to 10,000Wd of energy.</ShipCapacitorSmall.description>
  <Ship_Reactor.label>ship fission reactor</Ship_Reactor.label>
  <Ship_Reactor.description>A compact, self-contained fission reactor. Burns uranium fuel pods. Vents heat into a heatsink network if available, or into the surrounding room if not.\n\nIts base power production of 10,000W can be boosted with several increasingly risky overdrive modes.</Ship_Reactor.description>
  <ShipShuttleBay.label>shuttle bay</ShipShuttleBay.label>
  <ShipShuttleBay.description>Provides docking facilities for one shuttle. Must be kept clear of obstructions.</ShipShuttleBay.description>
  <ShipSalvageBay.label>salvage bay</ShipSalvageBay.label>
  <ShipSalvageBay.description>Harvests the remains of enemy ships after a battle. Each salvage bay can retrieve up to 1,000kg of material from a ship.</ShipSalvageBay.description>
  <Ship_CryptosleepCasket.label>auto-eject cryptosleep casket</Ship_CryptosleepCasket.label>
  <Ship_CryptosleepCasket.description>A cryptosleep casket with multiple built-in timers and contingencies. Can be opened without manual intervention. In the event of catastrophic ship failure, it can also act as an escape pod.\n\nIt would be a good idea to have at least one of these aboard any starship.</Ship_CryptosleepCasket.description>
  <CrittersleepCasket.label>crittersleep caskets (8)</CrittersleepCasket.label>
  <CrittersleepCasket.description>An array of self-powered sarcophagi capable of keeping up to eight small animals in stasis. Animals should be medically anesthetized before being placed into cryptosleep.</CrittersleepCasket.description>
  <CrittersleepCasketLarge.label>crittersleep caskets (32)</CrittersleepCasketLarge.label>
  <CrittersleepCasketLarge.description>A large array of self-powered sarcophagi capable of keeping up to thirty-two small animals in stasis. Animals should be medically anesthetized before being placed into cryptosleep.</CrittersleepCasketLarge.description>
  <Cryptonest.label>cryptonest</Cryptonest.label>
  <Cryptonest.description>A self-powered sarcophagus capable of keeping up to sixteen eggs in stasis.</Cryptonest.description>
  <ShipMoveBlueprint.label>New Ship Position</ShipMoveBlueprint.label>
  <ShipMoveBlueprint.description>Select where you would like to move the ship.</ShipMoveBlueprint.description>
  <DetachedShipPart.label>Detached Ship Part</DetachedShipPart.label>
  <DetachedShipPart.description>A destroyed portion of a spaceship.</DetachedShipPart.description>
  <MinifiedThingShipMove.label>minified thing</MinifiedThingShipMove.label>
  <Ship_FakeBeam.label>ship hull</Ship_FakeBeam.label>
  <Ship_FakeBeam.description>The outer structural elements of a ship's hull. Includes conduits for power, life-support gases, and coolant.</Ship_FakeBeam.description>
  <HullFoamWall.label>hullfoam</HullFoamWall.label>
  <HullFoamWall.description>An airtight slab of hullfoam.</HullFoamWall.description>
  <ShipHullfoamTile.label>hullfoam plating</ShipHullfoamTile.label>
  <ShipHullfoamTile.description>Airtight hullfoam, sprayed to replace a missing hull plate.</ShipHullfoamTile.description>
  <ShipCloakingDevice.label>cloaking device</ShipCloakingDevice.label>
  <ShipCloakingDevice.description>Generates a field which masks heat emissions, hiding your ship from passive scans. This prevents random ship battles from starting, but is not helpful once combat has already begun. It also cannot protect you from the powerful scanners used to find ships with high Notoriety.\n\nWhile the device is active, your ship's radiators will be disabled and heat will accumulate.</ShipCloakingDevice.description>
  <ShipHeatConduit.label>thermal conduit</ShipHeatConduit.label>
  <ShipHeatConduit.description>A liquid conduit for moving heat around a starship.</ShipHeatConduit.description>
  <ShipHeatsink.label>heatsink</ShipHeatsink.label>
  <ShipHeatsink.description>A liquid-cooled heatsink for storing excess heat from weapons fire. Slowly bleeds heat into the surrounding room; will not function in vacuum.</ShipHeatsink.description>
  <ShipHeatsinkLarge.label>large heatsink</ShipHeatsinkLarge.label>
  <ShipHeatsinkLarge.description>A liquid-cooled heatsink for storing excess heat from weapons fire. Slowly bleeds heat into the surrounding room; will not function in vacuum.</ShipHeatsinkLarge.description>
  <ShipCombatShieldGenerator.label>shield generator</ShipCombatShieldGenerator.label>
  <ShipCombatShieldGenerator.description>A shielding device which projects a momentum repulsor field. Shots can go out, but not in.\n\nGenerates heat when it blocks attacks. If no heatsink capacity is available, the shield will be damaged and require repairs.\n\nShip radiators cannot disperse heat while shields are up. Captains are advised to drop shields once heatsinks are close to capacity, or risk their ships turning into ovens.</ShipCombatShieldGenerator.description>
  <ShipTurret_Laser.label>laser turret</ShipTurret_Laser.label>
  <ShipTurret_Laser.description>A starship turret that fires a powerful laser. While it can inflict devastating damage, it is only usable at short range. Can be set to intercept torpedoes rather than firing on the enemy ship.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Laser.description>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop.label>laser</ShipTurret_LaserTop.label>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop.description>Laser cannon. Short-ranged but devastating.</ShipTurret_LaserTop.description>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop.verbs.0.label>shoot laser</ShipTurret_LaserTop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Laser.label>laser beam</Bullet_Fake_Laser.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretLaser.label>laser beam</Proj_ShipTurretLaser.label>
  <ShipTurret_Plasma.label>plasma turret</ShipTurret_Plasma.label>
  <ShipTurret_Plasma.description>A starship turret that fires a burst of superheated plasma. This balanced weapon can be used at up to medium range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Plasma.description>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.label>plasma</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.label>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.description>Plasma cannon. Medium-range and balanced.</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.description>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.verbs.0.label>fire plasma</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Plasma.label>plasma toroid</Bullet_Fake_Plasma.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretPlasma.label>plasma toroid</Proj_ShipTurretPlasma.label>
  <ShipTurret_Kinetic.label>railgun turret</ShipTurret_Kinetic.label>
  <ShipTurret_Kinetic.description>A starship turret that accelerates metal slugs to relativistic speeds. Its tracking system excels at striking distant targets, but becomes wildly inaccurate at close range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Kinetic.description>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop.label>railgun</ShipTurret_KineticTop.label>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop.description>Railgun. Best used at long range.</ShipTurret_KineticTop.description>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop.verbs.0.label>shoot slug</ShipTurret_KineticTop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Kinetic.label>railgun slug</Bullet_Fake_Kinetic.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretKinetic.label>railgun slug</Proj_ShipTurretKinetic.label>
  <ShipTorpedoOne.label>torpedo tube</ShipTorpedoOne.label>
  <ShipTorpedoOne.description>A single tube that launches all kinds of torpedoes. Highly accurate and devastating against shields, but slow to reach targets and vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</ShipTorpedoOne.description>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo_One.label>torpedo tube</Artillery_ShipTorpedo_One.label>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo_One.description>Torpedo launcher. Accurate and devastating against shields, but vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</Artillery_ShipTorpedo_One.description>
  <ShipTorpedoTwo.label>torpedo tubes (2)</ShipTorpedoTwo.label>
  <ShipTorpedoTwo.description>A pair of tubes that launch all kinds of torpedoes. Highly accurate and devastating against shields, but slow to reach targets and vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</ShipTorpedoTwo.description>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo_Two.label>torpedo tubes (2)</Artillery_ShipTorpedo_Two.label>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo_Two.description>Torpedo launcher. Accurate and devastating against shields, but vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</Artillery_ShipTorpedo_Two.description>
  <ShipTorpedoSix.label>torpedo tubes (6)</ShipTorpedoSix.label>
  <ShipTorpedoSix.description>A series of tubes that launch all kinds of torpedoes. Highly accurate and devastating against shields, but slow to reach targets and vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</ShipTorpedoSix.description>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo.label>torpedo tubes (6)</Artillery_ShipTorpedo.label>
  <Artillery_ShipTorpedo.description>Torpedo launcher. Accurate and devastating against shields, but vulnerable to point-defense lasers.</Artillery_ShipTorpedo.description>
  <ShipTurret_Laser_Large.label>large laser turret</ShipTurret_Laser_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_Laser_Large.description>A cruiser-sized turret that fires a powerful laser. While it can inflict devastating damage, it is only usable at short range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Laser_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.label>laser</ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.description>Laser cannon. Short-ranged but devastating.</ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.verbs.0.label>shoot laser</ShipTurret_LaserTop_Large.verbs.0.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretLaserTwo.label>laser beam</Proj_ShipTurretLaserTwo.label>
  <ShipTurret_Plasma_Large.label>large plasma turret</ShipTurret_Plasma_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_Plasma_Large.description>A cruiser-sized turret that fires a burst of superheated plasma. This balanced weapon can be used at up to medium range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Plasma_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.label>plasma</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.description>Plasma cannon. Medium-range and balanced.</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.verbs.0.label>fire plasma</ShipTurret_PlasmaTop_Large.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Plasma_Large.label>plasma toroid</Bullet_Fake_Plasma_Large.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretPlasma_Large.label>plasma toroid</Proj_ShipTurretPlasma_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_Kinetic_Large.label>large railgun turret</ShipTurret_Kinetic_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_Kinetic_Large.description>A cruiser-sized turret that accelerates metal slugs to relativistic speeds. Its tracking system excels at striking distant targets, but becomes wildly inaccurate at close range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_Kinetic_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.label>railgun</ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.label>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.description>Railgun. Best used at long range.</ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.description>
  <ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.verbs.0.label>shoot slug</ShipTurret_KineticTop_Large.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Kinetic_Large.label>railgun slug</Bullet_Fake_Kinetic_Large.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretKinetic_Large.label>railgun slug</Proj_ShipTurretKinetic_Large.label>
  <ShipSpinalEmitter.label>spinal capacitor</ShipSpinalEmitter.label>
  <ShipSpinalEmitter.description>The first segment of a spinal-mount weapon. Connects to one or more amplifiers, then a barrel.</ShipSpinalEmitter.description>
  <ShipSpinalAmplifier.label>spinal amplifier</ShipSpinalAmplifier.label>
  <ShipSpinalAmplifier.description>A middle segment of a spinal-mount weapon. Attach one or more of these to an emitter, then add a barrel to complete the gun.\n\nIncreases base damage by 25%, but also increases power consumption and heat generated by the same percentage.</ShipSpinalAmplifier.description>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelLaser.label>spinal barrel: laser</ShipSpinalBarrelLaser.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelLaser.description>The final segment of a spinal-mount cannon. Should be placed outside the ship, unless you want a new hole in your hull.</ShipSpinalBarrelLaser.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.label>spinal-mount cannon</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.label>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.description>Capital ship weaponry.</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.verbs.0.label>shoot</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopLaser.verbs.0.label>
  <Proj_ShipSpinalBeamLaser.label>death ray</Proj_ShipSpinalBeamLaser.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelPlasma.label>spinal barrel: plasma</ShipSpinalBarrelPlasma.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelPlasma.description>The final segment of a spinal-mount cannon. Should be placed outside the ship, unless you want a new hole in your hull.</ShipSpinalBarrelPlasma.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.label>spinal-mount cannon</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.label>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.description>Capital ship weaponry.</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.verbs.0.label>shoot</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopPlasma.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_Plasma_XL.label>plasma toroid</Bullet_Fake_Plasma_XL.label>
  <Proj_ShipSpinalBeamPlasma.label>death ray</Proj_ShipSpinalBeamPlasma.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelKinetic.label>spinal barrel: railgun</ShipSpinalBarrelKinetic.label>
  <ShipSpinalBarrelKinetic.description>The final segment of a spinal-mount cannon. Should be placed outside the ship, unless you want a new hole in your hull.</ShipSpinalBarrelKinetic.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.label>spinal-mount cannon</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.label>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.description>Capital ship weaponry.</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.description>
  <ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.verbs.0.label>shoot</ShipTurret_SpinalMountTopKinetic.verbs.0.label>
  <HullFoamDistributor.label>hullfoam distributor</HullFoamDistributor.label>
  <HullFoamDistributor.description>A pumping station for distributing hullfoam throughout a ship. When a portion of the ship's hull is destroyed in combat, this system will automatically patch the hole with hullfoam.</HullFoamDistributor.description>
  <ShipPurgePort.label>emergency purge port</ShipPurgePort.label>
  <ShipPurgePort.description>A system for channeling heat into low-melting-point metals like silver. Ejecting molten silver into space is a costly way to quickly purge stored heat. Shields will be dropped during a purge.</ShipPurgePort.description>
  <ShipPurgePortLarge.label>large emergency purge port</ShipPurgePortLarge.label>
  <ShipPurgePortLarge.description>A system for rapidly channeling heat into low-melting-point metals like silver. Ejecting molten silver into space is a costly way to quickly purge stored heat. Shields will be dropped during a purge.</ShipPurgePortLarge.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACI.label>cannon turret</ShipTurret_ACI.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACI.description>A starship turret that rapidly accelerates uranium slugs. Requires ammunition, but costs zero energy and very little heat to fire. Only useful at close range. Can be set to intercept torpedoes rather than firing at the enemy ship.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_ACI.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.fuelLabel>Shots until rearm</ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.fuelLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.fuelGizmoLabel>Uranium slugs</ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.outOfFuelMessage>Cannot shoot: No slugs</ShipTurret_ACI.comps.2.outOfFuelMessage>
  <ShipTurret_ACITop.label>autocannon</ShipTurret_ACITop.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACITop.description>Ship cannon. Best used at short range.</ShipTurret_ACITop.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACITop.verbs.0.label>shoot slug</ShipTurret_ACITop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_ACI.label>Autocannon slug</Bullet_Fake_ACI.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretACI.label>Autocannon Slug</Proj_ShipTurretACI.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACII.label>large cannon turret</ShipTurret_ACII.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACII.description>A cruiser-class turret that rapidly accelerates uranium slugs. Requires ammunition, but costs zero energy and very little heat to fire. Only useful at close range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_ACII.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.fuelLabel>Shots until rearm</ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.fuelLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.fuelGizmoLabel>Uranium slugs</ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.outOfFuelMessage>Cannot shoot: No slugs</ShipTurret_ACII.comps.1.outOfFuelMessage>
  <ShipTurret_ACIITop.label>autocannon</ShipTurret_ACIITop.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACIITop.description>Autocannon. Best used at short range.</ShipTurret_ACIITop.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACIITop.verbs.0.label>shoot slug</ShipTurret_ACIITop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_ACII.label>Autocannon slug</Bullet_Fake_ACII.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretACII.label>Autocannon Slug</Proj_ShipTurretACII.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACIII.label>artillery turret</ShipTurret_ACIII.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACIII.description>A capital-class turret that rapidly accelerates a stream of massive uranium slugs. Requires ammunition, but costs zero energy and very little heat to fire. Only useful at close range.\n\nWill vent heat to the surrounding room if no heatsink capacity is available.</ShipTurret_ACIII.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.fuelLabel>Shots until rearm</ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.fuelLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.fuelGizmoLabel>Uranium slugs</ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.fuelGizmoLabel>
  <ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.outOfFuelMessage>Cannot shoot: No slugs</ShipTurret_ACIII.comps.1.outOfFuelMessage>
  <ShipTurret_ACIIITop.label>autocannon</ShipTurret_ACIIITop.label>
  <ShipTurret_ACIIITop.description>Autocannon. Best used at short range.</ShipTurret_ACIIITop.description>
  <ShipTurret_ACIIITop.verbs.0.label>shoot slug</ShipTurret_ACIIITop.verbs.0.label>
  <Bullet_Fake_ACIII.label>Autocannon slug</Bullet_Fake_ACIII.label>
  <Proj_ShipTurretACIII.label>Autocannon Slug</Proj_ShipTurretACIII.label>
  <PersonalShuttle.label>personal shuttle</PersonalShuttle.label>
  <PersonalShuttle.description>A small, reusable shuttlecraft. Can be used for transport, surprise attacks, or reinforcing battles.</PersonalShuttle.description>
  <CargoShuttle.label>cargo shuttle</CargoShuttle.label>
  <CargoShuttle.description>A reusable shuttlecraft powered by uranium fuel pods. Can carry a significant amount of cargo.</CargoShuttle.description>
  <HeavyShuttle.label>heavy cargo shuttle</HeavyShuttle.label>
  <HeavyShuttle.description>A reusable shuttlecraft powered by uranium fuel pods. Can carry tonnes of cargo.</HeavyShuttle.description>
  <ArcholifePod.label>archolife pod</ArcholifePod.label>
  <ArcholifePod.description>A slurry of synthetic cells wrapped in a single-use incubator. Can be programmed (select a pawn and right-click) to "hatch" a radically redesigned version of an ordinary creature. Spawning an archothrumbo requires a stack of 10.</ArcholifePod.description>
  <ArchotechRepairGel.label>mechanite repair gel</ArchotechRepairGel.label>
  <ArchotechRepairGel.description>A one-use super-dose of mechanites tuned to repair damaged items. Applied to an object such as a weapon or piece of apparel, it restores the object to full condition.</ArchotechRepairGel.description>
  <ArchotechRepairGel.comps.0.useLabel>Use repair gel</ArchotechRepairGel.comps.0.useLabel>
  <ArchotechMechaniteCore.label>mechanite disassembler core</ArchotechMechaniteCore.label>
  <ArchotechMechaniteCore.description>A self-contained mechanite factory designed to produce disassembler mechanites.</ArchotechMechaniteCore.description>
  <ArchotechPsychicCore.label>psychic flayer core</ArchotechPsychicCore.label>
  <ArchotechPsychicCore.description>A large psychic effector capable of disrupting the minds of distant foes. Can be used to construct a spinal weapon.</ArchotechPsychicCore.description>
  <ArchotechExoticParticles.label>exotic particles</ArchotechExoticParticles.label>
  <ArchotechExoticParticles.description>Particles whose behavior defies conventionally-understood physics, safely contained. Can be used to construct a wide range of devices.</ArchotechExoticParticles.description>
  <ShipTorpedo_HighExplosive.label>high-explosive torpedo</ShipTorpedo_HighExplosive.label>
  <ShipTorpedo_HighExplosive.description>A torpedo tipped with high explosives. Can be fired from torpedo tubes. Explodes when damaged.</ShipTorpedo_HighExplosive.description>
  <Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_HighExplosive.label>high-explosive torpedo</Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_HighExplosive.label>
  <Bullet_Torpedo_HighExplosive.label>high-explosive torpedo</Bullet_Torpedo_HighExplosive.label>
  <ShipTorpedo_EMP.label>EMP torpedo</ShipTorpedo_EMP.label>
  <ShipTorpedo_EMP.description>A torpedo tipped with an EMP generator. Can be fired from torpedo tubes. Explodes when damaged.</ShipTorpedo_EMP.description>
  <Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_EMP.label>EMP torpedo</Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_EMP.label>
  <Bullet_Torpedo_EMP.label>EMP torpedo</Bullet_Torpedo_EMP.label>
  <ShipTorpedo_Antimatter.label>antigrain torpedo</ShipTorpedo_Antimatter.label>
  <ShipTorpedo_Antimatter.description>A torpedo tipped with an antigrain warhead. Can be fired from torpedo tubes. Explodes when damaged.</ShipTorpedo_Antimatter.description>
  <Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_Antimatter.label>antigrain torpedo</Bullet_Fake_Torpedo_Antimatter.label>
  <Bullet_Torpedo_Antimatter.label>antigrain torpedo</Bullet_Torpedo_Antimatter.label>
  <ShuttleFuelPods.label>uranium fuel pod</ShuttleFuelPods.label>
  <ShuttleFuelPods.description>A small canister of enriched uranium.</ShuttleFuelPods.description>
  <WeatherCancelDevice.label>weather normalization device</WeatherCancelDevice.label>
  <WeatherCancelDevice.description>A control unit for an ancient network of weather-control satellites, with a single-use authorization key. This device is pre-programmed to trigger a reset protocol across nearby regions - when used, it ends all ongoing weather effects. The satellites are even capable of rapidly dispersing toxic fallout, ending heat waves and cold snaps, and providing local relief from volcanic winters.</WeatherCancelDevice.description>
  <WeatherCancelDevice.comps.0.useLabel>Activate</WeatherCancelDevice.comps.0.useLabel>
  <SoSEntanglementManifold.label>entanglement manifold</SoSEntanglementManifold.label>
  <SoSEntanglementManifold.description>A small ultratech device which entangles itself with matter inside distant stars, essential to the function of the Johnson-Tanaka drive. It cannot be duplicated without glitterworld infrastructure.</SoSEntanglementManifold.description>
  <HullFoam.label>hullfoam canister</HullFoam.label>
  <HullFoam.description>A canister of compressed ceramo-metallic foam. When sprayed, it rapidly hardens into an airtight and relatively durable barrier. Its primary use involves patching destroyed sections of starship hull until proper repairs can be made.</HullFoam.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitBody.label>EVA suit</Apparel_SpaceSuitBody.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitBody.description>A suit designed to keep the occupant alive in outer space. Includes small thrusters for movement.</Apparel_SpaceSuitBody.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmet.label>EVA helmet</Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmet.description>A helmet designed to keep the occupant alive in outer space.</Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitBodyHeavy.label>heavy EVA suit</Apparel_SpaceSuitBodyHeavy.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitBodyHeavy.description>A pressure-sealed suit of powered armor, designed to keep the occupant alive in outer space. Includes small thrusters for movement.</Apparel_SpaceSuitBodyHeavy.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmetHeavy.label>Heavy EVA helmet</Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmetHeavy.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmetHeavy.description>A pressure-sealed power armor helmet, designed to keep the occupant alive in outer space.</Apparel_SpaceSuitHelmetHeavy.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBelt.label>survival belt</Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBelt.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBelt.description>An emergency survival belt used by starship crews. It remains dormant so long as air pressure is maintained. Once exposed to vacuum, the belt releases a semi-liquid membrane over the user's body and begins generating breathable air. For the next three hours, the user can survive exposure to vacuum, although their movements are slowed. The belt is single-use.</Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBelt.description>
  <Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBeltDummy.label>survival belt (activated)</Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBeltDummy.label>
  <Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBeltDummy.description>An emergency survival belt used by starship crews. It has released a semi-liquid membrane over the user's body and is actively generating breathable air. For the next three hours, the user can survive exposure to vacuum, although their movements are slowed. The belt is single-use.</Apparel_SpaceSurvivalBeltDummy.description>
  <Filth_SpaceBones.label>bones</Filth_SpaceBones.label>
  <Filth_SpaceReactorAsh.label>radioactive ash</Filth_SpaceReactorAsh.label>
  <ShuttleIncomingPersonal.label>shuttle (incoming)</ShuttleIncomingPersonal.label>
  <ShuttleIncomingCargo.label>shuttle (incoming)</ShuttleIncomingCargo.label>
  <ShuttleIncomingHeavy.label>shuttle (incoming)</ShuttleIncomingHeavy.label>
  <PersonalShuttleSkyfaller.label>shuttle (leaving)</PersonalShuttleSkyfaller.label>
  <CargoShuttleSkyfaller.label>shuttle (leaving)</CargoShuttleSkyfaller.label>
  <HeavyCargoShuttleSkyfaller.label>shuttle (leaving)</HeavyCargoShuttleSkyfaller.label>
  <ActiveShuttle.label>shuttle</ActiveShuttle.label>
  <Plant_Vanoroot.label>vanoroot</Plant_Vanoroot.label>
  <Plant_Vanoroot.description>A starchy tuber with a sweet fluid-filled center, vanoroot is a fast-growing and nutritious food crop. Vanometric processes in its cells provide all the energy it needs to grow, so it requires no sunlight.</Plant_Vanoroot.description>
  <RawVanoroot.label>vanoroot</RawVanoroot.label>
  <RawVanoroot.description>Raw vanoroot.</RawVanoroot.description>
  <Plant_Hypnobloom.label>hypnobloom</Plant_Hypnobloom.label>
  <Plant_Hypnobloom.description>An iridescent rose-like flower, the hypnobloom emits calming pheromones and a subtle psychic signal that enhances perceptions of beauty.</Plant_Hypnobloom.description>
  <Plant_Slaughtermelon.label>slaughtermelon</Plant_Slaughtermelon.label>
  <Plant_Slaughtermelon.description>A spiky, hard-shelled melon whose fruit is soaked in chemfuel. Highly explosive. Inedible, but can be harvested for chemfuel or used (along with IED triggers) as part of perimeter defenses.</Plant_Slaughtermelon.description>
  <Plant_Pharmatree.label>pharmatree</Plant_Pharmatree.label>
  <Plant_Pharmatree.description>A slow-growing bush whose sap can be rendered into pure liquid neutroamine. Its leaves also make the galaxy's least enjoyable tea.</Plant_Pharmatree.description>
  <Plant_Fireflower.label>fireflower</Plant_Fireflower.label>
  <Plant_Fireflower.description>A beautiful flower which vanometrically produces heat and light. Increases a room's temperature up to 21C. Produces a small explosion if set aflame.</Plant_Fireflower.description>
  <Plant_Meatbush.label>meatbush</Plant_Meatbush.label>
  <Plant_Meatbush.description>A slimy plant whose leaves are indistinguishable, in both taste and nutrition, from high-quality beef. The strange cooing noises it makes while being harvested have been described as "disturbing" and "proof that archotechs have a sense of humor."</Plant_Meatbush.description>
  <Plant_AmbrosiaArchotech.label>ambrosia bush</Plant_AmbrosiaArchotech.label>
  <Plant_AmbrosiaArchotech.description>A bush which yields the ambrosia fruit. Ambrosia fruit is delicious and produces a drug-like mood boost. Ambrosia cannot be farmed without the help of an archotech spore.\n\nIts rarity, beauty, and desirability are why ambrosia was named after the food of the ancient Greek gods.</Plant_AmbrosiaArchotech.description>
</LanguageData>