<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FSFAdvBionicEar.label>advanced bionic ear</FSFAdvBionicEar.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicEar.description>An advanced artificial ear. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicEar.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicEye.label>advanced bionic eye</FSFAdvBionicEye.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicEye.description>An advanced artifical eye. It perceives every type of electromagnetic radiation, including radio waves, infrared, light, x-rays, and gamma rays. Its visual acuity is precise enough to read handwriting from twenty meters away. It can emit various wavelengths of radiation like a flashlight, and has an internal subpersona AI which helps highlight useful visual information. Externally, it looks like a natural human eye, except it can change color at will.</FSFAdvBionicEye.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicJaw.label>advanced bionic jaw</FSFAdvBionicJaw.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicJaw.description>An advanced artificial jaw. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicJaw.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicArm.label>advanced bionic arm</FSFAdvBionicArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicArm.description>An advanced artifical arm. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicArm.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicSpine.label>advanced bionic spine</FSFAdvBionicSpine.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicSpine.description>An advanced artificial spine. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicSpine.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicHeart.label>advanced bionic heart</FSFAdvBionicHeart.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicHeart.description>An advanced artificial heart. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicHeart.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicLung.label>advanced bionic lung</FSFAdvBionicLung.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicLung.description>An advanced artificial lung. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicLung.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicKidney.label>advanced bionic kidney</FSFAdvBionicKidney.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicKidney.description>An advanced artificial kidney. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicKidney.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicLiver.label>advanced bionic liver</FSFAdvBionicLiver.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicLiver.description>An advanced artificial liver. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicLiver.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicStomach.label>advanced bionic stomach</FSFAdvBionicStomach.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicStomach.description>An advanced artificial stomach. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicStomach.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicLeg.label>advanced bionic leg</FSFAdvBionicLeg.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicLeg.description>An artifical leg. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but a pair of these can move the user as fast as a decent car, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time.</FSFAdvBionicLeg.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicBrain.label>positronic brain</FSFAdvBionicBrain.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicBrain.description>An extremely sophisticated computation device designed to house a human or artificial intelligence.  It’s primarily used to transfer a person’s consciousness to fight against the slow endless march of time and its effects on organic body parts.</FSFAdvBionicBrain.description>
  <FSFImplantBrainMeleeCombat.label>CQC assistant</FSFImplantBrainMeleeCombat.label>
  <FSFImplantBrainMeleeCombat.description>A low-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with processing audible and visual cues in close quarters combat to aid the user in dodging and striking an opponent.</FSFImplantBrainMeleeCombat.description>
  <FSFImplantBrainRangedCombat.label>targeting assistant</FSFImplantBrainRangedCombat.label>
  <FSFImplantBrainRangedCombat.description>A low-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with processing audible and visual information to aid the user in aiming faster and shooting more accurately.</FSFImplantBrainRangedCombat.description>
  <FSFImplantBrainAnimals.label>ethology assistant</FSFImplantBrainAnimals.label>
  <FSFImplantBrainAnimals.description>A low-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with identifying important audible and visual cues emitted by animals to aid the user in animal handling.</FSFImplantBrainAnimals.description>
  <FSFImplantBrainMedical.label>medical assistant</FSFImplantBrainMedical.label>
  <FSFImplantBrainMedical.description>A low-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. With an immense medical database and a variety of analytical tools it helps the user diagnose ailments and perform surgery.</FSFImplantBrainMedical.description>
  <FSFImplantBrainPlants.label>agricultural assistant</FSFImplantBrainPlants.label>
  <FSFImplantBrainPlants.description>A non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. With an immense agricultural database and a variety of analytical tools it helps the user better care for plants and forage for food.</FSFImplantBrainPlants.description>
  <FSFImplantTorsoWorker.label>worker frame</FSFImplantTorsoWorker.label>
  <FSFImplantTorsoWorker.description>A durable heavy plasteel frame designed to replace the skeleton and some of the surrounding tissue.  The modifications provide the user with greater mobility and manipulation at the expense of an increase in weight.  Not compatible with other body frames.</FSFImplantTorsoWorker.description>
  <FSFImplantTorsoSpeed.label>sprinter frame</FSFImplantTorsoSpeed.label>
  <FSFImplantTorsoSpeed.description>A durable lightweight plasteel frame designed to replace the skeleton and some of the surrounding tissue.  The modifications provide the user with greater speed and agility while also decreasing their weight.  Not compatible with other body frames.</FSFImplantTorsoSpeed.description>
  <FSFImplantTorsoPsychic.label>psychic frame</FSFImplantTorsoPsychic.label>
  <FSFImplantTorsoPsychic.description>A durable plasteel frame designed to replace the skeleton and some of the surrounding tissue.  The frame is embedded with special psychic focusing materials which enhances the user’s psychic sensitivity and helps dissipate psychic entropy.  Not compatible with other body frames.</FSFImplantTorsoPsychic.description>
  <FSFImplantTorsoClimateControl.label>climate control</FSFImplantTorsoClimateControl.label>
  <FSFImplantTorsoClimateControl.description>A small internal module designed to help regulate the bodies temperature allowing a person to endure harsher cold or heat without ill effects.</FSFImplantTorsoClimateControl.description>
  <FSFImplantTorsoRespirator.label>internal respirator</FSFImplantTorsoRespirator.label>
  <FSFImplantTorsoRespirator.description>A small internal module that functions much like a gas mask.  It filters out harmful elements from the air before passing it on to the lungs.</FSFImplantTorsoRespirator.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicPowerArm.label>advanced bionic power arm</FSFAdvBionicPowerArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicPowerArm.description>An advanced artificial arm fitted with retractable wrist blades. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</FSFAdvBionicPowerArm.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicTaserArm.label>advanced bionic shocker arm</FSFAdvBionicTaserArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicTaserArm.description>An advanced artificial arm capable of delivering a less than lethal high powered electrical charge that can instantly down enemies. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.
		
		The electrical discharge system is capable of instantly downing humans in a single hit and capable of downing somewhat larger creatures with a second. While the effects are generally instantaneous the device requires several seconds to discharge its energy and reset which renders the user unable to move temporarily.
		
		Note: Rimworld has a built in instant death chance when enemies are downed that scales with population. To bypass this mechanic and use this bionic without randomly killing enemies you'll need a mod to tweak or remove the instant down chance.</FSFAdvBionicTaserArm.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicDrillArm.label>advanced bionic drill arm</FSFAdvBionicDrillArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicDrillArm.description>An advanced artificial arm with a built-in snake drill, which allows the miner to rapidly find and exploit weak lines in the rock. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</FSFAdvBionicDrillArm.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicFieldArm.label>advanced bionic field arm</FSFAdvBionicFieldArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicFieldArm.description>An advanced artificial arm with multiple built-in telescopic finger-like protrusions that can simultaneously harvest from several points on the same plant, or precisely sow several holes at once. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</FSFAdvBionicFieldArm.description>
  <FSFAdvBionicConstructionArm.label>advanced bionic construction arm</FSFAdvBionicConstructionArm.label>
  <FSFAdvBionicConstructionArm.description>An advanced artificial arm with multiple built-in tools used in general construction work. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</FSFAdvBionicConstructionArm.description>
  <FSFArchotechEar.label>archotech ear</FSFArchotechEar.label>
  <FSFArchotechEar.description>An advanced artificial ear built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechEar.description>
  <FSFArchotechJaw.label>archotech jaw</FSFArchotechJaw.label>
  <FSFArchotechJaw.description>An advanced artificial jaw built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechJaw.description>
  <FSFArchotechSpine.label>archotech spine</FSFArchotechSpine.label>
  <FSFArchotechSpine.description>An advanced artificial spine built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechSpine.description>
  <FSFArchotechHeart.label>archotech heart</FSFArchotechHeart.label>
  <FSFArchotechHeart.description>An advanced artificial heart built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechHeart.description>
  <FSFArchotechLung.label>archotech lung</FSFArchotechLung.label>
  <FSFArchotechLung.description>An advanced artificial lung built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechLung.description>
  <FSFArchotechKidney.label>archotech kidney</FSFArchotechKidney.label>
  <FSFArchotechKidney.description>An advanced artificial kidney built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechKidney.description>
  <FSFArchotechLiver.label>archotech liver</FSFArchotechLiver.label>
  <FSFArchotechLiver.description>An advanced artificial liver built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechLiver.description>
  <FSFArchotechStomach.label>archotech stomach</FSFArchotechStomach.label>
  <FSFArchotechStomach.description>An advanced artificial stomach built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechStomach.description>
  <FSFArchotechPowerArm.label>Archotech Power Arm</FSFArchotechPowerArm.label>
  <FSFArchotechPowerArm.description>An artifical arm built by an archotech fitted with retractable wrist blades. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechPowerArm.description>
  <FSFArchotechPowerCore.label>archotech power core</FSFArchotechPowerCore.label>
  <FSFArchotechPowerCore.description>An advanced artificial stomach built by an archotech. It uses some unknown system to replaces the body’s need for food and water. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechPowerCore.description>
  <FSFArchotechSkinI.label>synthetic skin gland</FSFArchotechSkinI.label>
  <FSFArchotechSkinI.description>An advanced artificial skin gland built by an archotech. The gland releases chemicals and nanomachines that remodels the user’s skin, making it flawless and tougher than plasteel. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</FSFArchotechSkinI.description>
  <GastroAnalyzer.label>gastro-analyzer</GastroAnalyzer.label>
  <GastroAnalyzer.description>This bionic nose implant enhances the sense of smell, with a focus towards food-related smells. A multi-layered ultrafine absorption mesh detects compounds in the air. A microprocessor formats the readings into an olfactory nerve signal to send to the brain through a nerve-link interface. The result is that the user can smell foods with a depth, richness, and precision unknown among unenhanced humans, allowing them to cook more effectively. The whole unit is small enough to be installed in the nose without affecting the user's appearance.</GastroAnalyzer.description>
  <Immunoenhancer.label>immunoenhancer</Immunoenhancer.label>
  <Immunoenhancer.description>An analysis computer inspects the bloodstream, classifies pathogens, and rapidly prompts the body’s natural immune system to respond to them faster than it could alone. This speeds immunity gain significantly.</Immunoenhancer.description>
  <ArchotechEye.label>archotech eye</ArchotechEye.label>
  <ArchotechEye.description>An artifical eye built by an archotech. It perceives every type of electromagnetic radiation, including radio waves, infrared, light, x-rays, and gamma rays. Its visual acuity is precise enough to read handwriting from twenty meters away. It can emit various wavelengths of radiation like a flashlight, and has an internal subpersona AI which helps highlight useful visual information. Externally, it looks like a natural human eye, except it can change color at will. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechEye.description>
  <ArchotechArm.label>archotech arm</ArchotechArm.label>
  <ArchotechArm.description>An artifical arm built by an archotech. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechArm.description>
  <ArchotechLeg.label>archotech leg</ArchotechLeg.label>
  <ArchotechLeg.description>An artifical leg built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but a pair of these can move the user as fast as a decent car, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLeg.description>
  <FSFArtificialNose.label>artificial nose</FSFArtificialNose.label>
  <FSFArtificialNose.description>An artificial nose that works as a suitable replacement for an organic one.</FSFArtificialNose.description>
  <FSFBionicJaw.label>bionic jaw</FSFBionicJaw.label>
  <FSFBionicJaw.description>An advanced artificial jaw. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while a lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological jaw in almost every way.</FSFBionicJaw.description>
  <FSFBionicPowerArm.label>bionic power arm</FSFBionicPowerArm.label>
  <FSFBionicPowerArm.description>An advanced artificial arm fitted with retractable power claw blades. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. While not as effective for non-combat tasks as a bionic arm the retractable blades make it a powerful weapon.</FSFBionicPowerArm.description>
  <FSFBionicLung.label>bionic lung</FSFBionicLung.label>
  <FSFBionicLung.description>An advanced artificial lung. It has synthetic muscle fibers and a lattice-dust healing system. It is better than a biological lung in almost every way.</FSFBionicLung.description>
  <FSFBionicKidney.label>bionic kidney</FSFBionicKidney.label>
  <FSFBionicKidney.description>An advanced artificial kidney. It has synthetic muscle fibers and a lattice-dust healing system. It is better than a biological kidney in almost every way.</FSFBionicKidney.description>
  <FSFBionicLiver.label>bionic liver</FSFBionicLiver.label>
  <FSFBionicLiver.description>An advanced artificial liver. It has synthetic muscle fibers and a lattice-dust healing system. It is better than a biological liver in almost every way.</FSFBionicLiver.description>
  <FSFProstheticEye.label>prosthetic eye</FSFProstheticEye.label>
  <FSFProstheticEye.description>A eye prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFProstheticEye.description>
  <FSFProstheticHand.label>prosthetic hand</FSFProstheticHand.label>
  <FSFProstheticHand.description>A hand prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real hand.</FSFProstheticHand.description>
  <FSFProstheticFoot.label>prosthetic foot</FSFProstheticFoot.label>
  <FSFProstheticFoot.description>A foot prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real foot.</FSFProstheticFoot.description>
  <FSFProstheticSpine.label>prosthetic spine</FSFProstheticSpine.label>
  <FSFProstheticSpine.description>A spine prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFProstheticSpine.description>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticLung.label>prosthetic lung</FSFSimpleProstheticLung.label>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticLung.description>A lung prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFSimpleProstheticLung.description>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticKidney.label>prosthetic kidney</FSFSimpleProstheticKidney.label>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticKidney.description>A kidney prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFSimpleProstheticKidney.description>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticLiver.label>prosthetic liver</FSFSimpleProstheticLiver.label>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticLiver.description>A liver prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFSimpleProstheticLiver.description>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticStomach.label>prosthetic stomach</FSFSimpleProstheticStomach.label>
  <FSFSimpleProstheticStomach.description>A stomach prosthesis. It's not as efficient as the real thing but it's better than the nothing.</FSFSimpleProstheticStomach.description>
</LanguageData>