<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PsychoidBrewing.label>psychoid brewing</PsychoidBrewing.label>
  <PsychoidBrewing.description>Prepare psychoid leaves into a mildly euphoria-inducing and addictive tea at the campfire or cooking stove.</PsychoidBrewing.description>
  <TreeSowing.label>tree sowing</TreeSowing.label>
  <TreeSowing.description>Sow the local biome's natural trees in your fields.</TreeSowing.description>
  <Brewing.label>beer brewing</Brewing.label>
  <Brewing.description>Build a brewery and fermenting vats to transform hops into tasty, tasty beer.</Brewing.description>
  <ComplexFurniture.label>complex furniture</ComplexFurniture.label>
  <ComplexFurniture.description>Build complex furniture like beds, end tables, dining chairs, armchairs, dressers, tool cabinets, billiard tables, and poker tables, vents, sarcophagi, and more.</ComplexFurniture.description>
  <PassiveCooler.label>passive cooler</PassiveCooler.label>
  <PassiveCooler.description>Make passive coolers, to cool indoor spaces without using electricity.</PassiveCooler.description>
  <Stonecutting.label>stonecutting</Stonecutting.label>
  <Stonecutting.description>Cut rock chunks into stone blocks for use in construction. Build beautiful stone tile floors or ugly concrete walkways.</Stonecutting.description>
  <ComplexClothing.label>complex clothing</ComplexClothing.label>
  <ComplexClothing.description>Tailor complicated garments like pants, dusters, and cowboy hats.</ComplexClothing.description>
  <DrugProduction.label>drug production</DrugProduction.label>
  <DrugProduction.description>Build a drug lab for basic drug synthesis. Further research is required to make specific drugs.</DrugProduction.description>
  <Cocoa.label>cocoa</Cocoa.label>
  <Cocoa.description>Sow cocoa trees to create your own delicious chocolate. Eating chocolate fulfills the need for recreation, and it's valuable on the market too.</Cocoa.description>
  <Devilstrand.label>devilstrand</Devilstrand.label>
  <Devilstrand.description>Plant devilstrand, a slow-growing mushroom that yields an exceptionally tough, heat-resistant plant fiber.</Devilstrand.description>
  <CarpetMaking.label>carpet making</CarpetMaking.label>
  <CarpetMaking.description>Weave beautiful carpets from cloth.</CarpetMaking.description>
  <Pemmican.label>pemmican</Pemmican.label>
  <Pemmican.description>Make pemmican, a preserved mixture of meat and plant matter that doesn't go bad for a long time. Great for traveling.</Pemmican.description>
  <Smithing.label>smithing</Smithing.label>
  <Smithing.description>Build smithies for crafting metal weapons like knives, gladii, and maces. Work metal into clean, beautiful floor tiles.</Smithing.description>
  <RecurveBow.label>recurve bow</RecurveBow.label>
  <RecurveBow.description>Build the recurve bow, an effective and inexpensive ranged weapon.</RecurveBow.description>
  <PsychiteRefining.label>psychite refining</PsychiteRefining.label>
  <PsychiteRefining.description>Refine psychoid leaves into flake and yayo, different forms of the euphoric psychite drug.</PsychiteRefining.description>
  <WakeUpProduction.label>wake-up production</WakeUpProduction.label>
  <WakeUpProduction.description>Synthesize wake-up, a work performance-enhancing drug which replaces the need for sleep.</WakeUpProduction.description>
  <GoJuiceProduction.label>go-juice production</GoJuiceProduction.label>
  <GoJuiceProduction.description>Produce go-juice, a synthetic combat-performance-enhancing drug which improves shooting, melee, and movement ability, and dulls pain.</GoJuiceProduction.description>
  <PenoxycylineProduction.label>penoxycyline production</PenoxycylineProduction.label>
  <PenoxycylineProduction.description>Produce penoxycyline, a disease prevention drug which blocks plague, malaria, and more before they start.</PenoxycylineProduction.description>
  <LongBlades.label>long blades</LongBlades.label>
  <LongBlades.description>Craft longswords and spears.</LongBlades.description>
  <PlateArmor.label>plate armor</PlateArmor.label>
  <PlateArmor.description>Smith suits of plate armor from metal or wood. This heavy armor noticeably slows movement, but protects very effectively.</PlateArmor.description>
  <Greatbow.label>greatbow</Greatbow.label>
  <Greatbow.description>Craft greatbows for killing enemies at great range.</Greatbow.description>
  <Electricity.label>electricity</Electricity.label>
  <Electricity.description>Harness the power of electricity for a hundred different tasks.</Electricity.description>
  <Batteries.label>battery</Batteries.label>
  <Batteries.description>Build batteries for storing electricity.</Batteries.description>
  <BiofuelRefining.label>biofuel refining</BiofuelRefining.label>
  <BiofuelRefining.description>Build biofuel refineries to make chemfuel from biological matter like wood or foodstuffs.</BiofuelRefining.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.label>watermill generator</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>Build watermill generators on rivers to generate a steady supply of power.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  <NutrientPaste.label>nutrient paste</NutrientPaste.label>
  <NutrientPaste.description>Build nutrient paste dispensers which efficiently produce edible meals from raw nutritive feedstocks, while requiring no labor at all.</NutrientPaste.description>
  <SolarPanels.label>solar panel</SolarPanels.label>
  <SolarPanels.description>Build solar panels for electricity generation.</SolarPanels.description>
  <AirConditioning.label>air conditioning</AirConditioning.label>
  <AirConditioning.description>Build coolers to make people comfortable in hot weather, or to construct freezers for storing perishable goods.</AirConditioning.description>
  <Autodoors.label>autodoor</Autodoors.label>
  <Autodoors.description>Build autodoors which automatically open when someone approaches, without slowing anyone down.</Autodoors.description>
  <Hydroponics.label>hydroponics</Hydroponics.label>
  <Hydroponics.description>Build hydroponics basins to rapidly grow crops indoors regardless of the terrain or weather outside.</Hydroponics.description>
  <TubeTelevision.label>tube television</TubeTelevision.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>Produce tube televisions for recreational watching.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>packaged survival meal</PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>
  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>Produce packaged survival meals which never go bad. Great for traveling.</PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>
  <Firefoam.label>firefoam</Firefoam.label>
  <Firefoam.description>Construct firefoam poppers, automatic fire-safety devices which spread fire-retardant foam in response to encroaching flames.</Firefoam.description>
  <IEDs.label>IEDs</IEDs.label>
  <IEDs.description>Build improvised traps from any kind of mortar shell.</IEDs.description>
  <GeothermalPower.label>geothermal power</GeothermalPower.label>
  <GeothermalPower.description>Build geothermal power plants on top of steam geysers, for uninterrupted power.</GeothermalPower.description>
  <SterileMaterials.label>sterile materials</SterileMaterials.label>
  <SterileMaterials.description>Construct sterile tiles to make cleanrooms for safer and more effective medical treatment, research, and cooking.</SterileMaterials.description>
  <ColoredLights.label>colored lights</ColoredLights.label>
  <ColoredLights.description>Construct colored lights for decorative purposes. Cosmetic only.</ColoredLights.description>
  <Machining.label>machining</Machining.label>
  <Machining.description>Build machining tables to craft guns, grenades, flak armor, and to shred dead mechanoids for resources.</Machining.description>
  <SmokepopBelt.label>smokepop packs</SmokepopBelt.label>
  <SmokepopBelt.description>Build smokepop packs which allow the wearer to deploy a defensive smokescreen.</SmokepopBelt.description>
  <Prosthetics.label>prosthetics</Prosthetics.label>
  <Prosthetics.description>Build inexpensive prosthetic body parts to replace lost limbs. Requires a skilled doctor to attach.</Prosthetics.description>
  <Gunsmithing.label>gunsmithing</Gunsmithing.label>
  <Gunsmithing.description>Craft simple manually-operated guns like revolvers, pump shotguns, bolt-action rifles, and incendiary launchers.</Gunsmithing.description>
  <FlakArmor.label>flak armor</FlakArmor.label>
  <FlakArmor.description>Craft clothing with metal armor sewn in to resist bullets and explosions. This weighty armor slows movement slightly.</FlakArmor.description>
  <Mortars.label>mortars</Mortars.label>
  <Mortars.description>Build mortars which can lob shells long distances - even over walls.</Mortars.description>
  <BlowbackOperation.label>blowback operation</BlowbackOperation.label>
  <BlowbackOperation.description>Craft low-power blowback-operated guns like autopistols and machine pistols.</BlowbackOperation.description>
  <GasOperation.label>gas operation</GasOperation.label>
  <GasOperation.description>Craft high-power guns like chain shotguns, LMGs, and heavy SMGs.</GasOperation.description>
  <GunTurrets.label>gun turrets</GunTurrets.label>
  <GunTurrets.description>Produce simple automated gun turrets.</GunTurrets.description>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.label>microelectronics</MicroelectronicsBasics.label>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>Work with complex microelectronics. This unlocks the hi-tech research bench and comms console.</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.label>flatscreen television</FlatscreenTelevision.label>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Produce high-resolution flatscreen televisions for greater enjoyment.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <MoisturePump.label>moisture pump</MoisturePump.label>
  <MoisturePump.description>Construct moisture pumps, which very slowly normalize the moisture in the ground around them. They can turn wet ground dry and convert soft sand into normal sand.</MoisturePump.description>
  <HospitalBed.label>hospital bed</HospitalBed.label>
  <HospitalBed.description>Construct hospital beds which improve medical outcomes.</HospitalBed.description>
  <DeepDrilling.label>deep drilling</DeepDrilling.label>
  <DeepDrilling.description>Build deep drills for extracting resources from underground. You'll need a ground-penetrating scanner to find the resources.</DeepDrilling.description>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.label>ground-penetrating scanner</GroundPenetratingScanner.label>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.description>Build ground-penetrating scanners that can detect drillable resources under the surface. Requires an advanced component to construct.</GroundPenetratingScanner.description>
  <TransportPod.label>transport pod</TransportPod.label>
  <TransportPod.description>Construct launchable transport pods that you can use to send people and supplies long distances across the planet's surface. Can be used for raiding, travel, sending gifts, and more.</TransportPod.description>
  <MedicineProduction.label>medicine production</MedicineProduction.label>
  <MedicineProduction.description>Produce standard industrial-tech medicine by combining herbal medicine, neutroamine, and cloth.</MedicineProduction.description>
  <LongRangeMineralScanner.label>long-range mineral scanner</LongRangeMineralScanner.label>
  <LongRangeMineralScanner.description>Construct long-range mineral scanners your researchers can use to detect precious minerals across the planet. Can be tuned to find a specific mineral. Requires advanced components to construct.</LongRangeMineralScanner.description>
  <ShieldBelt.label>shields</ShieldBelt.label>
  <ShieldBelt.description>Build wearable shield gear. Shields use momentum-repulsion technology to prevent projectiles from traversing the field boundary.</ShieldBelt.description>
  <PrecisionRifling.label>precision rifling</PrecisionRifling.label>
  <PrecisionRifling.description>Craft precisely-machined guns like assault rifles and sniper rifles.</PrecisionRifling.description>
  <HeavyTurrets.label>autocannon turret</HeavyTurrets.label>
  <HeavyTurrets.description>Produce the heavy autocannon turret.</HeavyTurrets.description>
  <MultibarrelWeapons.label>multibarrel weapons</MultibarrelWeapons.label>
  <MultibarrelWeapons.description>Assemble miniguns.</MultibarrelWeapons.description>
  <MultiAnalyzer.label>multi-analyzer</MultiAnalyzer.label>
  <MultiAnalyzer.description>Build multi-analyzers which increase research speed and allow higher-level research projects.</MultiAnalyzer.description>
  <VitalsMonitor.label>vitals monitor</VitalsMonitor.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Build vitals monitors which improve medical outcomes when placed next to hospital beds.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <Fabrication.label>fabrication</Fabrication.label>
  <Fabrication.description>Build fabrication benches, capable of high-tech projects ranging from component assembly to power armor construction.</Fabrication.description>
  <Fabrication.discoveredLetterTitle>About: Getting advanced components</Fabrication.discoveredLetterTitle>
  <Fabrication.discoveredLetterText>You now have the technology to build a fabrication bench - but it also requires some advanced components to get started. You can collect advanced components several ways:\n\n  -All outlander settlements sell advanced components. Send a caravan to buy some.\n  -Some visiting traders sell advanced components. Invite or wait for them.\n  -Some quests are rewarded with advanced components.</Fabrication.discoveredLetterText>
  <AdvancedFabrication.label>advanced fabrication</AdvancedFabrication.label>
  <AdvancedFabrication.description>Fabricate advanced components from standard components and other materials.</AdvancedFabrication.description>
  <Cryptosleep.label>cryptosleep casket</Cryptosleep.label>
  <Cryptosleep.description>Construct cryptosleep caskets, which can put living beings in a state of indefinite suspended animation.</Cryptosleep.description>
  <ReconArmor.label>recon armor</ReconArmor.label>
  <ReconArmor.description>Craft recon armor, a light powered armor suit used by scout troops who need protection on the move. Note that these also require advanced components.</ReconArmor.description>
  <PoweredArmor.label>marine armor</PoweredArmor.label>
  <PoweredArmor.description>Build marine armor, a general-use powered armor suit used by high-tech shock troops. Note that these also require advanced components.</PoweredArmor.description>
  <ChargedShot.label>pulse-charged munitions</ChargedShot.label>
  <ChargedShot.description>Build weapons which fire pulse-charged munitions for extra damage. Note that these also require advanced components.</ChargedShot.description>
  <Bionics.label>bionic replacements</Bionics.label>
  <Bionics.description>Build high-tech bionic body parts to replace lost limbs and eyes. Requires a skilled doctor to attach.</Bionics.description>
  <SniperTurret.label>uranium slug turret</SniperTurret.label>
  <SniperTurret.description>Produce the armor-penetrating uranium slug turret. It fires uranium slugs which tear through plasteel like paper, but it's less effective at close range.</SniperTurret.description>
  <ShipBasics.label>starflight basics</ShipBasics.label>
  <ShipBasics.description>Construct the structural and supportive elements of a starship. This is the first step in building a ship to leave this star system.</ShipBasics.description>
  <ShipBasics.discoveredLetterTitle>About: Launching the ship</ShipBasics.discoveredLetterTitle>
  <ShipBasics.discoveredLetterText>Escaping from this planet - it would be freedom at last, and maybe a return home.\n\nBut also incredibly dangerous.\n\nMany desperate souls want off this planet. Ship reactors take 15 days to charge up. Once you begin that process, the ship reactor will emit an energy signature detectable from thousands of kilometers away. Raiders will flock to attack you in waves, with an intensity you've never seen. Mechanoids are also known to be attracted to such energy signatures for their own mysterious reasons.\n\nIt won't start until you activate your ship's reactor, but when it does, it'll be ferocious. You'll need to stockpile resources, weapons, and defenses for the onslaught if you hope to escape alive.</ShipBasics.discoveredLetterText>
  <ShipCryptosleep.label>vacuum cryptosleep casket</ShipCryptosleep.label>
  <ShipCryptosleep.description>Construct hardened cryptosleep caskets tough enough to be exposed to vacuum, for transporting people on the years-long journey between stars.</ShipCryptosleep.description>
  <ShipReactor.label>starship reactor</ShipReactor.label>
  <ShipReactor.description>Build a long-duration nuclear reactor to power a starship. Note that reactors have a long startup process that will attract raiders.</ShipReactor.description>
  <ShipEngine.label>Johnson-Tanaka drive</ShipEngine.label>
  <ShipEngine.description>Construct a Johnson-Tanaka drive for a ship. The JT drive can push you to other stars by leveraging quantum scale effects to beam momentum to distant stars. Of course, as with all starships, it still takes many years to get anywhere.</ShipEngine.description>
  <ShipComputerCore.label>machine persuasion</ShipComputerCore.label>
  <ShipComputerCore.description>Build a reward-signal system to persuade an existing persona core into serving as a ship's machine captain. Since people sleep during interstellar travel, a persona core is necessary to handle the complex decisions of a years-long starflight.</ShipComputerCore.description>
  <ShipSensorCluster.label>starflight sensors</ShipSensorCluster.label>
  <ShipSensorCluster.description>Construct long-range sensors for a starship. These sensors are essential for navigation, communication, and threat avoidance.</ShipSensorCluster.description>
</LanguageData>