<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Forbidden_Studies.label>Decipher strange symbols</Forbidden_Studies.label>
  <Forbidden_Studies.description>Deciphers some of the materials language to make further research possible.</Forbidden_Studies.description>
  <Forbidden_Deities.label>Probe occult deities</Forbidden_Deities.label>
  <Forbidden_Deities.description>Repeatable research to discover occult deities to worship.</Forbidden_Deities.description>
  <Forbidden_Lore.label>Study successful cults</Forbidden_Lore.label>
  <Forbidden_Lore.description>Repeatable research to improve the researcher's cult mindedness and social skills during the research process.\n\nThis research is recommended for pawns looking to become preachers.</Forbidden_Lore.description>
  <Forbidden_Attire.label>Ritual Attire</Forbidden_Attire.label>
  <Forbidden_Attire.description>Allows for the design and creation of occult robes, hoods, and various masks. Wearing proper clothing increases chances of successful sacrifices.</Forbidden_Attire.description>
  <Forbidden_Sculptures.label>Sculptures</Forbidden_Sculptures.label>
  <Forbidden_Sculptures.description>Allows for the design and creation of occult sculptures dedicated to otherworldly entities.</Forbidden_Sculptures.description>
  <Forbidden_Obelisks.label>Obelisk Construction</Forbidden_Obelisks.label>
  <Forbidden_Obelisks.description>Allows for the design and construction of occult obelisks.</Forbidden_Obelisks.description>
  <Forbidden_Altar.label>Altar</Forbidden_Altar.label>
  <Forbidden_Altar.description>Allows the creation of an altar of worship to conduct rituals for beings beyond this world.</Forbidden_Altar.description>
  <Forbidden_Sacrifice.label>Altar of Sacrifice</Forbidden_Sacrifice.label>
  <Forbidden_Sacrifice.description>Allows you to upgrade an altar to an altar of sacrifice to show greater appreciation of extradimensional beings.</Forbidden_Sacrifice.description>
  <Forbidden_Reports.label>Chronicling</Forbidden_Reports.label>
  <Forbidden_Reports.description>Adds a Reports button to the altar that shows the most recent sacrifice's results in detail.</Forbidden_Reports.description>
  <Forbidden_Human.label>Human Sacrifice</Forbidden_Human.label>
  <Forbidden_Human.description>Allows you to upgrade an altar to an altar of human sacrifice, allowing for impressive benefits from cosmic entities.</Forbidden_Human.description>
</LanguageData>