<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <agriculture.label>agriculture I</agriculture.label>
  <agriculture.description>Researches plant genetics to unlock new types of plants to grow! \n\n Unlocks a new tier of vegetables to grow. \n\n Unlocks sowing of Snow Beats, Beans, Red Lentils, and Olives.</agriculture.description>
  <agricultureII.label>agriculture II</agricultureII.label>
  <agricultureII.description>Researches plant genetics to unlock new types of plants to grow! \n\n Unlocks a new fruits to grow. Fruit has a higher nutrition and requires less to make meals. \n\n Unlocks sowing of Grapes, Agave, Strawberries, Blueberries, and Watermelons.</agricultureII.description>
  <agricultureIII.label>agriculture III</agricultureIII.label>
  <agricultureIII.description>Researches plant genetics to unlock new and exciting new types of plants to grow! Requires Tree Sowing. \n\n Unlocks new fruit trees to grow. Fruit trees have a longer grow time but a higher yield. \n\n Unlocks sowing of Apples, Bananas, Oranges, and Peaches trees.</agricultureIII.description>
  <VG_Ambrosia.label>ambrosia</VG_Ambrosia.label>
  <VG_Ambrosia.description>Researches the ability to grow ambrosia  in hydroponic basins.</VG_Ambrosia.description>
  <agricultureIV.label>Wild biome plants</agricultureIV.label>
  <agricultureIV.description>Researches plant genetics to unlock new and exciting types of plants to grow! \n\n Unlocks new fruits and trees to grow. Fruit trees have a longer grow time but a higher yield. \n\n Unlocks sowing of cherry, coconut, fig, date trees. Pineapples, cloudberries, and gooseberries.</agricultureIV.description>
  <VG_HoneyTree.label>Honey Bee Tree</VG_HoneyTree.label>
  <VG_HoneyTree.description>Researches engineered bee trees that attract bees to live in and produce honey! Requires Tree Sowing. \n\n Unlocks Bee trees.</VG_HoneyTree.description>
  <Cocoa.description.description>Sow cocoa plants to create your own delicious chocolate. Eating chocolate fulfills the need for recreation, and it's valuable on the market too. \n\nUnlocks Trees and Bushes.</Cocoa.description.description>
</LanguageData>