<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <CTier1.label>awisa</CTier1.label>
  <CTier1.description>The basic citizen of the Collective society is called an Awisa, anyone living in the Collective who doesn't have at least this title is a slave. Awisa do not enjoy many rights and are usually treated without much dignity, and more often than not they are still considered property of the Collective. \n\nAwisa are often looked down upon even by those just immediately above them in status, such as the Akkumia.</CTier1.description>
  <CTier2.label>akkumia</CTier2.label>
  <CTier2.description>Immediately above the Awisa, the Akkumia is an average ranking citizen of the Collective society but generally do not have many rights. Together, the Akkumia, the Awisa, and those in slavery form the vast majority of the population in the Collective.\n\nAkkumia are usually neglected as a member of the Collective society, and many Akkumia would prefer life outside of the Collective.</CTier2.description>
  <CTier3.label>dykumia</CTier3.label>
  <CTier3.description>The Dykumia are the equivalent to privledged citizens in the Collective. They are mostly free to persue their own ambitions, as long as their interests are in line with the Collective's strict laws and regulation. Dykumia enjoy comforts within the Collective, but still live in fear from under the nobility.</CTier3.description>
  <CTier4.label>Aklugan</CTier4.label>
  <CTier4.description>Aklugan are the lowest caste of nobility within the Collective, enjoying far more wealth and status than the worker castes of the Collective.\n\nAklugan serve an important role for the Collective, branching the connection between the worker castes with nobility. They serve as administrators or police, enforcing the will of the Collective upon the labor force.</CTier4.description>
  <CTier5.label>Arkkian</CTier5.label>
  <CTier5.description>The Arkkian are the middle caste of the Collective's nobility, they often serve as lawmakers, chief administrators, or generals.\n\nThey face no social pressures that dissuade independent thought, unlike the lower castes.</CTier5.description>
  <CTier6.label>dyarkkian</CTier6.label>
  <CTier6.description>The dyarkkian are the highest caste of the Collective's nobility that can be achieved, their power is only second to the Ekris and those they appoint.</CTier6.description>
  <CTier7.label>ekarkkian</CTier7.label>
  <CTier7.description>The Ekarkkian are the highest caste of nobility within the Collective under the Ekris, they dictate most administrative affairs and govern the Collective. The Ekarkkian are an unearnable title, as they are specifically appointed by the Ekris. Despite prestigious or ambitious individuals being selected, the criteria for it is unknown and sometimes seemingly random citizens are selected by the Ekris. The Ekarkkians usually govern the collective as the highest power; as the Ekris only rarely make decrees.</CTier7.description>
  <CTier8.label>ekris</CTier8.label>
  <CTier8.description>The Ekris are the mysterious ruling body of the Collective, Collective loyalists consider their dogma to be divine. This title cannot be earned, only inherited, as the Ekris are composed of 14 ancient lines of Crystalloid families. Their power is absolute on any matter considering the Collective.\n\nThe Ekris are shrouded in mystery, they rarely speak to the Collective or give orders, leading to wide speculation as to what their actual goals are.</CTier8.description>
</LanguageData>