<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Peaceful.label>peaceful</Peaceful.label>
  <Peaceful.description>Build a community in a sandbox environment. Major direct threats are disabled, but challenges like disease, mental breaks, and mad animals can still occur.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Players who want to learn the game mechanics with minimal pressure.
- Players who just want to build.
- Players who just want to relax.</Peaceful.description>
  <Easy.label>community builder</Easy.label>
  <Easy.description>Build a community with a taste of danger. Threats appear, but they're weakened.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Players who are new to this kind of game.
- Players who want to build a perfect colony.
- Players who want to relax.</Easy.description>
  <Medium.label>adventure story</Medium.label>
  <Medium.description>There's room to grow and thrive, but it's still a dangerous planet.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Experienced strategy gamers on their first game of RimWorld.
- Experienced RimWorld players who want some breathing room to pursue funny or weird goals.</Medium.description>
  <Rough.label>strive to survive</Rough.label>
  <Rough.description>Strive to survive on a rough, tough planet. There will be triumph and tragedy.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Experienced players who want a rough story requiring skill to survive.</Rough.description>
  <Hard.label>blood and dust</Hard.label>
  <Hard.description>Face brutal survival challenges. Even if you play well, people will die. You will need to anticipate threats before they arrive, and seek out every advantage.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Experienced players who want to struggle to survive.</Hard.description>
  <Extreme.label>losing is fun</Extreme.label>
  <Extreme.description>This setting is designed to be unfair. Huge threats will crash upon you without mercy until your colony dies. Only choose this setting if you are happy with the drama of struggling and dying.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Experienced players who want to face a brutal, unfair challenge where even great skill may not prevent death.
- Lovers of tragedy.
- Digital masochists.</Extreme.description>
  <Custom.label>Custom</Custom.label>
  <Custom.description>This setting allows you to define your own playstyle in detail.

(*SectionTitle)Recommended for:(/SectionTitle)

- Players who are happy with one of the standard playstyles levels, but want to change a few things.
- Players who want to experiment with something different.</Custom.description>
</LanguageData>