<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ChefMaid.label>ChefMaid Costume</ChefMaid.label>
  <ChefMaid.description>The ChefMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, cooking skill and overall working speed.</ChefMaid.description>
  <CleanerMaid.label>CleanerMaid Costume</CleanerMaid.label>
  <CleanerMaid.description>The CleanerMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, harvest skill, cleaning skill and overall working speed.</CleanerMaid.description>
  <CrafterMaid.label>CrafterMaid Costume</CrafterMaid.label>
  <CrafterMaid.description>The CrafterMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, studying skill, crafting skill and overall working speed.</CrafterMaid.description>
  <FightMaid.label>FightMaid Costume</FightMaid.label>
  <FightMaid.description>The FightMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, defensive power, accuracy, and overall working speed.</FightMaid.description>
  <HeaderMaid.label>HeaderMaid Costume</HeaderMaid.label>
  <HeaderMaid.description>The HeaderMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, recruit prisoner chance, social contact skill and overall working speed.</HeaderMaid.description>
  <NurseMaid.label>NurseMaid Costume</NurseMaid.label>
  <NurseMaid.description>The NurseMaid Costume. This suit will increasing the moving speed, surgery success chance, and overall working speed.</NurseMaid.description>
  <MaidHatNA.label>Maid Hat A</MaidHatNA.label>
  <MaidHatNA.description>Maid Hat type A, can protect your maid's head. Increasing work speed and moving speed.</MaidHatNA.description>
  <MaidHatNB.label>Maid Hat B</MaidHatNB.label>
  <MaidHatNB.description>Maid Hat type B, Design for fightmaid. This hat can protect your maid's head. Increasing speed, moving speed, and defensive power.</MaidHatNB.description>
  <MaidHatNC.label>Maid Hat C</MaidHatNC.label>
  <MaidHatNC.description>Maid Hat type C, can protect your maid's head. Increasing work speed and moving speed.</MaidHatNC.description>
  <MaidCostumeCraftingTable.label>Maid Costume Crafting Work Table</MaidCostumeCraftingTable.label>
  <MaidCostumeCraftingTable.description>A working table to make maid costume.</MaidCostumeCraftingTable.description>
</LanguageData>