<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DrillArm.label>drill arm</DrillArm.label>
  <DrillArm.description>A mechanical arm replacement for speeding up mining. It has a built-in snake drill, which allows the miner to rapidly find and exploit weak lines in the rock. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</DrillArm.description>
  
  <ElbowBlade.label>elbow blade</ElbowBlade.label>
  <ElbowBlade.description>A razor-sharp blade that extends at will from a hidden opening at the end of the ulna. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating slice attacks.</ElbowBlade.description>
  
  <FieldHand.label>field hand</FieldHand.label>
  <FieldHand.description>This mechanical hand replacement is made to speed up the sowing and harvesting tasks of a farmer. Multiple telescoping finger-like protrusions can simultaneously harvest from several points on the same plant, or precisely sow several holes at once. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</FieldHand.description>
  
  <HandTalon.label>hand talon</HandTalon.label>
  <HandTalon.description>A razor-sharp talon which extends from a hidden opening between the middle and ring fingers. The talon is longer than the palm, but it becomes flexible upon retracting, allowing the user to curl it up and conceal it inside the hand. It can perform rapid slashing attacks, but is poor at penetrating armor.</HandTalon.description>
  
  <KneeSpike.label>knee spike</KneeSpike.label>
  <KneeSpike.description>A spike that extends at will from a hidden opening on the front of the knee. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating stabbing attacks which penetrate even thick armor.</KneeSpike.description>
  
  <Mindscrew.label>mindscrew</Mindscrew.label>
  <Mindscrew.description>Inflicts continuous pain on the user. Mindscrews are used by some authorities as a long-term punishment. Some even install them voluntarily as a demonstration of ideological or religious devotion.</Mindscrew.description>
  
  <VenomFangs.label>venom fangs</VenomFangs.label>
  <VenomFangs.description>A pair of injectors implanted through the canine teeth, connected to a venom pump. The user can bite an enemy, extend the injectors, and pump venom into the target.</VenomFangs.description>
  
  <VenomTalon.label>venom talon</VenomTalon.label>
  <VenomTalon.description>A retractable finger talon connected to a venom pump in the lower arm. The user can scratch an enemy while squirting venom into the wound. The talon is designed to be installed in the middle finger. It's fast, but poor at penetrating armor.</VenomTalon.description>
</LanguageData>