<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AnimaFiber.label>anima fiber</AnimaFiber.label>
  <AnimaFiber.description>These fibers were harvested from domesticated anima grass and can be used for crafting clothes for psycasters.</AnimaFiber.description>
  <Apparel_AnimaCrown.label>anima crown</Apparel_AnimaCrown.label>
  <Apparel_AnimaCrown.description>A crown for the chiefs of the psycaster tribes. Enhances psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation.</Apparel_AnimaCrown.description>
  <Apparel_AnimaWarMask.label>anima war mask</Apparel_AnimaWarMask.label>
  <Apparel_AnimaWarMask.description>An artistically terrifying war mask that hides the wearer's face and makes them more confident. Thanks to the anima fibers and jade used in the production of the mask, it can enhance the psycaster's psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation.</Apparel_AnimaWarMask.description>
  <Apparel_AnimaWarVeil.label>anima war veil</Apparel_AnimaWarVeil.label>
  <Apparel_AnimaWarVeil.description>A war veil, made out of reinforced cloth torn to appear damaged in combat. Some believe this functions as a talisman of courage.</Apparel_AnimaWarVeil.description>
  <Apparel_AnimaTribal.label>anima tribalwear</Apparel_AnimaTribal.label>
  <Apparel_AnimaTribal.description>A full-body garment crafted using anima fibers specially for tribal psycasters.</Apparel_AnimaTribal.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.label>anima staff</MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.description>A wooden staff threaded with anima fibers. While it is a solid melee weapon, its main purpose is to enhance the wielder's psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation, allowing more use of psychic powers.</MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.tools.0.label>head</MeleeWeapon_AnimaStaff.tools.0.label>
  <Plant_DomesticatedAnimaGrass.label>domesticated anima grass</Plant_DomesticatedAnimaGrass.label>
  <Plant_DomesticatedAnimaGrass.description>Ancient psycaster tribes managed to domesticate the anima grass and use it to harvest so-called "anima fiber" that can be used as a material for clothes for psycasters.</Plant_DomesticatedAnimaGrass.description>
</LanguageData>