<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <TM_ArcaneConduitTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Arcane Conduit</TM_ArcaneConduitTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_ArcaneConduitTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is abnormally receptive to the ebb and flow of mana, [PAWN_pronoun] will gain mana 40% faster than normal but [PAWN_possessive] maximum mana capacity is reduced by 20.</TM_ArcaneConduitTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_ManaWellTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Mana Well</TM_ManaWellTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_ManaWellTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has an increased resistance to the ebb and flow of mana which allows [PAWN_objective] to hold an additional 40 mana, but reduces [PAWN_possessive] mana regeneration by 20%.</TM_ManaWellTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_BoundlessTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Boundless</TM_BoundlessTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_BoundlessTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] excels at combat arts and is able to execute combat maneuvers 40% more frequently, however, [PAWN_possessive] talent has fostered an arrogant attitude that reduces [PAWN_possessive] experience gain by 25% and causes other fighters to dislike [PAWN_objective].</TM_BoundlessTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_FaeBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Fae blood</TM_FaeBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_FaeBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a descendant of fae folk and has a natural connection to the arcane. [PAWN_possessive] arcane resistance is reduced by 40% but mana regeneration and maximum mana is increased by 20%. Spell costs are reduced by 10%.</TM_FaeBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_GiantsBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Giants blood</TM_GiantsBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_GiantsBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a descendant of giants - endowed with with great strength and stamina, though slow to recover. [PAWN_possessive] max stamina is increased by 80%, but stamina regeneration is reduced by 40%. Any attack made while using a melee weapon, or unarmed, deals an additional 25% damage.</TM_GiantsBloodTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_EnlightenedTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Enlightened</TM_EnlightenedTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_EnlightenedTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is blessed by magic, able to harness its power without suffering the full side-effects. Psychic sensitivity is increased by 50% and any magic ability used only incurs half the normal arcane weakness.</TM_EnlightenedTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_CursedTD.degreeDatas.0.label>Cursed</TM_CursedTD.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_CursedTD.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is cursed by magic - tormented by the constant, burning rush of power through [PAWN_possessive] being, and can only gain relief by expending arcane energy. [PAWN_nameDef] will slowly accumulate arcane weakness up until [PAWN_pronoun] would become catatonic, and may become catatonic at any point while at this threshold. Using magical abilities that would normally incur arcane weakness will instead proportionally reduce arcane weakness, as well as the effects of the curse.</TM_CursedTD.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_OKWithDeath.degreeDatas.0.label>Unaffected by death</TM_OKWithDeath.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_OKWithDeath.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has accepted that death is another part of life and doesn't get upset when learning about a dead ally or seeing one of the undead.</TM_OKWithDeath.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Undead.degreeDatas.0.label>Undead</Undead.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Undead.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has been reanimated as an undead.</Undead.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Gifted.degreeDatas.0.label>magically gifted</TM_Gifted.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Gifted.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has a magical gift. [PAWN_pronoun] can harness this gift to become a mage by studying the mysterious secrets within an arcane script.</TM_Gifted.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Empath.degreeDatas.0.label>Empath</TM_Empath.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Empath.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an empath, able to feel and manipulate the emotions of those around [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_possessive]'s abilities are tied to magic, but have affected [PAWN_objective] on a more innate level. However, with training, [PAWN_nameDef] can still become an adept magic user. For better or worse, empath's have a very strong presence and can easily read the presence of others; the effectiveness of their abilities are closely tied to their aptitude for overcoming another's defenses.</TM_Empath.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Wanderer.degreeDatas.0.label>Wanderer</TM_Wanderer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Wanderer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a wanderer; an outcast, half-breed mage class frequently dubbed a hedge-mage. [PAWN_possessive] carefree personality has kept [PAWN_possessive] from developing class abilities. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] has learned to improve on a vast number of utility abilities that allow [PAWN_objective] to adapt to any situation.
		
Wanderers prefer the open road and gain a mood boost for being in a caravan. Caravans with a wanderer will ignore the movement penalties of any world tile. However, their wanderlust will cause them to suffer a mood penalty for remaining at a colony for too long.</TM_Wanderer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <InnerFire.degreeDatas.0.label>Fire mage</InnerFire.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <InnerFire.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the elements of fire.</InnerFire.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <HeartOfFrost.degreeDatas.0.label>Ice mage</HeartOfFrost.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <HeartOfFrost.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the elements of water.</HeartOfFrost.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <StormBorn.degreeDatas.0.label>Lightning mage</StormBorn.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <StormBorn.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the elements of lightning.</StormBorn.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Arcanist.degreeDatas.0.label>Arcane mage</Arcanist.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Arcanist.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with arcane forces, interacting directly with raw arcane power to move matter and energy at will.</Arcanist.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Druid.degreeDatas.0.label>Druid</Druid.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Druid.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the forces of nature.</Druid.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Paladin.degreeDatas.0.label>Paladin</Paladin.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Paladin.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has been bestowed with divine might and has sworn to uphold justice wherever [PAWN_pronoun] stands.</Paladin.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Summoner.degreeDatas.0.label>Summoner</Summoner.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Summoner.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is able to summon beings and materialize objects from other planes of existence.</Summoner.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Necromancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Necromancer</Necromancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Necromancer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the forces of death.</Necromancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Lich.degreeDatas.0.label>Lich</Lich.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Lich.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has transformed into a lich, forsaking life in exchange for an power and an immortal existence. [PAWN_pronoun] disdains menial taks, choosing to employ undead for trivial matters.</Lich.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Priest.degreeDatas.0.label>Priest</Priest.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Priest.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the forces of life and healing and has taken a vow against harming others.</Priest.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.0.label>Entertainer</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a natural entertainer, able to lighten the mood and lift the spirits of everyone around [PAWN_objective].</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.1.label>Performer</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a performer; expanding on natural talent, [PAWN_pronoun] has begun to take an conscious role to improve the mood of other colonists.</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.2.label>Minstrel</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.2.description>Everyone loves being around [PAWN_nameDef]. [PAWN_pronoun] has talent, wit and skill in many forms of entertainment and is able to make a personal connection with almost everyone.</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.2.description>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.3.label>Bard</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.3.label>
  <TM_Bard.degreeDatas.3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a master entertainer. Sharp wit, deft hands, and dry humor are [PAWN_possessive] weapons, and [PAWN_pronoun] is a master of all [PAWN_possessive] weapons.</TM_Bard.degreeDatas.3.description>
  <Succubus.degreeDatas.0.label>Succubus</Succubus.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Succubus.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has a strange genetic strain that grants her enhanced physical attributes. She is also extremely attractive with an exotic facial structure that captures the eye. A succubus is more likely to exploit her physical advantages and have others do her work for her. [PAWN_possessive] succubus charm has its disadvantages and can cause some to become jealous and even despise [PAWN_objective].</Succubus.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Warlock.degreeDatas.0.label>Warlock</Warlock.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Warlock.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a Warlock - able to manifest physical and demonic forces using his unique access to arcane power. The warlock shares the same genetic mixture as a succubus, but as a male, [PAWN_pronoun] is affected with mental enhancements that include clairvoyance and telekineses. The warlock can occasionally affect the outcome of a social interaction using their mental capabilities, regardless of how the interaction actually occurred.</Warlock.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Geomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Geomancer</Geomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Geomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is attuned with the earth and natural order, drawing power from the physical realm and intertwining it with arcane energy. [PAWN_pronoun] is capable of reinforcing physical elements, and bending them, as [PAWN_pronoun] needs.</Geomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Technomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Technomancer</Technomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Technomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has learned to see magic and science as two parts of the same force and is able to use arcane power to interface directly with components of technology. [PAWN_pronoun] is capable of manipulating objects with advanced mechanics, electronics, or computing it to achieve [PAWN_possessive] goals, but has difficulty interacting with biological systems.</Technomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <BloodMage.degreeDatas.0.label>Blood Mage</BloodMage.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <BloodMage.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a blood mage and has consigned to the dark art of manipulating the life blood of living things as a means of increasing [PAWN_possessive] power.\n\nAs a blood mage, [PAWN_nameDef] has learned to control the life force within and command it to [PAWN_possessive] will. [PAWN_possessive] connection to life makes it easier to associate with other living things, but doesn't appreciate effort without immediate results.</BloodMage.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Enchanter.degreeDatas.0.label>Enchanter</Enchanter.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Enchanter.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an enchanter, attuned to the composition of matter and materials. [PAWN_pronoun] can manipulate matter to [PAWN_possessive] will, frequently in unnatural ways, and [PAWN_possessive] powers of transmutation can be permanent when sufficient effort is applied.</Enchanter.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Chronomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Chronomancer</Chronomancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Chronomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a chronomancer. Through arcane sight, [PAWN_pronoun] is able to view reality as it once was and as it could be, and can manipulate objects between those realities.</Chronomancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <ChaosMage.degreeDatas.0.label>Chaos Mage</ChaosMage.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <ChaosMage.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has rejected all predefined magic paths and refuses to attribute objective reality in [PAWN_possessive] search for power; there are no truths, all magic is permitted. This tradition has enabled [PAWN_nameDef] to learn any type of magic, although [PAWN_pronoun] will never master any.</ChaosMage.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_TheShadow.degreeDatas.0.label>Shadow</TM_TheShadow.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_TheShadow.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a half-breed demon with an affinity for shadow magic. [PAWN_pronoun] has developed [PAWN_possessive] unique talents through combat training and physical conditioning making [PAWN_objective] the perfect assassin.</TM_TheShadow.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Brightmage.degreeDatas.0.label>Brightmage</TM_Brightmage.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Brightmage.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a brightmage, able to harness the powers of light to purge evil. [PAWN_pronoun] approaches any task with an unrivaled fervor that usually places [PAWN_objective] at the forefront. Being a Brightmage introduces a dependency on the sun and light, because of this, [PAWN_nameDef] has developed an intense hatred for shadowy and dark caricatures.</TM_Brightmage.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Shaman.degreeDatas.0.label>Shaman</TM_Shaman.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Shaman.degreeDatas.0.description>Shamans take a more harmonious approach to arcane powers than most mages, choosing to pursue a path that works with the ebb and flow of magic to offset or enhance the natural order. [PAWN_nameDef] is kin to the spirit realm and more attuned to nature and its elements.</TM_Shaman.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Golemancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Golemancer</TM_Golemancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Golemancer.degreeDatas.0.description>Golemancers prefer to weave their magic through powerful runes and sigils that are able to transfer purpose into an object. [PAWN_nameDef] is no exception; [PAWN_pronoun] can create runes that enhance basic mechanics, alter chemicals in biological matter, and animate mundane material into life-like, monstrous creatures. Golemancers are most effective when channeling their magic through symbols and find it more difficult to convert mana to energy directly but are also have higher arcane resistances. Most golemancers tend to find rocks more interesting than people and have little concern for cleanliness.</TM_Golemancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Possessed.degreeDatas.0.label>Possessed</TM_Possessed.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Possessed.degreeDatas.0.description>The body of [PAWN_nameDef] is inhabited by the spirit of another pawn. Possession in a living pawn creates an internal conflict as the functions of the body are shared between two souls. This conflict can be reduced if personalities align, but will become further aggravated if they contrast. Possession of a deceased pawn will not experience mental conflicts, but will slowly deplete the energy of the possessing spirit. Spirit can be recharged through meditation or absorption.</TM_Possessed.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Possessor.degreeDatas.0.label>Spirit</TM_Possessor.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Possessor.degreeDatas.0.description>The body of [PAWN_nameDef] is inhabited by the spirit of another pawn. Possession in a living pawn creates an internal conflict as the functions of the body are shared between two souls. This conflict can be reduced if personalities align, but will become further aggravated if they contrast. Possession of a deceased pawn will not experience mental conflicts, but will slowly deplete the energy of the possessing spirit. Spirit can be recharged through meditation or absorption.</TM_Possessor.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <PhysicalProdigy.degreeDatas.0.label>physically adept</PhysicalProdigy.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <PhysicalProdigy.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is physically adept and has potential to learn special combat forms.</PhysicalProdigy.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Wayfarer.degreeDatas.0.label>Wayfarer</TM_Wayfarer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Wayfarer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a wayfarer; an self-disciplined fighter that excels at tricks and dirty fighting. [PAWN_possessive] carefree personality has kept [PAWN_objective] from developing class abilities. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] has learned to improve a vast number of utility abilities that allow [PAWN_objective] to adapt to any situation.

Wayfarers prefer the open road and will gain a mood boost for being in a caravan, and any caravan with a wayfarer will travel 25% faster. However, wayfarers will suffer a mood penalty if they remain at colony for too long.</TM_Wayfarer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Apothecary.degreeDatas.0.label>Apothecary</TM_Apothecary.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Apothecary.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an apothecary, trained in the preparation of medicines, balms, tinctures and drugs. [PAWN_possessive] profession exhibits strict discipline and dedication, and [PAWN_pronoun] has learned to apply [PAWN_possessive] discipline to more generic, physical skills. With training, [PAWN_pronoun] can become capable in many combat techniques to augment [PAWN_possessive] skill in herbs.</TM_Apothecary.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Gladiator.degreeDatas.0.label>Gladiator</Gladiator.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Gladiator.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has learned how to train the Gladiator combat style.</Gladiator.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.0.label>Woodsman</Ranger.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a trained woodsman; preferring the silence and lethality of a bow and armed with field-craft and cunning, [PAWN_pronoun] is prepared to defend [PAWN_possessive] land from invaders.</Ranger.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.1.label>Hunter</Ranger.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a hunter; [PAWN_pronoun] employs field-craft, cunning, and skill with a bow to defend [PAWN_possessive] land from invaders.</Ranger.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.2.label>Scout</Ranger.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a scout; comfortable in the wilds, and relied upon to be the eyes and ears of a colony. [PAWN_pronoun] employs expertise in field-craft, cunning, and the bow to defend [PAWN_possessive] land from invaders.</Ranger.degreeDatas.2.description>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.3.label>Ranger</Ranger.degreeDatas.3.label>
  <Ranger.degreeDatas.3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a ranger; master of the wilds.  [PAWN_pronoun] is a master of [PAWN_possessive] craft and defender of [PAWN_possessive] land.</Ranger.degreeDatas.3.description>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.0.label>Sharpshooter</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has trained to become a sniper, skilled in the economy and accuracy of long range, small arms combat. Training to become a sniper has caused some colonists to be uncomfortable around [PAWN_objective], not that [PAWN_pronoun] cares.</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.1.label>Sniper</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has trained to become a sniper, skilled in the economy and accuracy of long range, small arms combat. Becoming a sniper has caused [PAWN_objective] to become distanced from other colonists and somewhat unapproachable, not that [PAWN_pronoun] cares.</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.2.label>Master Sniper</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a master sniper, skilled in the economy and accuracy of long range, small arms combat. Being a sniper has made [PAWN_objective] avoid other colonists, not that they care.</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.2.description>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.3.label>Legendary Sniper</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.3.label>
  <TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a legendary sniper, skilled in the economy and accuracy of long range, small arms combat.  Other colonists avoid eye contact and whisper in corners about how dangerous [PAWN_pronoun] is and that suits [PAWN_objective] just fine.</TM_Sniper.degreeDatas.3.description>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.0.label>Bladesman</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is training to become a master of the blade and excels at fighting in melee combat.</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.1.label>Blademaster</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.1.label>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has trained to become a sword master, dangerously skilled in melee combat.</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.1.description>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.2.label>Bladedancer</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.2.label>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a blade dancer, highly skilled in melee combat.  Watching [PAWN_objective] fight is like watching a dance, every action precise and flawless as it flows from one form into another.</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.2.description>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.3.label>Legendary bladedancer</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.3.label>
  <Bladedancer.degreeDatas.3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has become a legend, [PAWN_possessive] skill in melee combat is is known across the world. [PAWN_possessive] skill in combat makes it look as if each movement, each strike, is merely a stitch in a tapestry that depicts [PAWN_possessive] victory.</Bladedancer.degreeDatas.3.description>
  <Faceless.degreeDatas.0.label>Faceless</Faceless.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <Faceless.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a master of disguise and imitation; able to manipulate and capture the muscle and mental actions of another and release it as their own.</Faceless.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Psionic.degreeDatas.0.label>Psionic</TM_Psionic.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Psionic.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a Psionic - able to manifest mental willpower into raw energy without the use of a psychic amplifier. [PAWN_pronoun] is able to project psionic energy but finds it easier and more efficient to apply it as an extension of [PAWN_possessive] body. For this reason, [PAWN_pronoun] prefers to be free of encumbering weapons when manifesting psionic energy.

[PAWN_nameDef] has become less social since developing psionic powers, preferring to be unhindered by other pawns.

*The regeneration rate of psionic energy is based on psychic sensitivity - reducing sensitivity to 0 will prevent psionic energy from regenerating.</TM_Psionic.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <DeathKnight.degreeDatas.0.label>Death Knight</DeathKnight.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <DeathKnight.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a Death Knight - harbinger of doom and a representative of the ever approaching inevitability of death and decay. [PAWN_possessive] solemn attitude makes most pawns uneasy and even fewer approve of [PAWN_possessive] methods.</DeathKnight.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Monk.degreeDatas.0.label>Monk</TM_Monk.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Monk.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a Monk, dedicated to mastering Chi - the energy that connects all life in the universe. [PAWN_pronoun] harnesses Chi to create magical effects and exceed [PAWN_possessive] physical capabilities. [PAWN_nameDef] is also able to disrupt the Chi in others, affecting their command over spells and abilities.</TM_Monk.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_Commander.degreeDatas.0.label>Commander</TM_Commander.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_Commander.degreeDatas.0.description>As a Commander, [PAWN_nameDef] exhibits a charismatic personality and stalwart presence that makes other pawns want to follow [PAWN_possessive] lead. Commander's utilize the weight of their presence to inspire nearby pawns, and when that's not enough, they can issue orders that drive their followers to victory. Because [PAWN_nameDef] is used to everyone doing [PAWN_possessive] bidding, [PAWN_pronoun] considers menial tasks beneath [PAWN_possessive] status, and is generally a lackluster worker.</TM_Commander.degreeDatas.0.description>
  <TM_SuperSoldier.degreeDatas.0.label>Super Soldier</TM_SuperSoldier.degreeDatas.0.label>
  <TM_SuperSoldier.degreeDatas.0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a highly trained Soldier, specializing in pistol, shotgun, or rifle weapons. [PAWN_possessive] weapon specialization is augmented by a standard set of combat training. Super Soldiers are trained to be aggressive and consider violence the natural solution to any argument.</TM_SuperSoldier.degreeDatas.0.description>
</LanguageData>