<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Apparello_GSkin.label>jumpsuit</Apparello_GSkin.label>
  <Apparello_GSkin.description>A basic Jumpsuit. Normally seen worn on Glitterworld light infantry, officials and especially firefighters for it's heat absorbing properties</Apparello_GSkin.description>
  <Apparello_XcomOne.label>overalls</Apparello_XcomOne.label>
  <Apparello_XcomOne.description>Spaceship engineers all across the galaxy are known to wear these for the resistance they provide against their worst enemy: The electric cables.</Apparello_XcomOne.description>
  <Apparello_Standissue.label>standard issue overalls</Apparello_Standissue.label>
  <Apparello_Standissue.description>Standard military issue air force overalls. Very common amongst orbital drop squads</Apparello_Standissue.description>
  <Apparello_SFSurge.description>Starfleet medical officer's uniform coat. Most often seen on Starfleet doctors. Doctors wearing garments like these would only need to say "You tell that to your wife yourself" and all the blood plasma packs would be plugged in to the blood vessels, dodging the devastating loss of life no other medical personnel could even hope to accomplish</Apparello_SFSurge.description>
  <Apparello_SFSurge.label>medical uniform coat</Apparello_SFSurge.label>
  <Apparello_Sheet.label>padded vest</Apparello_Sheet.label>
  <Apparello_Sheet.description>Crude Leather padding for added protection against blunt damage.</Apparello_Sheet.description>
  <Apparello_Gspot.label>alloy vest</Apparello_Gspot.label>
  <Apparello_Gspot.description>Standard issue protective vest on the glitterworlds. Made of multiple layers of extremely light but strong alloy.</Apparello_Gspot.description>
  <Apparello_Gshell.label>light power armor</Apparello_Gshell.label>
  <Apparello_Gshell.description>Powered light armor, fashioned after the infamous Light power armor mark IV which comes with attached GlitOrion® hip'n'hop™ thrusters, which enables slightly faster movement.</Apparello_Gshell.description>
  <Apparello_MedicalApron.label>surgeon's apron</Apparello_MedicalApron.label>
  <Apparello_MedicalApron.description>Lovely plastic apron for all your bloodspilling needs.</Apparello_MedicalApron.description>
  <Apparello_Smithaprontosaurus.label>bib apron</Apparello_Smithaprontosaurus.label>
  <Apparello_Smithaprontosaurus.description>These kind of hardened leather aprons are used by professionals of many trades.</Apparello_Smithaprontosaurus.description>
  <Apparello_Cookaprontosaurus.label>apron</Apparello_Cookaprontosaurus.label>
  <Apparello_Cookaprontosaurus.description>Pocketed cloth apron intended for enhancing your housekeeping experience. It's a hygiene thing, you wouldn't understand.</Apparello_Cookaprontosaurus.description>
  <Apparello_Trypophobiaa.description>"What is a trader? A miserable little pile of bags" ~Count Dravania, moments before being lynched by an angry mob.</Apparello_Trypophobiaa.description>
  <Apparello_Trypophobiaa.label>trader's coat</Apparello_Trypophobiaa.label>
  <Apparello_PonPon.description>Gunslinger's second best friend, Right after the sixshooter and Ten-Gallon Stetson! No, wait make that the third best.</Apparello_PonPon.description>
  <Apparello_PonPon.label>poncho</Apparello_PonPon.label>
  <Apparello_Longlylonglong.label>longcoat</Apparello_Longlylonglong.label>
  <Apparello_Longlylonglong.description>Very, very warm and majestic.</Apparello_Longlylonglong.description>
  <Apparello_Skull.label>raider jacket</Apparello_Skull.label>
  <Apparello_Skull.description>Your basic jacket modified with crude shoulderpads and spikes.</Apparello_Skull.description>
  <Apparello_Preston.description>Captain's uniform jacket. Gives the wearer very commanding presence. Most often seen on Starfleet admirals. Commanders wearing garments like these would only need to say "Make it so" and all the tachyon colliders would be rerouted to the shields to withstand the devastating blast no other ships could even hope to survive</Apparello_Preston.description>
  <Apparello_Preston.label>uniform coat</Apparello_Preston.label>
  <Apparello_Brocade.label>brocade vest</Apparello_Brocade.label>
  <Apparello_Brocade.description>Always keep calm and collected. And wear brocade. The definite go to piece of apparel for any gentleguy or gal</Apparello_Brocade.description>
  <Apparello_Urbulence.label>mesh shirt</Apparello_Urbulence.label>
  <Apparello_Urbulence.description>All the punks felt lucky wearing these.</Apparello_Urbulence.description>
  <Apparel_UniPjays.label>union suit</Apparel_UniPjays.label>
  <Apparel_UniPjays.description>A full-body garment for cold nights. Comes with a buttflap for convenience.</Apparel_UniPjays.description>
  <Apparello_Orkpad.description>Shoulderpads cobbled together from metal scraps. All painted and ready for action!</Apparello_Orkpad.description>
  <Apparello_Orkpad.label>metal shoulderpads</Apparello_Orkpad.label>
  <Apparello_Urpad.description>Shoulderpads cobbled together from urban scraps. Sometimes even leather</Apparello_Urpad.description>
  <Apparello_Urpad.label>shoulderpads</Apparello_Urpad.label>
  <Apparello_Ammobelt.label>bandolier</Apparello_Ammobelt.label>
  <Apparello_Ammobelt.description>Belt designed for carrying ammunition.</Apparello_Ammobelt.description>
  <Apparello_Urbskin.label>urban trousers</Apparello_Urbskin.label>
  <Apparello_Urbskin.description>Trousers with suspenders, leave them hanging for that urban look</Apparello_Urbskin.description>
  <Apparello_Suspender.label>stablehand trousers</Apparello_Suspender.label>
  <Apparello_Suspender.description>Ain't a chap on earf lookin' as honest as one wearin' these. With these equipped one should feel more comfortable wading through mud and filth and therefore more inclined to get the job done without distractions</Apparello_Suspender.description>
  <Apparello_Armorpants.label>padded pants</Apparello_Armorpants.label>
  <Apparello_Armorpants.description>Pair of pants with extra padding in key locations.</Apparello_Armorpants.description>
  <Apparello_Spacemarinepants.label>spacemarine leggings</Apparello_Spacemarinepants.label>
  <Apparello_Spacemarinepants.description>Highly advanced plasteel leggings</Apparello_Spacemarinepants.description>
  <Apparello_Spacerpants.label>enviro-leggings</Apparello_Spacerpants.label>
  <Apparello_Spacerpants.description>High quality and adapts well to temperature changes. Ideal for space exploration</Apparello_Spacerpants.description>
  <Apparello_Chapel.label>chaps</Apparello_Chapel.label>
  <Apparello_Chapel.description>Chaps with holsters. All the fastest shots wore these. They usually got shot in the back. Tinkle winkle moonshine, probably should wear some pants with these.</Apparello_Chapel.description>
  <Apparello_TribalPants.label>waistcloth</Apparello_TribalPants.label>
  <Apparello_TribalPants.description>Waistcloth. They itch a little.</Apparello_TribalPants.description>
  <Apparello_Holdem.label>fancy pants</Apparello_Holdem.label>
  <Apparello_Holdem.description>They're very stylish.</Apparello_Holdem.description>
  <Apparello_Scrapants.label>patch pants</Apparello_Scrapants.label>
  <Apparello_Scrapants.description>very crude and ugly pair of pants.</Apparello_Scrapants.description>
  <Apparello_Pollypocket.label>cargo pants</Apparello_Pollypocket.label>
  <Apparello_Pollypocket.description>Trousers with huge pocket space. They help weakened beings to carry more. Ideal for construction purposes.</Apparello_Pollypocket.description>
  <Apparello_Jeans.label>jeans</Apparello_Jeans.label>
  <Apparello_Jeans.description>Sturdy farmer pants. Designed for mucking about on the field.</Apparello_Jeans.description>
  <Apparello_Jodhpurs.label>jodhpurs</Apparello_Jodhpurs.label>
  <Apparello_Jodhpurs.description>Anyone wearing these will have a very commanding presence towards simple minded creatures, like animals.</Apparello_Jodhpurs.description>
  <Apparello_Skirtwirly.label>skirt</Apparello_Skirtwirly.label>
  <Apparello_Skirtwirly.description>For when your legs need all that extra space.</Apparello_Skirtwirly.description>
  <Apparello_Lederhose.label>leather pants</Apparello_Lederhose.label>
  <Apparello_Lederhose.description>Leather pants (sometimes even real leather!) The punk wearing these will always feel lucky.</Apparello_Lederhose.description>
  <Apparello_square.label>checkered trousers</Apparello_square.label>
  <Apparello_square.description>Checkered and ready to go!.</Apparello_square.description>
  <Apparello_Syndicatellorare.label>wanderer's chestplate</Apparello_Syndicatellorare.label>
  <Apparello_Syndicatellorare.description>Lone wanderers would wear something like this while on their noble crusade or vendetta.</Apparello_Syndicatellorare.description>
  <Apparello_Scytherframe.label>prototype scyther frame</Apparello_Scytherframe.label>
  <Apparello_Scytherframe.description>Mobility enhancing wireframe based on inner workings of a mechanoid 'scyther' unit. Warning! Due to awkward adaptation to human bodystructure long usage may cause major muscle strains.
Wearer may be rendered susceptible to unwanted side-effects. Including but not limited to: Complete loss of motor functions, Motion sickness, and nose bleed.</Apparello_Scytherframe.description>
  <Apparello_HiveArmor.label>prototype hive armor</Apparello_HiveArmor.label>
  <Apparello_HiveArmor.description>Fashioned after the centipede bodystructure. This extremely bulky armor is nigh indestructable. The Sheer weight of this piece of armor drastically hinders mobility</Apparello_HiveArmor.description>
  <Apparello_Steamhull.label>prototype steamhull</Apparello_Steamhull.label>
  <Apparello_Steamhull.description>Combination of mobility enhancing components of the Scyther frame and heavy plating of the Hive armor.
The increased energy consumption from the added scyther frame servos, have forced the shock dampeners work on lesser capacity,
thus rendering the wearer more vulnerable to injuries but the higher mobility under combat situations are well worth it. Generates absurd amounts of heat though.</Apparello_Steamhull.description>
  <Apparello_GShellII.label>medic's powered armor</Apparello_GShellII.label>
  <Apparello_GShellII.description>Powered medium armor, designed for combat medics. Comes with attached GlitOrion© hip'n'hop™ thrusters and StimulantPak™ for faster mobility and treating wounds</Apparello_GShellII.description>
  <Apparello_Syndicatetello.label>shielded coat</Apparello_Syndicatetello.label>
  <Apparello_Syndicatetello.description>A long coat with bullet resistant alloy breastplate, fitted with personal shield. Modern technology full of grit</Apparello_Syndicatetello.description>
  <Apparello_Medicade.label>joywirer's brocade</Apparello_Medicade.label>
  <Apparello_Medicade.description>All the joywire artists wearing these know how to talk to their clients or at the very least, give the impression that they'd know what the heck they are doing.</Apparello_Medicade.description>
  <Apparello_Mogo.label>tunica el mógo</Apparello_Mogo.label>
  <Apparello_Mogo.description>Ritual vestments of the ancient, now extinct tribe - Chéw ón Tuna Sámmich - 
El Mógo for short. The El Mógoan Muffalo Prophets' prophecied of a day when three meteors, bearing sleeping gods would descent from the skies. Common belief was that the gods would build a lift to the spirit realms.
These vestments were created in the intent of binding the soul of slain gods to the wearer and thus gaining passage on the lift.</Apparello_Mogo.description>
  <Apparello_Tunic.label>tunic</Apparello_Tunic.label>
  <Apparello_Tunic.description>Very sleek and skillfully crafted suit capable of protecting the wearer from formidable threats.</Apparello_Tunic.description>
  <Apparello_Tribalpad.description>Ceremonial shoulderguard</Apparello_Tribalpad.description>
  <Apparello_Tribalpad.label>tribal shoulderpads</Apparello_Tribalpad.label>
  <Apparello_Tribalshield.description>Shield made of planks and padding. Used by native tribes in hopes to deflect bullets and to summon the courage of the great 'Shiled-Sheild Téh Gaurdian' A Godly protector of the tribes.</Apparello_Tribalshield.description>
  <Apparello_Tribalshield.label>tribal shield</Apparello_Tribalshield.label>
  <ApparelloTinkerer.label>Tinkering bench</ApparelloTinkerer.label>
  <ApparelloTinkerer.description>A workbench with a set of tools for tinkering. Can work without electricity at 40% of normal speed.</ApparelloTinkerer.description>
  <ApparelloSchematics.label>Schematic cabinet</ApparelloSchematics.label>
  <ApparelloSchematics.description>Can be connected to HiTech research bench and Tinkering bench. Increases research and work speed. This cabinet contains schematics and patterns. Each scribbled full of drafts for gear that couldn't possibly even work.. or could they? Atleast they're a source of inspiration.</ApparelloSchematics.description>
  <Apparello_Doom.label>UAC marine helmet</Apparello_Doom.label>
  <Apparello_Doom.description>The B4D-455 class infantry helmet used by the Union Aerospace Corporation marines during the incident at the Mars science facility. The production of these were since discontinued. A real relic of distant past.</Apparello_Doom.description>
  <Apparello_Quotee.label>war-engineer's comm-link</Apparello_Quotee.label>
  <Apparello_Quotee.description>Often referred to as redcaps. The war-engineers were in charge of keeping the supply lines up and running.
There's stories of one heroic Forward scout war-engineer crashlanding on a tunnelworld during a war in the local star system.
Said engineer eventually escaped the planet after somehow managing to activate a nuclear device in the planet's core, which left the planet uninhabitable.

It is not known whether his tale of the Tunnelworld being under dictatorship of a powerhungry scientist was true or not.
The ramblings about speedrunning through hell with his girlfriend on tow was big blow on his credibility.

Only confirmed truth in whole story is that the tunnelworld did indeed blow up!</Apparello_Quotee.description>
  <Apparel_Psymask.label>psy co. gasmask™</Apparel_Psymask.label>
  <Apparel_Psymask.description>The Psy company's gasmask™ has to be their most profiting product of all times.
It's built in vision sensor technology allowed the wearer to operate in thickest of toxic clouds and more importantly, survive.</Apparel_Psymask.description>
  <Apparello_Zorro.label>wanderer's hat and mask</Apparello_Zorro.label>
  <Apparello_Zorro.description>This apparel is fashioned after the famed hat used by the legendary vigilante El Fox - 'En garde, noble foe! You cannot avoid justice- The vigilante justice!'</Apparello_Zorro.description>
  <Apparello_Footy.label>clan marked balaclava</Apparello_Footy.label>
  <Apparello_Footy.description>Without proper methods of finding out, You'll be forever uncertain whether this balaclava is the real deal or not. The marking on the forehead strongly suggests it indeed is a remnant of the ancient clan of pugilists</Apparello_Footy.description>
  <Apparello_Meffect.label>fancy enviro-headgear</Apparello_Meffect.label>
  <Apparello_Meffect.description>Warm and cozy and most importantly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffect.description>
  <Apparello_Meffectwo.label>enviro-headgear</Apparello_Meffectwo.label>
  <Apparello_Meffectwo.description>Mostly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffectwo.description>
  <Apparello_Kurt.label>aerocowl MkII</Apparello_Kurt.label>
  <Apparello_Kurt.description>The ingenious aerodynamic miracle by Kurtech. It's not really a cowl anymore but at this point it's too late to rename it.</Apparello_Kurt.description>
  <Apparello_Kurtlite.label>aerocowl</Apparello_Kurtlite.label>
  <Apparello_Kurtlite.description>The ingenious aerodynamic miracle by Kurtech.</Apparello_Kurtlite.description>
  <Apparello_Rockman.label>Shuttle pilot helm</Apparello_Rockman.label>
  <Apparello_Rockman.description>All the famous shuttle pilots wore one of these, some were more adorned than others. This is one of the more practical and basic ones.</Apparello_Rockman.description>
  <Apparello_Raideroos.label>outlanders scrap mask</Apparello_Raideroos.label>
  <Apparello_Raideroos.description>Something pulled seemingly straight out of junkyard. It has it's own kind of charm to it</Apparello_Raideroos.description>
  <Apparello_Yi.label>infiltrator headgear</Apparello_Yi.label>
  <Apparello_Yi.description>Equipped with very intricate target tracking system and pathing analyzer. The headgear was very popular among assassins and spies of all kinds. It's a real shame the type of batteries used in this haven't been manufactured in decades. However! someone has rigged this thing up to power from kinetic dynamo</Apparello_Yi.description>
  <Apparello_Raz.label>joywirer's Cap</Apparello_Raz.label>
  <Apparello_Raz.description>Hardened leather and snazzy goggles. it's almost as if you could pilot your way through someone's psyche with this cap equipped!</Apparello_Raz.description>
  <Apparello_Goggles.label>science goggles</Apparello_Goggles.label>
  <Apparello_Goggles.description>Due to intense radiation these goggles have been subjected to, they cause temporary and sudden baldness.</Apparello_Goggles.description>
  <Apparello_Visoor.label>shuttlepilot's Visor</Apparello_Visoor.label>
  <Apparello_Visoor.description>Shuttlepilot's visors. used to fulfill your usual piloting needs like calling in "houston; mayday mayday - landing struts are jammed, I repeat landing struts are jammed. Copy? Roger Wilco. Starfox one out."</Apparello_Visoor.description>
  <Apparello_Shadess.label>sunshades</Apparello_Shadess.label>
  <Apparello_Shadess.description>Sunshades. Most favoured protection from the sun. Wearer never gets caught with the excuse 'sun was shining in my eye'</Apparello_Shadess.description>
  <Apparello_Piloggle.label>aviator Sunglasses</Apparello_Piloggle.label>
  <Apparello_Piloggle.description>Authentic Rim-Ban™ quality. Cover your eyes with awesome!</Apparello_Piloggle.description>
  <Apparello_Brimsk.label>archNem© Ski™ goggles</Apparello_Brimsk.label>
  <Apparello_Brimsk.description>Military grade skiing goggles, slightly stylized design. Known for it's heavy impact resistance</Apparello_Brimsk.description>
  <Apparello_Mojo.label>modest tribal Mask</Apparello_Mojo.label>
  <Apparello_Mojo.description>Basic tribal mask, for that wooden impression.</Apparello_Mojo.description>
  <Apparello_Mojotwo.label>gaudy tribal Mask</Apparello_Mojotwo.label>
  <Apparello_Mojotwo.description>Makes you look ever so slightly more sociable.</Apparello_Mojotwo.description>
  <Apparello_MojoFeather.label>tribal headdress</Apparello_MojoFeather.label>
  <Apparello_MojoFeather.description>Tribal headdress or a foot bottom torturing device. It's very feathery</Apparello_MojoFeather.description>
  <Apparello_Wendywelder.label>welding mask</Apparello_Wendywelder.label>
  <Apparello_Wendywelder.description>A little spark in they eye is said to be a good thing. Still, being prepared never harmed anyone.</Apparello_Wendywelder.description>
  <Apparello_Hardhat.label>hardhat</Apparello_Hardhat.label>
  <Apparello_Hardhat.description>Favoured by the constructions workers all across the galaxy. These are known to have saved lives of many a prey of the terrifying falling lunchbox, hammer or brick</Apparello_Hardhat.description>
  <Apparello_Chefhat.label>chef's hat</Apparello_Chefhat.label>
  <Apparello_Chefhat.description>These iconic chef hats do serve an actual purpose - Keeping the hair in check. Finding hair in your soup often means dissatisfied customer.</Apparello_Chefhat.description>
  <Apparello_Chefhatplus.label>tinkercraft chefhat</Apparello_Chefhatplus.label>
  <Apparello_Chefhatplus.description>Armed with timers and very basic scent-detector helps anyone cook the meals just right. The chef hat on it is just for declaring the purpose of this headgear</Apparello_Chefhatplus.description>
  <Apparello_Cyninja.label>tac-team headcover</Apparello_Cyninja.label>
  <Apparello_Cyninja.description>Designed to be used by tactical squads in urban warfare situations. comes with pre-installed velocity booster and inbuilt aiming assist. It does expose the wearer's brain to minimal and totally acceptable levels of radioactivity, which is okay!</Apparello_Cyninja.description>
  <Apparello_Medihelmet.label>medic's kevlar helmet</Apparello_Medihelmet.label>
  <Apparello_Medihelmet.description>A lightweight combat helmet with a complex design, reinforced with plasteel. Not effective against blunt weapons.</Apparello_Medihelmet.description>
  <Apparello_Proto.label>prototype nerve-enhancer</Apparello_Proto.label>
  <Apparello_Proto.description>Prototype of very innovative headgear aimed to enhance synaptic reaction rates. It has some very unsavory side effects such as overbearing nervousness, Ringing ears, strange background noises and/or voices.</Apparello_Proto.description>
  <Apparello_ProtoFin.label>nerve-enhancer</Apparello_ProtoFin.label>
  <Apparello_ProtoFin.description>Very innovative headgear aimed to enhance synaptic reaction rates. It still has some very unsavory side effects although not as bad as before. placing the advanced AI core on it seemed to work out most of the kinks. Unfortunately the AI core also amplifies wearer psychic sensitivity, leaving them extremely vulnerable to psychic powers</Apparello_ProtoFin.description>
  <Apparello_Commissar.label>peaked cap</Apparello_Commissar.label>
  <Apparello_Commissar.description>Often seen on military officers. These indigenous alpha mammals of the battlefields tend to be so amazing their skills rubs off on their clothes</Apparello_Commissar.description>
  <Apparello_Gassy.label>gasmask</Apparello_Gassy.label>
  <Apparello_Gassy.description>Unwieldy and cumbersome protection from gas attacks, Not in common use anymore due to better more advanced alternatives. However, still favoured by the raiders for it's intimidating look</Apparello_Gassy.description>
  <Apparello_Cybissar.label>Tac-Team peaked cap</Apparello_Cybissar.label>
  <Apparello_Cybissar.description>it's just a Tac-Team mask with peaked cap attached. It's very neat.</Apparello_Cybissar.description>
  <Apparello_Medband.label>medic's bandana</Apparello_Medband.label>
  <Apparello_Medband.description>Medic's bandana. Used to point out people who shouldn't be shot at from the crowd. Such rules are hardly ever followed on the Rimworlds.</Apparello_Medband.description>
  <Apparello_Docteur.label>surgeon's headgear</Apparello_Docteur.label>
  <Apparello_Docteur.description>When fiddling with someone else's vital organs, sanitary equipment is crucial. Wearing these enhances the doctor's sight with the amplifier modules on the goggles. And the surgical mask prevents unwanted bacteria entering the vic.. patient</Apparello_Docteur.description>
  <Apparello_Plainhat.label>cork hat</Apparello_Plainhat.label>
  <Apparello_Plainhat.description>Weighted hats for the hardy men who worked the desert plains where winds were strong enough to blow mans hat off, The sun so strong it would fell an ox. But not the Plainsmen, no! They'd work dusk till dawn ..or atleast till supper.</Apparello_Plainhat.description>
  <Apparello_Furhat.label>ushanka</Apparello_Furhat.label>
  <Apparello_Furhat.description>Keep your head warm in cold climates, wear fur! Be warned though, in the right place, the fur wears you!</Apparello_Furhat.description>
  <Apparello_Bandit.label>bandit scarf</Apparello_Bandit.label>
  <Apparello_Bandit.description>Robbing a stagecoach has never been as much fun without wearing a scarf on your face. Scarves provide small resistance against toxic fallout.</Apparello_Bandit.description>
  <Apparello_Cardshark.label>cardshark hat</Apparello_Cardshark.label>
  <Apparello_Cardshark.description>Stylish, elegant and soft to the touch. Known as the most important part of western attire. Especially amongst the card cheats and otherwise slippery individuals</Apparello_Cardshark.description>
  <Apparello_TriMeCornMatey.label>Tricorn</Apparello_TriMeCornMatey.label>
  <Apparello_TriMeCornMatey.description>The wide brim of this hat is cocked up at three points thus the triangular shape. The points of the hat are believed to represent power, wisdom and courage. This information Zeldom comes up even though it is Linked to many a triangular objects, no one questions it's validity and is widely accepted as Ganon.</Apparello_TriMeCornMatey.description>
  <Apparello_Sandtrader.label>caravaneer's hat</Apparello_Sandtrader.label>
  <Apparello_Sandtrader.description>Roaming merchants use these to protect their face from dust storms, toxic fallouts and the like.</Apparello_Sandtrader.description>
  <Apparello_Tradecone.label>paddy hat</Apparello_Tradecone.label>
  <Apparello_Tradecone.description>Traveling merchants and rice paddy farmers would often protect themselves from the sun with hats like these. It has very oriental feel to it.</Apparello_Tradecone.description>
  <Apparello_Fedora.label>fedora</Apparello_Fedora.label>
  <Apparello_Fedora.description>These hats are often associated with gangsters and government officials, which are both practically the same. "Will m'lady join the colony. Nyaah?"</Apparello_Fedora.description>
  <Apparello_Headset.label>headset with bandana</Apparello_Headset.label>
  <Apparello_Headset.description>Common usage for these has been communication. it's wireless and doesn't work. But it gives the impression that you're somehow more social and capable at things that require social skills.</Apparello_Headset.description>
  <Apparello_Beret.label>beret</Apparello_Beret.label>
  <Apparello_Beret.description>Soft and keeps the head warm. Very common amongst both offduty soldiers and high ranking officers. Uniforms commonly inspire respect but also creates a very stern image of the wearer</Apparello_Beret.description>
  <Apparello_Tophat.label>tophat</Apparello_Tophat.label>
  <Apparello_Tophat.description>Rare sight on the rimworlds, Tophats make the wearer feel the power over the lesser beings</Apparello_Tophat.description>
  <Apparello_Bandal.label>baseball cap</Apparello_Bandal.label>
  <Apparello_Bandal.description>Your common cap. Perhaps most famed from the ages old game where you hit balls with your bat and then run home. This was a very violent game and entirely based on dirty hit and run tactics. Thankfully it is not practiced any longer at this day and age.</Apparello_Bandal.description>
  <Apparello_Vandal.label>scarf</Apparello_Vandal.label>
  <Apparello_Vandal.description>Urbworld crims would often don these on while robbing the local corner store. These kind of criminals are famous for their itchy trigger fingers, poor aim, brick throwing and trashcan kicking shenanigans. Scarves provide small resistance against toxic fallout.</Apparello_Vandal.description>
  <Apparello_Lecap.label>kepi</Apparello_Lecap.label>
  <Apparello_Lecap.description>The most important piece of many a rebel army uniform. Designed to be worn on hot climates.</Apparello_Lecap.description>
  <Apparello_Hoood.label>hood</Apparello_Hoood.label>
  <Apparello_Hoood.description>Ultimate protection from the wind! The kind of headwear you see worn by shady characters in dark alleys, glaring at you, with gleaming eyes, Ready to stab yo- *gurgle*</Apparello_Hoood.description>
  <Apparello_Sombrero.label>sombrero</Apparello_Sombrero.label>
  <Apparello_Sombrero.description>Keeps the sun off your eyes during siesta! Ay caramba!</Apparello_Sombrero.description>
  <Apparello_Moron.label>explorer's morion</Apparello_Moron.label>
  <Apparello_Moron.description>17th century morion. Extremely common in medieval worlds. However finding these usually means it's remnants of the Spacefaring lockpick expedition (Named such for their mark: a lock with two razors or wings painted on their morions)
The Lockpick expedition was one of the largest expedition teams in known history. Their last destination were reported being 'the transcended space'. Their fate is unknown and they've not been heard of or seen since.
Their fairly pristine condition equipment are still found floating around the far corners of space.</Apparello_Moron.description>
</LanguageData>