<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VCE_RawApple.label>apples</VCE_RawApple.label>
  <VCE_RawApple.description>Glossy, red apples. Apples have been used as snacking food, a dessert ingredient, and brewed into cider since early mankind.</VCE_RawApple.description>
  <VCE_RawPeach.label>peaches</VCE_RawPeach.label>
  <VCE_RawPeach.description>An edible juicy fruit called peach or nectarine. A ripe peach will have a fragrant aroma and be delicious eaten fresh out of hand.</VCE_RawPeach.description>
  <VCE_RawCherry.label>cherries</VCE_RawCherry.label>
  <VCE_RawCherry.description>Tiny purple-red sweet cherries. Cherries are notable for requiring a brief freezing season, as such they quickly became a favorite among northern occidental cultures.</VCE_RawCherry.description>
  <VCE_RawPlum.label>plums</VCE_RawPlum.label>
  <VCE_RawPlum.description>A smooth-skinned purple fruit. Many cultures dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation. Instead of rotting, once the 15 days have passed the plums will dry into prunes, which are considered preserved food.</VCE_RawPlum.description>
  <VCE_RawPrunes.label>prunes</VCE_RawPrunes.label>
  <VCE_RawPrunes.description>Dried plums. Prunes take a very long time to deteriorate.</VCE_RawPrunes.description>
  <VCE_RawPear.label>pears</VCE_RawPear.label>
  <VCE_RawPear.description>Crispy green pears. While at first similar to apples, pears are slightly more fibrous and less sweet.</VCE_RawPear.description>
  <VCE_RawPricklyPear.label>prickly pears</VCE_RawPricklyPear.label>
  <VCE_RawPricklyPear.description>Pink, melon-like edible fruits, used historically for both snacking as well as medicine by desert natives.</VCE_RawPricklyPear.description>
  <VCE_Bearberry.label>bearberries</VCE_Bearberry.label>
  <VCE_Bearberry.description>These are small, pink berries known as bearberries. While raw bearberries possess an acidic and bland taste, after cooking a natural sweetness comes through and the results can be much more palatable.</VCE_Bearberry.description>
  <VCE_RawBanana.label>bananas</VCE_RawBanana.label>
  <VCE_RawBanana.description>Yellow, elongated berries, easily peeled to reveal a deeply sweet, nearly mushy flesh inside. They have been a favorite of both humans and other primates across the tropics for millenia.</VCE_RawBanana.description>
  <VCE_RawOrange.label>oranges</VCE_RawOrange.label>
  <VCE_RawOrange.description>Spherical and perforated, oranges are notoriously annoying to peel and quite pulpy, but known as one of the absolute juiciest fruits with a bright tang and sour aftertaste.</VCE_RawOrange.description>
  <VCE_RawOnion.label>onions</VCE_RawOnion.label>
  <VCE_RawOnion.description>An edible bulb of pungent, savory taste and smell with almost as many varieties as cooking applications.</VCE_RawOnion.description>
  <VCE_RawPumpkin.label>pumpkins</VCE_RawPumpkin.label>
  <VCE_RawPumpkin.description>Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest.</VCE_RawPumpkin.description>
  <VCE_RawPepper.label>peppers</VCE_RawPepper.label>
  <VCE_RawPepper.description>Tiny, spicy, crimson pods often used in sauces, relishes, or powders. While the flavor itself is mild the capsaicin contained inside means humans find them oddly addicting, if painful when consumed in mass. Animals are known to avoid eating the plant entirely.</VCE_RawPepper.description>
  <VCE_RawPeas.label>peas</VCE_RawPeas.label>
  <VCE_RawPeas.description>Spherical green seeds tucked safely away in a fleshy pod. Peas are notable for having potentially long shelf-lives when dried properly.</VCE_RawPeas.description>
  <VCE_RawEggplant.label>eggplants</VCE_RawEggplant.label>
  <VCE_RawEggplant.description>A bulbous purple fruit of the nightshade family. Eggplant is rarely served as a side, generally filling the role of the main component of the dish.</VCE_RawEggplant.description>
  <VCE_RawCabbage.label>cabbages</VCE_RawCabbage.label>
  <VCE_RawCabbage.description>A somewhat hardy, leafy green vegetable, often chopped and then fermented or stewed.</VCE_RawCabbage.description>
  <VCE_RawBeets.label>beets</VCE_RawBeets.label>
  <VCE_RawBeets.description>An herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike, notably nutritious and historically used in dye making.</VCE_RawBeets.description>
  <VCE_RawTomatoes.label>tomatoes</VCE_RawTomatoes.label>
  <VCE_RawTomatoes.description>A series of juicy, glossy red fruits attached by vine, used commonly as a vegetable. Strong stewing releases natural sugars and mellows out acids contained within.</VCE_RawTomatoes.description>
  <VCE_Grass.label>Grass</VCE_Grass.label>
  <VCE_Grass.description>Cultivated grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground.</VCE_Grass.description>
  <VCE_TallGrass.label>tall grass</VCE_TallGrass.label>
  <VCE_TallGrass.description>Cultivated tall grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground. Slows down anyone moving over it.</VCE_TallGrass.description>
  <VCE_Agave.label>agave</VCE_Agave.label>
  <VCE_Agave.description>A large-leafed desert plant with edible flowers and stalks.</VCE_Agave.description>
  <VCE_Onion.label>onion plant</VCE_Onion.label>
  <VCE_Onion.description>An edible bulb of pungent, savory taste and smell with almost as many varieties as cooking applications. Cannot suffer the effects of blight.</VCE_Onion.description>
  <VCE_Pumpkin.label>pumpkin plant</VCE_Pumpkin.label>
  <VCE_Pumpkin.description>Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest. However, their durability means added weight and mass - Too cumbersome for hydroponics basins.</VCE_Pumpkin.description>
  <VCE_Pepper.label>pepper plant</VCE_Pepper.label>
  <VCE_Pepper.description>Tiny, spicy, crimson pods often used in sauces, relishes, or powders. While the flavor itself is mild the capsaicin contained inside means humans find them oddly addicting, if painful when consumed in mass. Animals are known to avoid eating them entirely.</VCE_Pepper.description>
  <VCE_Peas.label>pea plant</VCE_Peas.label>
  <VCE_Peas.description>Spherical green seeds tucked safely away in a fleshy pod. Pea plants are known to be quite thirsty, and will benefit greatly from rainfall. Peas are also notable for having potentially long shelf-lives when dried properly.</VCE_Peas.description>
  <VCE_Eggplant.label>eggplant</VCE_Eggplant.label>
  <VCE_Eggplant.description>A bulbous purple fruit of the nightshade family. Eggplant is rarely served as a side, generally filling the role of the main component of the dish. Flourishes in warm weather.</VCE_Eggplant.description>
  <VCE_Cabbage.label>cabbage plant</VCE_Cabbage.label>
  <VCE_Cabbage.description>A somewhat hardy, leafy green vegetable, often chopped and then fermented or stewed. This particular strain seems highly resistant to airborne toxin and radiation.</VCE_Cabbage.description>
  <VCE_Beet.label>beet plant</VCE_Beet.label>
  <VCE_Beet.description>An herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike, notably nutritious and historically used in dye making. While beets do require rich soil they are quite hearty, and will continue to grow very slowly through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VCE_Beet.description>
  <VCE_Tomato.label>tomato plant</VCE_Tomato.label>
  <VCE_Tomato.description>A series of juicy, glossy red fruits attached by vine, used commonly as a vegetable. Strong stewing releases natural sugars and mellows out acids contained within. Tomatoes are easily removed from the vine without having to uproot the plant.</VCE_Tomato.description>
  <VCE_AppleTree.label>apple tree</VCE_AppleTree.label>
  <VCE_AppleTree.description>A tree bearing glossy, red apples, while a myriad of different varieties exist this particular type favors warm summers and mild winters. Apples have been used as snacking food, a dessert ingredient, and brewed into cider since early mankind.</VCE_AppleTree.description>
  <VCE_PeachTree.label>peach tree</VCE_PeachTree.label>
  <VCE_PeachTree.description>A deciduous tree bearing fuzzy, stone fruit known as peaches, peach trees often require full sunlight and warm temperatures. Ancient oriental cultures cultivated these trees groves at a time, noting its ability to survive in drought conditions.</VCE_PeachTree.description>
  <VCE_CherryTree.label>cherry tree</VCE_CherryTree.label>
  <VCE_CherryTree.description>A tree bearing tiny purple-red sweet cherries. Cherry trees are notable for requiring a brief freezing season, as such their fruit quickly became a favorite among northern occidental civilizations. This particular genus is quite beautiful, speckled with pink blossoms throughout, blooming fully each winter.</VCE_CherryTree.description>
  <VCE_PlumTree.label>plum tree</VCE_PlumTree.label>
  <VCE_PlumTree.description>A bushy tree bearing a smooth-skinned purple fruit. Plums are particularly tart and produced into a variety of jams, jellies, and ciders. Many cultures also dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation.</VCE_PlumTree.description>
  <VCE_PearTree.label>pear tree</VCE_PearTree.label>
  <VCE_PearTree.description>A stout tree bearing crispy green pears, pear trees are notable for requiring high amounts of water and cool weather, and also doing quite well in shade. While at first similar to apples, pears are slightly more fibrous and less sweet.</VCE_PearTree.description>
  <VCE_Opuntia.label>opuntia</VCE_Opuntia.label>
  <VCE_Opuntia.description>More often referred to as the “prickly pear” cactus, this plant is known to be quite bountiful even in hot, dry deserts. The pads of this tall, spiny cactus bloom pink, melon-like edible fruits, used historically for both snacking as well as medicine by desert natives.</VCE_Opuntia.description>
  <VCE_BearBerryBush.label>bearberry bush</VCE_BearBerryBush.label>
  <VCE_BearBerryBush.description>A low-lying bush speckled with pink berries that thrives in poor, even sandy soil. While raw bearberries possess an acidic and bland taste, after cooking a natural sweetness comes through and the results can be much more palatable. This plant can be grown in pots.</VCE_BearBerryBush.description>
  <VCE_BananaTree.label>banana tree</VCE_BananaTree.label>
  <VCE_BananaTree.description>A broad-leafed, tall tropical tree adorned with a cluster of yellow, elongated berries succinctly known as bananas. Bananas are easily peeled to reveal a deeply sweet, nearly mushy flesh inside and have been a favorite of both humans and other primates across the tropics for millenia. Bananas are easy to harvest, since a whole "hand" can be cut at the same time.</VCE_BananaTree.description>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.label>orange tree</VCE_OrangeTree.label>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.description>A bushy, semi-tropical tree dotted with orange fruits well equipped for growing in humid environments and in wet soil. Spherical and perforated, oranges are notoriously annoying to peel and quite pulpy, but known as one of the absolute juiciest fruits with a bright tang and sour aftertaste.</VCE_OrangeTree.description>
  <VCE_Beet.label.label>chioggia beet plant</VCE_Beet.label.label>
  <VCE_Beet.description.description>An herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike. Though these look like ordinary beets from the outside, on the inside they have distinct red-and-white-striped flesh. These are highest on the sweetness scale. While beets do require rich soil they are quite hearty, and will continue to grow very slowly through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VCE_Beet.description.description>
  <VCE_RawBeets.label.label>chioggia beets</VCE_RawBeets.label.label>
  <VCE_RawBeets.description.description>An herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike. Though these look like ordinary beets from the outside, on the inside they have distinct red-and-white-striped flesh. These are highest on the sweetness scale.</VCE_RawBeets.description.description>
  <RC2_PlantEggPlant.label.label>fairy tale eggplant</RC2_PlantEggPlant.label.label>
  <RC2_PlantEggPlant.description.description>These spongy fruits are technically berries - but, use them like a berry, and you'll have a bad time. Instead, they're used similarly to vegetables. Grown in temperate and tropical climates. The tiny fairy tale variety has purple and white stripes and is no bigger than the palm of your hand. They can be prepared in the same way as larger eggplants, but take especially well to grilling since they’re so tender.</RC2_PlantEggPlant.description.description>
  <RC2_RawEggplants.label.label>fairy tale eggplants</RC2_RawEggplants.label.label>
  <RC2_RawEggplants.description.description>Raw fairy tale eggplants. Used in a variety of dishes. Technically they're a fruit, but culinarily they're used as a vegetable.</RC2_RawEggplants.description.description>
  <VCE_Cabbage.label.label>cauliflower plant</VCE_Cabbage.label.label>
  <VCE_Cabbage.description.description>A large round vegetable that has a hard white centre surrounded by green leaves, naturally high in fiber and B-vitamins. This particular strain seems highly resistant to airborne toxins and radiation.</VCE_Cabbage.description.description>
  <VCE_RawCabbage.label.label>cauliflowers</VCE_RawCabbage.label.label>
  <VCE_RawCabbage.description.description>A large round vegetable that has a hard white centre surrounded by green leaves, naturally high in fiber and B-vitamins.</VCE_RawCabbage.description.description>
  <VCE_Onion.label.label>white onion plant</VCE_Onion.label.label>
  <VCE_Onion.description.description>A strong and pungent variety of onions, perfect for flavourful salads or for general cooking applications when strong flavours are desired. Cannot suffer the effects of blight.</VCE_Onion.description.description>
  <VCE_RawOnion.label.label>white onions</VCE_RawOnion.label.label>
  <VCE_RawOnion.description.description>A strong and pungent variety of onions, perfect for flavourful salads or for general cooking applications when strong flavours are desired.</VCE_RawOnion.description.description>
  <VCE_Pumpkin.label.label>mammoth gold pumpkin plant</VCE_Pumpkin.label.label>
  <VCE_Pumpkin.description.description>One of the biggest varieties of pumpkin, the mammoth gold can grow to between 25 and 50 Kg of weight. Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest. However, their durability means added weight and mass - Too cumbersome for hydroponics basins.</VCE_Pumpkin.description.description>
  <VCE_RawPumpkin.label.label>mammoth gold pumpkins</VCE_RawPumpkin.label.label>
  <VCE_RawPumpkin.description.description>One of the biggest varieties of pumpkin, the mammoth gold can grow to between 25 and 50 Kg of weight. Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest.</VCE_RawPumpkin.description.description>
  <VCE_Tomato.label.label>red beefsteak tomato plant</VCE_Tomato.label.label>
  <VCE_Tomato.description.description>A variety of tomatoes with a firm, meaty, rich, vibrant red colour. Its flavour is mild, juicy and balanced compared to other varieties. Tomatoes are easily removed from the vine without having to uproot the plant.</VCE_Tomato.description.description>
  <VCE_RawTomatoes.label.label>red beefsteak tomatoes</VCE_RawTomatoes.label.label>
  <VCE_RawTomatoes.description.description>A variety of tomatoes with a firm, meaty, rich, vibrant red colour. Its flavour is mild, juicy and balanced compared to other varieties.</VCE_RawTomatoes.description.description>
  <VCE_AppleTree.label.label>granny smith apple tree</VCE_AppleTree.label.label>
  <VCE_AppleTree.description.description>A tree bearing hard apples, with a light green skin and crisp, juicy flesh. The flavour is tart and acidic. It remains firm when baked, making it a very popular cooking apple used in pies, where it can be sweetened.</VCE_AppleTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawApple.label.label>granny smith apples</VCE_RawApple.label.label>
  <VCE_RawApple.description.description>Hard apples, with a light green skin and crisp, juicy flesh. The flavour is tart and acidic. It remains firm when baked, making it a very popular cooking apple used in pies, where it can be sweetened.</VCE_RawApple.description.description>
  <VCE_CherryTree.label.label>sakura tree</VCE_CherryTree.label.label>
  <VCE_CherryTree.description.description>Also known as the cherry blossom, Sakura trees produce small fruits known as sakuranbo, small cherries that do not have much flesh beyond the seed within. Due to their bitter taste, sakuranbo are not traditionally eaten raw, but these trees have been genetically modified to produce sweeter tasting fruits. This particular genus is quite beautiful, speckled with pink blossoms throughout, blooming fully each winter.</VCE_CherryTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawCherry.label.label>sakuranbo</VCE_RawCherry.label.label>
  <VCE_RawCherry.description.description>Small cherries that do not have much flesh beyond the seed within. Due to their bitter taste, sakuranbo are not traditionally eaten raw, but these fruits have been genetically modified to have a sweeter taste.</VCE_RawCherry.description.description>
  <VCE_PeachTree.label.label>apricot tree</VCE_PeachTree.label.label>
  <VCE_PeachTree.description.description>The apricot is a fruit that resembles the peach but much smaller, pale yellow or orange with some red shades. It is mainly consumed fresh, although it is also used to make some by-products like stewed fruit, jams, juices and dried apricots. Apricots have a high concentration of vitamin C. This variety of apricot tree is quite hardy, and they can be planted in stony soil.</VCE_PeachTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawPeach.label.label>apricots</VCE_RawPeach.label.label>
  <VCE_RawPeach.description.description>A fruit that resembles the peach but much smaller, pale yellow or orange with some red shades. It is mainly consumed fresh, although it is also used to make some by-products like stewed fruit, jams, juices and dried apricots. Apricots have a high concentration of vitamin C.</VCE_RawPeach.description.description>
  <VCE_PlumTree.label.label>damson plum tree</VCE_PlumTree.label.label>
  <VCE_PlumTree.description.description>The Damson plum tree, also archaically called the "damascene", is a bushy tree bearing a relatively small ovoid fruit with a distinctive, somewhat astringent taste, widely used for culinary purposes, particularly in fruit preserves and jams. Many cultures also dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation.</VCE_PlumTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawPlum.label.label>damson plums</VCE_RawPlum.label.label>
  <VCE_RawPlum.description.description>A relatively small ovoid fruit with a distinctive, somewhat astringent taste, widely used for culinary purposes, particularly in fruit preserves and jams. Many cultures also dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation.</VCE_RawPlum.description.description>
  <VCE_BananaTree.label.label>gros michel banana tree</VCE_BananaTree.label.label>
  <VCE_BananaTree.description.description>A tall tropical tree adorned with a cluster of yellow, elongated berries. These trees have been genetically modified to resist the fungal infections that nearly caused their extinction in old Terra. The Gros Michel variety has a distinct taste, different from that of Cavendish variety bananas. Bananas are easy to harvest, since a whole "hand" can be cut at the same time.</VCE_BananaTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawBanana.label.label>gros michel bananas</VCE_RawBanana.label.label>
  <VCE_RawBanana.description.description>Yellow, elongated berries. These bananas have been genetically modified to resist the fungal infections that nearly caused their extinction in old Terra. The Gros Michel variety has a distinct taste, different from that of Cavendish variety bananas.</VCE_RawBanana.description.description>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.label.label>mandarin tree</VCE_OrangeTree.label.label>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.description.description>A small citrus tree with fruit resembling miniature oranges, usually eaten plain or in fruit salads. Mandarins are smaller and oblate, rather than spherical, like the common oranges (which are a mandarin hybrid). The taste is considered less sour, as well as sweeter and stronger. Mandarin trees are well equipped for growing in humid environments and in wet soil.</VCE_OrangeTree.description.description>
  <VCE_RawOrange.label.label>mandarins</VCE_RawOrange.label.label>
  <VCE_RawOrange.description.description>A small citrus tree with fruit resembling miniature oranges, usually eaten plain or in fruit salads. Mandarins are smaller and oblate, rather than spherical, like the common oranges (which are a mandarin hybrid). The taste is considered less sour, as well as sweeter and stronger.</VCE_RawOrange.description.description>
  <VCE_Eggplant.label.label>black beauty aubergine plant</VCE_Eggplant.label.label>
  <VCE_Eggplant.description.description>A bulbous, tender, tasty purplish-black fruit of the nightshade family. Aubergines or eggplants are great in a variety of dishes, and the Black Beauty variety is delicious grilled, baked and stir-fried. Flourishes in warm weather.</VCE_Eggplant.description.description>
  <VCE_RawEggplant.label.label>black beauty aubergines</VCE_RawEggplant.label.label>
  <VCE_RawEggplant.description.description>A bulbous, tender, tasty purplish-black fruit of the nightshade family. Aubergines or eggplants are great in a variety of dishes, and the Black Beauty variety is delicious grilled, baked and stir-fried.</VCE_RawEggplant.description.description>
  <VCE_Grass.label.label>forage grass</VCE_Grass.label.label>
  <VCE_TallGrass.label.label>forage tall grass</VCE_TallGrass.label.label>
  <VCE_Grass.description.description>Cultivated forage grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground.</VCE_Grass.description.description>
  <VCE_TallGrass.description.description>Cultivated forage tall grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground. Slows down anyone moving over it.</VCE_TallGrass.description.description>
</LanguageData>