<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Beggars.label>beggars</Beggars.label>
  <Beggars.pawnSingular>beggar</Beggars.pawnSingular>
  <Beggars.pawnsPlural>beggars</Beggars.pawnsPlural>
  <Beggars.description>A group of beggars seeking charity.</Beggars.description>
  <Beggars.leaderTitle>leader</Beggars.leaderTitle>
  <TribeCannibal.label>cannibal tribe</TribeCannibal.label>
  <TribeCannibal.description>These people have been here a very long time. Maybe their ancestors crashed here a thousand years ago. Maybe they survived some cataclysm that destroyed a technological civilization here. In any case, the tribals are mostly nomadic people who live off the land using primitive tools and weapons.\n\nDespite their apparent technological weakness, the tribals can be dangerous enemies because of their skill with low-tech warfare, their numbers, and their hardiness.\n\nThis particularly vicious tribe believes eating the flesh of their enemies is a great honor.</TribeCannibal.description>
  <NudistTribe.label>nudist tribe</NudistTribe.label>
  <NudistTribe.description>These people have been here a very long time. Maybe their ancestors crashed here a thousand years ago. Maybe they survived some cataclysm that destroyed a technological civilization here. In any case, the tribals are mostly nomadic people who live off the land using primitive tools and weapons.\n\nDespite their apparent technological weakness, the tribals can be dangerous enemies because of their skill with low-tech warfare, their numbers, and their hardiness.\n\nThis particular tribe believes that covering one's body is wrong.</NudistTribe.description>
  <CannibalPirate.label>cannibal pirate gang</CannibalPirate.label>
  <CannibalPirate.description>A loose confederation of pirate groups who've agreed to mostly fight outsiders instead of fighting each other.\n\nPirates don't sow, they don't build, and they rarely trade. Driven by a blood-and-honor culture that values personal strength and ruthlessness, they enrich themselves by raiding and robbing their more productive neighbors.\n\nTheir technology level depends mostly on who they've managed to steal from recently. Mostly they carry gunpowder weapons, though some prefer to stab victims at close range.\n\nThis particular gang of pirates are cannibals.</CannibalPirate.description>
  <Pilgrims.label>pilgrims</Pilgrims.label>
  <Pilgrims.pawnSingular>pilgrim</Pilgrims.pawnSingular>
  <Pilgrims.pawnsPlural>pilgrims</Pilgrims.pawnsPlural>
  <Pilgrims.description>A group of pilgrims seeking to venerate an ancient relic.</Pilgrims.description>
  <Pilgrims.leaderTitle>leader</Pilgrims.leaderTitle>
</LanguageData>