<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <BasicOreProcessing.label>Basic ore processing and smelting</BasicOreProcessing.label>
  <BasicOreProcessing.description>Basic fundamentals of ore processing and production of ingots from them.
Allows smelting of iron and copper ingots in a simple furnace.</BasicOreProcessing.description>
  <AdvancedOreProcessing.label>Advanced ore processing</AdvancedOreProcessing.label>
  <AdvancedOreProcessing.description>The use of an arc furnace will allow the processing of ores such as ilmenite and cobalt and produce more advanced alloys.
Allows you to create an electric arc furnace to produce cobalt, nickel, chromium and palladium.</AdvancedOreProcessing.description>
  <HeavyDutyAlloys.label>Super heavy Alloys</HeavyDutyAlloys.label>
  <HeavyDutyAlloys.description>The study of alloys will create new generation alloys that are many times superior to current ones.
Allows you to create plasteel and titanium.</HeavyDutyAlloys.description>
  <GasIndustry.label>Gas industry</GasIndustry.label>
  <GasIndustry.description>It opens up the possibility of producing gas and processing it in a special gas machine.</GasIndustry.description>
  <ElectricityAndGas.label>Electricity and gas</ElectricityAndGas.label>
  <ElectricityAndGas.description>Use gas energy to generate electricity.
Allows you to create a gas turbine to produce energy from gas.</ElectricityAndGas.description>
  <GasTraspAndStorage.label>Gas transportation and storage</GasTraspAndStorage.label>
  <GasTraspAndStorage.description>Learn how to better transport and store gas.
Allows you to create a large tanker and gas cylinders.</GasTraspAndStorage.description>
  <HydrogenProduction.label>Hydrogen production</HydrogenProduction.label>
  <HydrogenProduction.description>Learn how to produce hydrogen using steam conversion of natural gas.</HydrogenProduction.description>
  <GasToHeat.label>Gas to heat</GasToHeat.label>
  <GasToHeat.description>Create a gas heater that will be more efficient than an electric heater.</GasToHeat.description>
  <ChemicalSynthesis.label>Chemical synthesis</ChemicalSynthesis.label>
  <ChemicalSynthesis.description>Improve the processing system that allows you to use chemical synthesis.</ChemicalSynthesis.description>
  <GasWeapon.label>Gas weapon</GasWeapon.label>
  <GasWeapon.description>The destructive force of combustion of gaseous substances allows them to be used to create protective equipment.</GasWeapon.description>
</LanguageData>