<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AttomachineryWood.label>attowood</AttomachineryWood.label>
  <AttomachineryWood.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of natural oak. It is virtually indistinguishable from wood, apart from the patterns.</AttomachineryWood.description>
  <AttomachineryRedCarpet.label>red attocarpet</AttomachineryRedCarpet.label>
  <AttomachineryRedCarpet.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a rich red carpet. This carpet analogue seems to feel just like red shag carpet. It's perfectly lovable.</AttomachineryRedCarpet.description>
  <AttomachineryBlueCarpet.label>blue attocarpet</AttomachineryBlueCarpet.label>
  <AttomachineryBlueCarpet.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a deep blue carpet. This carpet analogue feels like a shallow stream, perfect temperature. It leaves no residue or uncomfort.</AttomachineryBlueCarpet.description>
  <AttomachineryGreenCarpet.label>green attocarpet</AttomachineryGreenCarpet.label>
  <AttomachineryGreenCarpet.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a mossy green carpet. This one feels like short, dense and lush grass on ones feet. For the nature head.</AttomachineryGreenCarpet.description>
  <AttomachineryCreamCarpet.label>cream attocarpet</AttomachineryCreamCarpet.label>
  <AttomachineryCreamCarpet.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a creamy white carpet. This one feels like walking through whipped cream, although it leaves no residue or smell that would state otherwise.</AttomachineryCreamCarpet.description>
  <AttomachineryGrayCarpet.label>gray attocarpet</AttomachineryGrayCarpet.label>
  <AttomachineryGrayCarpet.description>Attomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a dark gray carpet. Surpisingly, this carpet analogue feels so neutral that one can't help but feel indifferent to it. It's not boring, just evidently professional.</AttomachineryGrayCarpet.description>
  <AttomachineryNaturalState.label>natural attomachinery</AttomachineryNaturalState.label>
  <AttomachineryNaturalState.description>The natural state of the attomachinery. With this deep green it seems to phase between a concrete analogue and a carpet.</AttomachineryNaturalState.description>
  <AttomachineryNaturalsoil.label>attosoil</AttomachineryNaturalsoil.label>
  <AttomachineryNaturalsoil.description>The Attomachines pull energy from the quantum foam in order to nutriate the plant beyond comprehension. It perfectly assembles itself in such a way that the plant is perfectly grown within no time at all.</AttomachineryNaturalsoil.description>
  <PicomachineryWood.label>picowood</PicomachineryWood.label>
  <PicomachineryWood.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of natural mahogany. It is virtually indistinguishable from wood, apart from the patterns.</PicomachineryWood.description>
  <PicomachineryRedCarpet.label>red picocarpet</PicomachineryRedCarpet.label>
  <PicomachineryRedCarpet.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a rich red carpet. This carpet analogue seems to feel just like red shag carpet. It's perfectly lovable.</PicomachineryRedCarpet.description>
  <PicomachineryBlueCarpet.label>blue picocarpet</PicomachineryBlueCarpet.label>
  <PicomachineryBlueCarpet.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a deep blue carpet. This carpet analogue feels like a shallow stream, perfect temperature. It leaves no residue or uncomfort.</PicomachineryBlueCarpet.description>
  <PicomachineryGreenCarpet.label>green picocarpet</PicomachineryGreenCarpet.label>
  <PicomachineryGreenCarpet.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a mossy green carpet. This one feels like short, dense and lush grass on ones feet. For the nature head.</PicomachineryGreenCarpet.description>
  <PicomachineryCreamCarpet.label>cream picocarpet</PicomachineryCreamCarpet.label>
  <PicomachineryCreamCarpet.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a creamy white carpet. This one feels like walking through whipped cream, although it leaves no residue or smell that would state otherwise.</PicomachineryCreamCarpet.description>
  <PicomachineryGrayCarpet.label>gray picocarpet</PicomachineryGrayCarpet.label>
  <PicomachineryGrayCarpet.description>Picomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a dark gray carpet. Surpisingly, this carpet analogue feels so neutral that one can't help but feel indifferent to it. It's not boring, just evidently professional.</PicomachineryGrayCarpet.description>
  <PicomachineryNaturalState.label>natural picomachinery</PicomachineryNaturalState.label>
  <PicomachineryNaturalState.description>The natural state of the picomachinery. With this deep purple it seems to phase between a concrete analogue, carpet, and wood.</PicomachineryNaturalState.description>
  <PicomachineryNaturalsoil.label>picosoil</PicomachineryNaturalsoil.label>
  <PicomachineryNaturalsoil.description>Picomachines which simulate the near perfect environment for any plant. It first scans the plant, finds out what it needs, and then provides it perfectly, allowing for perfect growth rates.</PicomachineryNaturalsoil.description>
  <NanomachineryWood.label>nanowood</NanomachineryWood.label>
  <NanomachineryWood.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of natural chestnut. It is virtually indistinguishable from wood, apart from the patterns.</NanomachineryWood.description>
  <NanomachineryRedCarpet.label>red nanocarpet</NanomachineryRedCarpet.label>
  <NanomachineryRedCarpet.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a rich red carpet. This carpet analogue seems to feel just like red shag carpet. It's perfectly lovable.</NanomachineryRedCarpet.description>
  <NanomachineryBlueCarpet.label>blue nanocarpet</NanomachineryBlueCarpet.label>
  <NanomachineryBlueCarpet.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a deep blue carpet. This carpet analogue feels like a shallow stream, perfect temperature. It leaves no residue or uncomfort.</NanomachineryBlueCarpet.description>
  <NanomachineryGreenCarpet.label>green nanocarpet</NanomachineryGreenCarpet.label>
  <NanomachineryGreenCarpet.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a mossy green carpet. This one feels like short, dense and lush grass on ones feet. For the nature head.</NanomachineryGreenCarpet.description>
  <NanomachineryCreamCarpet.label>cream nanocarpet</NanomachineryCreamCarpet.label>
  <NanomachineryCreamCarpet.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a creamy white carpet. This one feels like walking through whipped cream, although it leaves no residue or smell that would state otherwise.</NanomachineryCreamCarpet.description>
  <NanomachineryGrayCarpet.label>gray nanocarpet</NanomachineryGrayCarpet.label>
  <NanomachineryGrayCarpet.description>Nanomachines which have restructured and coloured themselves to the texture and colour of a dark gray carpet. Surpisingly, this carpet analogue feels so neutral that one can't help but feel indifferent to it. It's not boring, just evidently professional.</NanomachineryGrayCarpet.description>
  <NanomachineryNaturalState.label>natural nanomachinery</NanomachineryNaturalState.label>
  <NanomachineryNaturalState.description>The natural state of the nanomachinery. With this deep blue it seems to phase between a concrete analogue, carpet, and wood.</NanomachineryNaturalState.description>
  <NanomachineryNaturalsoil.label>nanosoil</NanomachineryNaturalsoil.label>
  <NanomachineryNaturalsoil.description>The nanomachines reconfigure themselves into a soil like analogue, while also simulating nutrients and certain trace elements perfect for growing. While not as good as Picosoil or Attosoil, it certainly is a step up from regular dirt.</NanomachineryNaturalsoil.description>
</LanguageData>