<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Mech_Agrihand.label>agrihand</Mech_Agrihand.label>
  <Mech_Agrihand.description>A small mechanoid designed to sow and harvest crops. While it is better suited to labor than combat, it can fight with built-in cutting blades if necessary.</Mech_Agrihand.description>
  <Mech_Agrihand.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Agrihand.tools.head.label>
  <Mech_Agrihand.tools.right_blade.label>right blade</Mech_Agrihand.tools.right_blade.label>
  <Mech_Agrihand.tools.right_blade.labelNoLocation>blade</Mech_Agrihand.tools.right_blade.labelNoLocation>
  
  <Mech_Cleansweeper.label>cleansweeper</Mech_Cleansweeper.label>
  <Mech_Cleansweeper.description>A light mechanoid designed for cleaning. Lacking a ranged weapon, it can make only weak melee attacks.</Mech_Cleansweeper.description>
  <Mech_Cleansweeper.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Cleansweeper.tools.head.label>
  
  <Mech_Constructoid.label>constructoid</Mech_Constructoid.label>
  <Mech_Constructoid.description>A small mechanoid designed to perform construction tasks. It can perform blunt melee attacks if necessary.</Mech_Constructoid.description>
  <Mech_Constructoid.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Constructoid.tools.head.label>
  <Mech_Constructoid.tools.torso.label>torso</Mech_Constructoid.tools.torso.label>
  
  <Mech_Fabricor.label>fabricor</Mech_Fabricor.label>
  <Mech_Fabricor.description>A small work mechanoid designed to craft all manner of manufactured objects.</Mech_Fabricor.description>
  <Mech_Fabricor.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Fabricor.tools.head.label>
  
  <Mech_Lifter.label>lifter</Mech_Lifter.label>
  <Mech_Lifter.description>A small mechanoid designed for hauling. Lacking a ranged weapon, it can make only weak melee attacks.</Mech_Lifter.description>
  <Mech_Lifter.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Lifter.tools.head.label>
  
  <Mech_Militor.label>militor</Mech_Militor.label>
  <Mech_Militor.description>A small combat mechanoid armed with a low-power mini-shotgun. Roughly four feet tall, militors lack the power, range, and toughness of more senior combat mechs. However, it is cheap to gestate and maintain, and so is often used as a rear guard or swarm attacker.\n\nIn war, mech armies are known to send militors into urban ruins to hunt down survivors after breaking the human defenses. For this reason, they are considered by some to be the most cruel of all mechanoid patterns.</Mech_Militor.description>
  <Mech_Militor.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Militor.tools.head.label>
  
  <Mech_Paramedic.label>paramedic</Mech_Paramedic.label>
  <Mech_Paramedic.description>A small mechanoid designed for non-violent emergency situation management and medical care. The paramedic can rescue the wounded, fight fires, treat the sick, and even perform surgery when a more-qualified human is not available. Its built-in jump launcher allows it to jump into, and out of, emergency situations, and its built-in firefoam popper can quickly extinguish fires.</Mech_Paramedic.description>
  <Mech_Paramedic.tools.head.label>head</Mech_Paramedic.tools.head.label>
  
  <Mech_WarUrchin.label>war urchin</Mech_WarUrchin.label>
  <Mech_WarUrchin.description>A small, deployable combat mechanoid usually manufactured inside an ultra-heavy war queen mech. War urchins are expendable fighters designed to swarm-attack enemies. They are mounted with short-ranged spiner guns and have a non-rechargeable power source.</Mech_WarUrchin.description>
  <Mech_WarUrchin.tools.head.label>head</Mech_WarUrchin.tools.head.label>
</LanguageData>