<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_DrankBlackTea.label>drank black tea</VBE_DrankBlackTea.label>
  <VBE_DrankBlackTea.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 20% and provides 15% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours.</VBE_DrankBlackTea.description>
  <VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.label>irish coffee high</VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>an irish coffee high</VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 16% amount and 16% reduction in rest fall rate. Increases global work speed by 16%. Hot coffee reduces hypothermia.</VBE_IrishCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_DrankKombuchaTea.label>drank kombucha tea</VBE_DrankKombuchaTea.label>
  <VBE_DrankKombuchaTea.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Kombucha tea reduces the effects of Diabetes if present.</VBE_DrankKombuchaTea.description>
  <VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.label>latte coffee high</VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a latte coffee high</VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 18% amount and 18% reduction in rest fall rate. Latte coffee reduces hypothermia.</VBE_LatteCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_YuenYeungHigh.label>yuenyeung high</VBE_YuenYeungHigh.label>
  <VBE_YuenYeungHigh.labelNoun>a coffee high</VBE_YuenYeungHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_YuenYeungHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 13% reduction in rest fall rate. The tea in it increases immunity gain speed by 15%. Cold coffee reduces heatstroke.</VBE_YuenYeungHigh.description>
  <VCE_ConsumedMintLeaves.label>consumed mint (from meal)</VCE_ConsumedMintLeaves.label>
  <VCE_ConsumedMintLeaves.description>Consumed some fresh mint leaves. The fresh breath increases social impact by 10%.</VCE_ConsumedMintLeaves.description>
  <VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.label>mint coffee high</VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a mint coffee high</VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 15% reduction in rest fall rate. Hot coffee reduces hypothermia. Mint coffee provides fresh breath, increasing social impact by 10%.</VBE_MintCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.label>dalgona coffee high</VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a dalgona coffee high</VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 15% reduction in rest fall rate. Cold coffee reduces heatstroke. Dalgona coffee provides a 10% research speed bonus.</VBE_DalgonaCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_DrankMintTea.label>drank mint tea</VBE_DrankMintTea.label>
  <VBE_DrankMintTea.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Mint tea provides fresh breath, increasing social impact by 10%.</VBE_DrankMintTea.description>
  <VBE_DrankMasalaChai.label>drank masala chai</VBE_DrankMasalaChai.label>
  <VBE_DrankMasalaChai.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Masala chai reduces the effects of Cholesterol if present.</VBE_DrankMasalaChai.description>
  <VBE_DrankNoonChai.label>drank noon chai</VBE_DrankNoonChai.label>
  <VBE_DrankNoonChai.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Noon chai reduces the effects of High Blood Pressure if present.</VBE_DrankNoonChai.description>
  <VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.label>lemon coffee high</VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.label>
  <VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>a lemon coffee high</VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.description>Caffeine naturally found in coffee once metabolised increases the stimuli in one's nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as clearing ones mind. Increases learning speed by a 15% amount and 15% reduction in rest fall rate. Hot coffee reduces hypothermia. Lemon coffee acts as a remedy against Gut Worms, increasing tending quality with each coffee drank.</VBE_LemonCoffeeHigh.description>
  <VBE_DrankLemonTea.label>drank lemon tea</VBE_DrankLemonTea.label>
  <VBE_DrankLemonTea.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Lemon tea acts as a remedy against Gut Worms, increasing tending quality with each coffee drank.</VBE_DrankLemonTea.description>
  <VBE_DrankEarlGreyTea.label>drank earl grey tea</VBE_DrankEarlGreyTea.label>
  <VBE_DrankEarlGreyTea.description>Tannins naturally found in tea once metabolised increases the stimuli in ones nervous system, suppressing ones urge to sleep, as well as boosting ones immune system. Increases immunity gain speed by 15% and provides 10% reduction in rest fall rate for 5 hours. Earl grey tea provides a 10% research speed bonus.</VBE_DrankEarlGreyTea.description>
</LanguageData>