<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.label>make espresso coffee</VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.label>
  <VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.description>Make a warm, bitter beverage usually complemented with milk and sugar. A favorite among students and office workers across the galaxy due to high caffeine content and pleasing aroma. Brewing coffee in a espresso machine is generally much faster.</VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.description>
  <VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.jobString>Making coffee.</VBE_MakeCoffeeFast.jobString>
  <VBE_ReheatCoffee.label>reheat iced coffee</VBE_ReheatCoffee.label>
  <VBE_ReheatCoffee.description>This espresso machine has a small built-in grill to reheat iced coffee.</VBE_ReheatCoffee.description>
  <VBE_ReheatCoffee.jobString>Reheating iced coffee.</VBE_ReheatCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.label>brew latte coffee</VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.description>Brew a potent espresso mixed with fresh milk to help ease bitterness before pouring and serving. Lattes have a reputation of being particularly meant for “sophisticated” individuals.</VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.jobString>Brewing latte coffee.</VBE_BrewLatteCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.label>brew mocha coffee</VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.description>Brew a coffee mixed with sweet and luxurious chocolate. Those of snobbish persuasion would argue mocha is more of a dessert than an actual coffee drink.</VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.jobString>Brewing mocha coffee.</VBE_BrewMochaCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.label>brew irish coffee</VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.description>Brew a drink made with whiskey and coffee blended thoroughly before forming a head and being topped with a spoonful of whipped cream. Perfect for those who just got out of bed and are already wanting to go back to it.</VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.jobString>Brewing irish coffee.</VBE_BrewIrishCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.label>brew cannibal coffee</VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.description>Brew a drink... for a very particular... refined coffee drinker.</VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.jobString>Brewing cannibal coffee.</VBE_BrewCannibalCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeTeaFast.label>make fast tea</VBE_MakeTeaFast.label>
  <VBE_MakeTeaFast.description>Make a pleasing, aromatic beverage prepared by steeping a bag of tea leaves in boiling water. Brewing tea in this specially prepared espresso machine is generally much faster.</VBE_MakeTeaFast.description>
  <VBE_MakeTeaFast.jobString>Making fast tea.</VBE_MakeTeaFast.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeBlackTea.label>make black tea</VBE_MakeBlackTea.label>
  <VBE_MakeBlackTea.description>Make a particularly bitter tea cut with creamy milk, wakes one up a bit and relaxes one's mind.</VBE_MakeBlackTea.description>
  <VBE_MakeBlackTea.jobString>Making black tea.</VBE_MakeBlackTea.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeYuenYeung.label>make yuenyeung</VBE_MakeYuenYeung.label>
  <VBE_MakeYuenYeung.description>Make a mixture of coffee and tea. Tea and coffee drinkers respectively set their differences aside while concocting this unholy amalgamation. Whether it’s served hot or cold it’s equally confusing to the imbiber.</VBE_MakeYuenYeung.description>
  <VBE_MakeYuenYeung.jobString>Making yuenyeung.</VBE_MakeYuenYeung.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeKombucha.label>make kombucha tea</VBE_MakeKombucha.label>
  <VBE_MakeKombucha.description>Make a sugary tea left out to ferment, after fermenting the end product is a sweet and sour, sometimes even naturally fizzy drink known as kombucha. Praised for health benefits, though some remain skeptical.</VBE_MakeKombucha.description>
  <VBE_MakeKombucha.jobString>Making kombucha tea.</VBE_MakeKombucha.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.label>brew espresso romano</VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.description>Brew an already acidic coffee garnished with a wedge of more acidic lemon, meant to be juiced into the coffee before quickly consumed while hot. An acquired taste to be sure but lauded by those who do prefer it.</VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.jobString>Brewing espresso romano.</VBE_BrewLemonCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeLemonTea.label>make lemon tea</VBE_MakeLemonTea.label>
  <VBE_MakeLemonTea.description>Make a dark tea cut with water, chilled and garnished with a wedge of bright lemon.</VBE_MakeLemonTea.description>
  <VBE_MakeLemonTea.jobString>Making lemon tea.</VBE_MakeLemonTea.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.label>make earl grey tea</VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.label>
  <VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.description>Make a very strong and semi-sweet fruity tea. Floral notes dance around one's pallet at even the most dull scent. People who finish the drink feel strangely urged to colonize.</VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.description>
  <VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.jobString>Making earl grey tea.</VBE_MakeEarlGreyTea.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewMintCoffee.label>brew mint coffee</VBE_BrewMintCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewMintCoffee.description>Brew a bitter espresso mixed with cream or milk, then further mixed with mint oil and garnished. Cool and velvety coffee gives way to an even cooler, soothing aftertaste, not to mention great smelling breath.</VBE_BrewMintCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewMintCoffee.jobString>Brewing mint coffee.</VBE_BrewMintCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.label>brew dalgona coffee</VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.label>
  <VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.description>Brew a trendy, newer drink in the world of coffee rumored to originate from far off steamworlds. Coffee granules are rapidly mixed with sugar to form a thick, luxuriously sweet foam. Afterwards the foam is dispersed over deeply chilled milk before drinking.</VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.description>
  <VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.jobString>Brewing dalgona coffee.</VBE_BrewDalgonaCoffee.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeGreenTea.label>make green tea</VBE_MakeGreenTea.label>
  <VBE_MakeGreenTea.description>Make a light, citrusy green tea spiked with sugar to create a buttery, almost nutty flavor.</VBE_MakeGreenTea.description>
  <VBE_MakeGreenTea.jobString>Making green tea.</VBE_MakeGreenTea.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeMintTea.label>make mint tea</VBE_MakeMintTea.label>
  <VBE_MakeMintTea.description>Make black tea leaves mixed with mint leaves and deeply steeped, then garnished with additional mint leaves. Leaves your breath surprisingly fresh.</VBE_MakeMintTea.description>
  <VBE_MakeMintTea.jobString>Making mint tea.</VBE_MakeMintTea.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeMasalaChai.label>make masala chai</VBE_MakeMasalaChai.label>
  <VBE_MakeMasalaChai.description>Make a musty, warm, almost woody tea crafted by simple leaves and complex spices. Alleged to be good against high cholesterol.</VBE_MakeMasalaChai.description>
  <VBE_MakeMasalaChai.jobString>Making masala chai.</VBE_MakeMasalaChai.jobString>
  <VBE_MakeNoonChai.label>make noon chai</VBE_MakeNoonChai.label>
  <VBE_MakeNoonChai.description>Make an ancient Kashmiri tea mixing tea leaves, a pinch of salt and baking soda, which results in an striking pink beverage that is famous for being not only delicious but also healthy for the body. Very efficient for treating those with a high blood pressure.</VBE_MakeNoonChai.description>
  <VBE_MakeNoonChai.jobString>Making noon chai.</VBE_MakeNoonChai.jobString>
</LanguageData>