<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AdvancedArchotechLeg.label>advanced archotech leg</AdvancedArchotechLeg.label>
  <AdvancedArchotechLeg.description>An advanced version of the archotech's artificial leg. It looks the same as a regular leg, but allows you much faster movement. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</AdvancedArchotechLeg.description>
  <AdvancedArchotechArm.label>advanced archotech arm</AdvancedArchotechArm.label>
  <AdvancedArchotechArm.description>An advanced version of the archotech's artificial arm. It looks the same, but studies on glitterworlds have proven the arm to be sentient. This added feature allows the arm to make quick descisions a human brain couldn't possibly make. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</AdvancedArchotechArm.description>
  <ArchotechObliterator.label>archotech obliterator</ArchotechObliterator.label>
  <ArchotechObliterator.description>An artificial arm which employs all the benefits of a normal archotech arm, but includes new melee combat features based around attrition and enemy capture. With extremely fast servos the fist is able to extend and retract at remarkable speeds, causing a minature shockwave to form infront of the fist. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechObliterator.description>
  <ArchotechHeart.label>archotech heart</ArchotechHeart.label>
  <ArchotechHeart.description>An artificial heart built by an archotech. Rather than pumping, the circulation of blood is a constant flow, releasing small nanomachines into the blood when needed. These small machines check for cholesterol, and other harmful things in arteries and capillaries, and metabolizes them into new nanomachinery, or into waste. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechHeart.description>
  <ArchotechKidney.label>archotech kidney</ArchotechKidney.label>
  <ArchotechKidney.description>An artificial kidney built by an archotech. It's capability to filter waste and extra water from the host's blood is so efficient that there's hardly any waste at all, instead being converted into useful antibodies and vitamins. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechKidney.description>
  <ArchotechLiver.label>archotech liver</ArchotechLiver.label>
  <ArchotechLiver.description>An artificial liver built by an archotech. It's user is able to metabolize pretty much anything, from being able to drink pure grain alcohol to metabolizing the most harmful of drugs. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLiver.description>
  <ArchotechPelvis.label>archotech pelvis</ArchotechPelvis.label>
  <ArchotechPelvis.description>An artificial pelvis built by an archotech. It doesn't do much, but allows for some improvements to the host, along with armor. Its workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechPelvis.description>
  <ArchotechSpine.label>archotech spine</ArchotechSpine.label>
  <ArchotechSpine.description>An artificial spine built by an archotech. Each individual disc and sector on the spine interacts with the will of it's host, and proceeds to adjust itself for optimal posture. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechSpine.description>
  <ArchotechLung.label>archotech lung</ArchotechLung.label>
  <ArchotechLung.description>An artificial lung built by an archotech. The optimization of respiration allows for even the smallest of breaths to last minutes. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLung.description>
  <ArchotechStomach.label>archotech stomach</ArchotechStomach.label>
  <ArchotechStomach.description>An artificial stomach built by an archotech. It's host is capable of eating as little, or as much as they want, as nutrition is automatically cared for by the stomach. It has full awareness of what it's host needs, from vitamins to minerals, and psychicly communicates this to them. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechStomach.description>
  <ArchotechDenture.label>archotech denture</ArchotechDenture.label>
  <ArchotechDenture.description>An artifical denture built by an archotech. Once installed in someone's mouth, it rapidly covers the other teeth until fully covered, or replaces missing teeth.</ArchotechDenture.description>
  <ArchotechEar.label>archotech ear</ArchotechEar.label>
  <ArchotechEar.description>An artificial ear built by an archotech. Once installed at the base of the ear, It's user is able to hear for miles ahead with no loss of quality, allowing them to hear the wingbeats of a fly from miles away if they so wish. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechEar.description>
  <ArchotechDeathClaw.label>archotech death claw</ArchotechDeathClaw.label>
  <ArchotechDeathClaw.description>An artificial arm built by an archotech. From the arm pertrudes giant spikes and claws which lash out and serrate anything that comes too close. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechDeathClaw.description>
  <ArchotechBrainMelder.label>archotech brain melder</ArchotechBrainMelder.label>
  <ArchotechBrainMelder.description>An impressive feat of medical engineering unlike anything else. From what has been gleaned by those who research archotechnologies, it seems to pump attomachines throughout the whole body from it's central core, which heal all scars. On top of this, it stimulates the brain's dopamine and seratonin receptors, giving it's user a great deal of satisfaction. Scientists still don't understand how it manages to do this while also keeping the user fully concious, or how it somehow improves their intellect and learning factors too.</ArchotechBrainMelder.description>
  <ArchotechMembrane.label>archotech membrane</ArchotechMembrane.label>
  <ArchotechMembrane.description>An extremely thin membrane over the entire body. It has many different uses, but it is mainly used for protection.</ArchotechMembrane.description>
  <BasicArchotechWorkbench.label>basic archotech workbench</BasicArchotechWorkbench.label>
  <BasicArchotechWorkbench.description>A very rudimentary way to create both the different tiers of nanomachines and their very basic large scale components.</BasicArchotechWorkbench.description>
  <Attomachinery.label>Attomachinery</Attomachinery.label>
  <Attomachinery.description>A dark cluster of attomachinery. Even with the highest grade glitterworld microscopes, it is impossible to see the entire structure of one of these cells, which is unlike anything ever seen before in reality, as these machines seem to be smaller than a hydrogen atom. The casing itself seems to be made out of the archotech substance. It seems to form a psychic bond with whoever touches it, allowing the user to use it for any type of fabrication. It's strength is unheard of anywhere else in the universe.</Attomachinery.description>
  <Picomachinery.label>Picomachinery</Picomachinery.label>
  <Picomachinery.description>A thick cluster of picomachinery. Each individual machine is measured at around 1/5th the size of a hydrogen atom. It is used as a major building unit in many transcendent archotech structures, from buildings to fabrics, although it is not as small as their attomachinery counterpart and can not create such advanced weapons. It's workings are foreign to the human mind, and are extremely difficult to observe, due to their size.</Picomachinery.description>
  <Nanomachinery.label>Nanomachinery</Nanomachinery.label>
  <Nanomachinery.description>A dense cluster of Nanomachinery. This almost resembles glitterworld mechanites, which is some of the most advanced tech avaliable. To a transcendent, however, it is merely a stepping stone to much smaller and more capable machines. It's still useful as a building material and fabric, but to much less of an extent then it's two successors. The strangest thing about this machine is it's ability to power itself. From what glitterworld scientists can see, it seemingly rips endless power from the quantum foam of the universe and converts it into mechanical energy. It is unknown how the machine is capable of doing such feats.</Nanomachinery.description>
</LanguageData>