<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <SewageSludgeComposting.label>sewage sludge composting</SewageSludgeComposting.label>
  <SewageSludgeComposting.description>When properly treated and processed, sewage sludge becomes biosolids that offer a small boost to terrain fertility. Useful for harsh environments with limited space to grow. Biosolids also produce a large boost to the fertility of sand which can make it fertile when combined with irrigation.</SewageSludgeComposting.description>
  <MultiSplitAirCon.label>multi-split air conditioning</MultiSplitAirCon.label>
  <MultiSplitAirCon.description>Build multi-split air conditioning systems with outdoor units piped to indoor units and freezers.</MultiSplitAirCon.description>
  <Plumbing.label>plumbing</Plumbing.label>
  <Plumbing.description>Use pipes, plumbing fixtures, storage tanks, wind pumps and other apparatuses to deliver and drain water and sewage.</Plumbing.description>
  <LogBoilers.label>heating</LogBoilers.label>
  <LogBoilers.description>Build log boilers which can be used to heat rooms and can be placed adjacent to baths to heat bathwater.</LogBoilers.description>
  <CentralHeating.label>central heating</CentralHeating.label>
  <CentralHeating.description>Build central heating systems with radiators, hot water tanks, boilers and thermostats.</CentralHeating.description>
  <ModernFixtures.label>modern bathroom fixtures</ModernFixtures.label>
  <ModernFixtures.description>Build modern-style bathroom fixtures like toilets and showers.</ModernFixtures.description>
  <ElectricPumps.label>electric pumps</ElectricPumps.label>
  <ElectricPumps.description>Powered water pumps for pressurized continuous water pumping.</ElectricPumps.description>
  <AdvancedShowers.label>power showers</AdvancedShowers.label>
  <AdvancedShowers.description>Build power showers which halve the time spent showering and improve comfort.</AdvancedShowers.description>
  <AdvancedToilets.label>smart toilets</AdvancedToilets.label>
  <AdvancedToilets.description>Build smart toilets which are twice as water efficient as a standard toilets and provide more comfort.</AdvancedToilets.description>
  <HotTubs.label>hot tubs</HotTubs.label>
  <HotTubs.description>Build hot tubs which can be used for hydrotherapy, relaxation, and pleasure.</HotTubs.description>
  <LargeWaterPumps.label>industrial-scale pumps</LargeWaterPumps.label>
  <LargeWaterPumps.description>Build industrial-scale water pumps and storage tanks.</LargeWaterPumps.description>
  <DeepWells.label>deep wells</DeepWells.label>
  <DeepWells.description>Drill deeper wells to access a much larger area of ground water.</DeepWells.description>
  <WashingMachines.label>washing machines</WashingMachines.label>
  <WashingMachines.description>Build washing machines that can wash clothes so well that you couldn't even tell someone died wearing it!.</WashingMachines.description>
  <WaterFiltration.label>water filtration</WaterFiltration.label>
  <WaterFiltration.description>Build water filtration systems which treat the water supply, eliminating the risk of disease.</WaterFiltration.description>
  <SepticTanks.label>septic tanks</SepticTanks.label>
  <SepticTanks.description>Build septic tanks which accumulate sewage and provide moderate treatment of sewage.</SepticTanks.description>
  <SewageTreatment.label>sewage treatment</SewageTreatment.label>
  <SewageTreatment.description>Build large sewage treatment systems which accumulate large amounts of sewage and provide fast treatment of sewage.</SewageTreatment.description>
  <SwimmingPools.label>swimming pools</SwimmingPools.label>
  <SwimmingPools.description>Build swimming pools.</SwimmingPools.description>
  <Irrigation.label>irrigation</Irrigation.label>
  <Irrigation.description>Build sprinklers that can irrigate soil to improve fertility.</Irrigation.description>
  <FireSuppression.label>fire suppression</FireSuppression.label>
  <FireSuppression.description>Build sprinklers that suppress fires with a spray of water.</FireSuppression.description>
</LanguageData>