<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <EVOR_Research_Start1.label>Raw Protein Extraction</EVOR_Research_Start1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Start1.description>With the increased knowledge of biology it is now possible to extract the raw building blocks out of already differentiated matter with the help of a Biofuel Refinery.</EVOR_Research_Start1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Start2.label>Nano-Scale Cellular Engineering</EVOR_Research_Start2.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Start2.description>By combining the knowledge of biology and bionics, it is now possible to engineer nanites that can mold raw biological materials into cells of our choosing with the help of a Machining Table.</EVOR_Research_Start2.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Start3.label>Bio-Mechanical Tissue Application</EVOR_Research_Start3.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Start3.description>Through the selective process of germinating and stimulating stem cells at the nano-scale with mechanites, it is possible to create simple biological frameworks.</EVOR_Research_Start3.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs1.label>Basic Organ Application</EVOR_Research_Organs1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs1.description>The continued understanding of stem cells and mechanite integration has allowed the development of advanced cellular structures which can be utilized to create advanced internal organs.</EVOR_Research_Organs1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs2.label>Complex Organ Application</EVOR_Research_Organs2.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs2.description>Further research into organ creation allows to design more efficient versions of our already-existing organs.</EVOR_Research_Organs2.description>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalEyes.label>Optic nerve rerouting</EVOR_Research_AdditionalEyes.label>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalEyes.description>Thanks to research into the development of fetuses it was discovered how to use stem cells to grow additional optic stalks which then develop into optic nerves.</EVOR_Research_AdditionalEyes.description>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalEars.label>Auditory sytem reinvention</EVOR_Research_AdditionalEars.label>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalEars.description>By breaking down and fully understanding the auditory systems of test subjects, a way was found to expand the auditory system insie of the head.</EVOR_Research_AdditionalEars.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs3.label>Advanced Organ Application</EVOR_Research_Organs3.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Organs3.description>The understanding of the most difficult cellular structures unlocks even more complex organs.</EVOR_Research_Organs3.description>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalOrgans.label>Additional Organs</EVOR_Research_AdditionalOrgans.label>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalOrgans.description>By decreasing the size of current organs and finding shortcuts between them, more room can be made for additional ones.</EVOR_Research_AdditionalOrgans.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Brain1.label>Neural Re-Engineering</EVOR_Research_Brain1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Brain1.description>By understanding how our vast intellect is driven by our brains, we can enchance our mental capabilities to untold heights.</EVOR_Research_Brain1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Outer1.label>Resilient Tissue Framework</EVOR_Research_Outer1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Outer1.description>Restructuring the tissue frameworks to survive the stress of being outside the body is crucial to creating defensive adaptations.</EVOR_Research_Outer1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs1.label>Biological Framework Application</EVOR_Research_Limbs1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs1.description>To create bones and musculature it must first be understood how to propagate the cells and mechanites in load bearing configurations.</EVOR_Research_Limbs1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs2.label>Advanced Limb Structures</EVOR_Research_Limbs2.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs2.description>The capability to create simple load-bearing structures has been understood, now the technology has to be scaled up.</EVOR_Research_Limbs2.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs3.label>Limb-Torso Support Structures</EVOR_Research_Limbs3.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs3.description>By researching how our bodies control and and structure our limbs, we can graft more limbs onto our bodies to grow beyond the limit of just four limbs.</EVOR_Research_Limbs3.description>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalLegs.label>Movement limbs improvisation</EVOR_Research_AdditionalLegs.label>
  <EVOR_Research_AdditionalLegs.description>Restructuring of the torso made it possible to efficiently attach more legs to ensure faster movement of pawns.</EVOR_Research_AdditionalLegs.description>
  <EVOR_Research_ExpandedLimbBattleUtility.label>Expanded limb battle utility</EVOR_Research_ExpandedLimbBattleUtility.label>
  <EVOR_Research_ExpandedLimbBattleUtility.description>Through further research into the animal kingdom, new ways to hide weapons inside of our limbs were discovered.</EVOR_Research_ExpandedLimbBattleUtility.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_Lesions.label>Weaponized Germ Engineering</EVOR_Research_Artifact_Lesions.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_Lesions.description>With more knowledge of how to build pathogens from the ground up, we can weaponize them as a deterrent.</EVOR_Research_Artifact_Lesions.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_Tortoise.label>Engineered Resistant Shell Plating</EVOR_Research_Artifact_Tortoise.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_Tortoise.description>With more knowledge of how to create durable biostructures, we can create a strong plating that is affective against all kinds of damage.</EVOR_Research_Artifact_Tortoise.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Psychic1.label>Psychic Synapse Network</EVOR_Research_Psychic1.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Psychic1.description>Thanks to research into the brain, an organ that increases the levels of psychic power can be created</EVOR_Research_Psychic1.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs4.label>Bio-weapon Symbiosis</EVOR_Research_Limbs4.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Limbs4.description>By creating specialized organisms to live in our limbs, we can create bio-weapons utilizing them that are part of our very own bodies.</EVOR_Research_Limbs4.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_NornCrown.label>Psychic Area Mood Profileration</EVOR_Research_Artifact_NornCrown.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_NornCrown.description>With more knowledge of how the mind interacts with psychic waves, a synaptic node that allows one to affect others with their mood can be created.</EVOR_Research_Artifact_NornCrown.description>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_ShimmerWorm.label>Pseudo-Invisibility Studies</EVOR_Research_Artifact_ShimmerWorm.label>
  <EVOR_Research_Artifact_ShimmerWorm.description>By combining the hosts with an alien worms DNA it is possible to turn the host invisible when perceiving pain.</EVOR_Research_Artifact_ShimmerWorm.description>
</LanguageData>