<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PTPsychicTraier.label>Psychic Trainer</PTPsychicTraier.label>
  <PTPsychicTraier.description>A chamber capable of training pawns to harness the power of psychic phenomenon, giving them psionic abilites.</PTPsychicTraier.description>
  <PTPsychicWorkbench.label>Psychic Workbench</PTPsychicWorkbench.label>
  <PTPsychicWorkbench.description>A workbench for disassembling psychic artifacts, creating psychic equipment, and even creating athenium.</PTPsychicWorkbench.description>
  <PTPsychicSuppressionFieldProjector.label>Psychic Suppression Field Projector</PTPsychicSuppressionFieldProjector.label>
  <PTPsychicSuppressionFieldProjector.description>A building which projects a psychic suppression field in a small area around it, lower the psychic sensitivity of those nearby. They can be tuned to different intensities and radii, though it takes time for them to change to new targets.\n\nDue to the complex wave interactions, suppression fields do not stack.</PTPsychicSuppressionFieldProjector.description>
  <PTPsionicCommandoArmor.label>psionic commando armor</PTPsionicCommandoArmor.label>
  <PTPsionicCommandoArmor.description>An advanced suit of power armor with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics. This version is focused on defensive capability, to the detriment of psionic enhancement.</PTPsionicCommandoArmor.description>
  <PTPsionicCommandoHelmet.label>psionic commando helmet</PTPsionicCommandoHelmet.label>
  <PTPsionicCommandoHelmet.description>An advanced power armor helmet with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics. This version is focused on defensive capability, to the detriment of psionic enhancement.</PTPsionicCommandoHelmet.description>
  <PTPsionicWarriorArmor.label>psionic warrior armor</PTPsionicWarriorArmor.label>
  <PTPsionicWarriorArmor.description>An advanced suit of power armor with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics. This version has a balanced focus between defensive capability and psionic enhancement.</PTPsionicWarriorArmor.description>
  <PTPsionicWarriorHelmet.label>psionic warrior helmet</PTPsionicWarriorHelmet.label>
  <PTPsionicWarriorHelmet.description>An advanced power armor helmet with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics. This version has a balanced focus between defensive capability and psionic enhancement.</PTPsionicWarriorHelmet.description>
  <PTPsionicConduitArmor.label>psionic conduit armor</PTPsionicConduitArmor.label>
  <PTPsionicConduitArmor.description>An advanced suit of power armor with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics. This version is focused on enhancing psionic capability to the detriment of defensive capacity.</PTPsionicConduitArmor.description>
  <PTPsionicConduitHelmet.label>psionic conduit helmet</PTPsionicConduitHelmet.label>
  <PTPsionicConduitHelmet.description>An advanced power armor helmet with embedded psychic conduits allowing for enhanced usage of psionics.</PTPsionicConduitHelmet.description>
  <PTAdvancedPsychicFoil.label>advanced psychic foil helmet</PTAdvancedPsychicFoil.label>
  <PTAdvancedPsychicFoil.description>An advanced psychic foil helmet, capable of insulating the wearer from most psychic waves.</PTAdvancedPsychicFoil.description>
  <PTPsiRobe.label>psi robe</PTPsiRobe.label>
  <PTPsiRobe.description>A robe that enhances the psionic capabilities of the wearer.\n\nRobes don't have any special properties that make them suited for psionic usage, but they just seem fitting.</PTPsiRobe.description>
  <PTFocusRobe.label>focus robe</PTFocusRobe.label>
  <PTFocusRobe.description>A robe that enhances the psi energy regeneration of the wearer.\n\nRobes don't have any special properties that make them suited for psionic usage, but they just seem fitting.</PTFocusRobe.description>
  <PTCapacitorRobe.label>capacitor robe</PTCapacitorRobe.label>
  <PTCapacitorRobe.description>A robe that enhances the max psi energy of the wearer.\n\nRobes don't have any special properties that make them suited for psionic usage, but they just seem fitting.</PTCapacitorRobe.description>
  <PTPsiHood.label>psi hood</PTPsiHood.label>
  <PTPsiHood.description>A hood that enhances the psionic capabilities of the wearer.\n\nHoods don't have any special properties that make them suited for psionic usage, but they just seem fitting.</PTPsiHood.description>
  <PTAthenium.label>Athenium</PTAthenium.label>
  <PTAthenium.description>A bizarre crystalline material capable of interacting with psychic waves. It is useful in the creation of psychically active equipment and devices.</PTAthenium.description>
</LanguageData>