<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Leather_ChJAndroid.label>android leather</Leather_ChJAndroid.label>
  <Leather_ChJAndroid.description>Tanned, dried, scraped synthetic android skin. Many people find this material horrifying. Some find it fascinating. While a decent leather, it neither protects nor insulates particularly well.</Leather_ChJAndroid.description>
  <ChJAndroidThermalBandages.label>thermal wrapping</ChJAndroidThermalBandages.label>
  <ChJAndroidThermalBandages.description>A garment which barely covers the wearer, just enough to cover the important bits. Does not come with a Multi-Pass.</ChJAndroidThermalBandages.description>
  <ChjAndroidMaidOutfit.label>maid dress</ChjAndroidMaidOutfit.label>
  <ChjAndroidMaidOutfit.description>Based off the traditional maid outfit, the broad apron and attractive cuffs disguise small motors that assist in cleaning and other common household tasks. Popular with the Urbworld elite who wish to preserve traditional charm while pragmatically utilizing technology to enhance their staff.</ChjAndroidMaidOutfit.description>
  <ChjAndroidMaidBattleDress.label>battle dress</ChjAndroidMaidBattleDress.label>
  <ChjAndroidMaidBattleDress.description>A charming combination of a light plasteel exo-skeleton and devilstrand-reinforced uniform with a sassy skirt. Female combat androids favor this style, which accentuates combat methodology: speed and overwhelming aggression.</ChjAndroidMaidBattleDress.description>
  <ChjAndroidBattleMaidHat.label>battle maid hat</ChjAndroidBattleMaidHat.label>
  <ChjAndroidBattleMaidHat.description>A traditional looking maid hat with a military theme. Comes with a headset for communicating with allies.</ChjAndroidBattleMaidHat.description>
  <ChJAndroidPrinter.label>android printer</ChJAndroidPrinter.label>
  <ChJAndroidPrinter.description>An oversized 3D printer specifically made for printing Androids. Outfitted with a highly advanced computer to ensure the printing process go as planned.\n\nBy breaking down nutritious plants and meat the printer can refine it into synthetic flesh, organs and fluids to mimic a living being very convincingly.</ChJAndroidPrinter.description>
  <ChJDroidPrinter.label>droid fabricator</ChJDroidPrinter.label>
  <ChJDroidPrinter.description>A automatic fabricator when supplied with power and materials will assemble a Droid. Droids are soulless automatons perfect for dumb labor and guard duty due to not needing to rest and partake in sapient tasks.</ChJDroidPrinter.description>
  <ChjDroidHibernationPad.label>hibernation pad</ChjDroidHibernationPad.label>
  <ChjDroidHibernationPad.description>A relatively flat circular pad where droids can hunker down and go into hibernation mode.</ChjDroidHibernationPad.description>
  <ChjFilthCoolant.label>coolant</ChjFilthCoolant.label>
  <ChjAndroidBattery.label>droid battery</ChjAndroidBattery.label>
  <ChjAndroidBattery.description>Consumable batteries compatible for use for Androids and Droids.</ChjAndroidBattery.description>
  <ChjDroidRepairParts.label>droid repair parts</ChjDroidRepairParts.label>
  <ChjDroidRepairParts.description>Miscellanous droid parts, adhesives, solder, welding resources &amp; metal plates for repairing droids.</ChjDroidRepairParts.description>
  <ChjDroidRepairKit.label>droid repair kit</ChjDroidRepairKit.label>
  <ChjDroidRepairKit.description>A repair kit containing the tools and materials, to fully restore a Droid to mint condition, from wear and tear to missing parts. Also refills coolant on Droids and Androids.\n\nUsed as a operation.</ChjDroidRepairKit.description>
  <ChjAndroid_SolarDuster.description>A long duster coat for blocking the sun and grit of the desert. Now with solarpanels for long journeys and passive power generation at home.</ChjAndroid_SolarDuster.description>
  <ChjAndroid_SolarDuster.label>droid solarpanel duster</ChjAndroid_SolarDuster.label>
  <ChjAndroid_ChemfuelGenerator.label>droid chemfuel generator belt</ChjAndroid_ChemfuelGenerator.label>
  <ChjAndroid_ChemfuelGenerator.description>A portable chemfuel generator which can be worn by Droids and Androids alike. Lasts for days on a single tank.</ChjAndroid_ChemfuelGenerator.description>
  <ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.label>droid assembly kit</ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.label>
  <ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.description>A kit containing a disassembled Droid with all the tools required to assemble it.</ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.description>
  <ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.comps.0.useLabel>Assemble Droid</ChjAndroidDroidAssemblyKit.comps.0.useLabel>
  <ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.label>battle droid assembly kit</ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.label>
  <ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.description>A kit containing a disassembled Battle droid with all the tools required to assemble it.</ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.description>
  <ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.comps.0.useLabel>Assemble Battle droid</ChjAndroidBattleDroidAssemblyKit.comps.0.useLabel>
  <ChjAndroidBullet_RebelRifle.label>charge bolt</ChjAndroidBullet_RebelRifle.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.label>rebel rifle</ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.description>Charged-shot energy/projectile semi automatic rifle made from whatever industrial equipment and broken charge weapon technology parts that could be scavenged.</ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.description>
  <ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.tools.0.label>stock</ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.tools.0.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.tools.1.label>barrel</ChjAndroidGun_RebelRifle.tools.1.label>
  <ChjAndroidBullet_Rebelpistol.label>rebel pistol bullet</ChjAndroidBullet_Rebelpistol.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.label>rebel pistol</ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.description>Scrambled together from a nailgun and outdated charge weapon technology this weapon is serviceable. Weak and short range, but quick.</ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.description>
  <ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.tools.0.label>grip</ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.tools.0.label>
  <ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.tools.1.label>barrel</ChjAndroidGun_Rebelpistol.tools.1.label>
  <Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.label>core launcher</Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.label>
  <Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.description>A wide-barreled core bolt launcher designed for use on battle droids. It fires superheated bolts of plasma with an explosive core that explode upon impact.</Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.description>
  <Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_ChjCoreLauncher.tools.1.label>
  <Bullet_ChjCoreLauncher.label>core bolt</Bullet_ChjCoreLauncher.label>
</LanguageData>