<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GerzeePowerArmor.label>Gerzee power armor</GerzeePowerArmor.label>
  <GerzeePowerArmor.description>A large suit of powered armor made to fit the Gerzee physique. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a Gerzee to wear this heavy armor and still move easily, while built-in cooling tech helps the wearer survive warfare in extremely hot climates.\n\nArmor like this is really only seen in warefare companies that attempt to alter Gerzee into viable soldiers.</GerzeePowerArmor.description>
  <GerzeeHelm_Apparel.label>Gerzee helmet</GerzeeHelm_Apparel.label>
  <GerzeeHelm_Apparel.description>A simple helmet for a Gerzee, giving moderate protection against sharp attacks. Not effective against blunt weapons. Can be used by non-Gerzee by adjusting the straps. While heavier than a normal helmet, the holes made for Gerzee eye stems means there's less overall protection than a regular simple helmet.</GerzeeHelm_Apparel.description>
  <GerzeePowerArmorHelmet.label>Gerzee power helmet</GerzeePowerArmorHelmet.label>
  <GerzeePowerArmorHelmet.description>A power armor helmet, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates.\n\nArmor like this is usually only seen in warefare companies that attempt to alter Gerzee into viable soldiers.</GerzeePowerArmorHelmet.description>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.label>Gerzee Ram</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.label>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.description>A huge battering ram crafted to be held only by creatures of great strength, like the Gerzee. Extremely hard-hitting. Despite the careful balancing required to make such a heavy weapon useable, it has a very slow swing recovery.</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.description>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.0.label>center grip</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.0.label>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.1.label>head</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.1.label>
  <Grungo_GerzeeFrozenPlant.label>Grungo plant</Grungo_GerzeeFrozenPlant.label>
  <Grungo_GerzeeFrozenPlant.description>A plant from the Gerzee homeworld with a texture similar to mushrooms. Naturally found under gigantic trees in frozen forests, the plant is an oddity to Humanity in that it will grow in freezing weather while also being hypersensitive to any form of light. Growing Grungo takes a lot of skillful work to get the plant started in such foreign soil, though the edible parts can be continuously harvested without needing to replant. Originally only eaten as a snack by Gerzee children who happen to walk past it, Grungo is the only freezing-temperature option to the Gerzee that's made it to the rimworlds.\n\nNote: The stats don't show the right numbers for minimum temperature. You can grow this in below-freezing temperatures.</Grungo_GerzeeFrozenPlant.description>
  <RawGrungo.label>raw grungo</RawGrungo.label>
  <RawGrungo.description>Raw grungo. If you're not a Gerzee or an animal, eating this raw has a good chance of giving you food poisoning.</RawGrungo.description>
  <GerzeePowerArmor.description.description>A large suit of powered armor made to fit the Gerzee physique. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a Gerzee to wear this heavy armor and still move easily, while built-in cooling tech helps the wearer survive warfare in extremely hot climates. While bulky and heavy, the advanced servo-motors greatly increase the wearer's load bearing capacity and assist in weapon-handling.\n\nArmor like this is really only seen in warefare companies that attempt to alter Gerzee into viable soldiers.</GerzeePowerArmor.description.description>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.tools.0.label>center grip</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.tools.0.label>
  <Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.tools.1.label>head</Gerzee_Ram_MeleeWeapon.tools.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>