<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RN_MRE_USArmy.label>MRE US Army</RN_MRE_USArmy.label>
  <RN_MRE_USArmy.description>Meal Ready to Eat. A high-quality packaged meal, manufactured for use in survival situations. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside. Great for traveling.</RN_MRE_USArmy.description>
  <RNMedicine_IFAK_Multicam.label>IFAK</RNMedicine_IFAK_Multicam.label>
  <RNMedicine_IFAK_Multicam.description>Individual First Aid Kit. A kit of industrial-era medical equipment. It contains basic drugs, tools for suturing and bone setting, diagnostic devices, and various pads and fluids.</RNMedicine_IFAK_Multicam.description>
  <RNMedicine_MedicBag.label>medic bag</RNMedicine_MedicBag.label>
  <RNMedicine_MedicBag.description>A medic bag for paramedic use. A kit of industrial-era medical equipment. It contains basic drugs, tools for suturing and bone setting, diagnostic devices, various pads, various fluids and other specialist equipment for dealing with a variety of ailments.</RNMedicine_MedicBag.description>
  <RNApparel_CryeCAGE_141TaskForce.label>Crye CAGE body armor (141)</RNApparel_CryeCAGE_141TaskForce.label>
  <RNApparel_CryeCAGE_141TaskForce.description>The CAGE (CRYE ASSAULT GEAR) ARMOR CHASSIS, is the result of years of design and engineering.
	
Manufactured by Crye Precision, this plate carrier is fully modular and highly adjustable. The body armor system is compliant with the NIJ Ballistic Standards, top of the line made.</RNApparel_CryeCAGE_141TaskForce.description>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Breezy.label>MICH helmet Breezy</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Breezy.label>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Breezy.description>The Modular Integrated Communications Helmet (MICH) is a U.S. combat helmet and one of several used by the U.S. military. It was developed by the United States Army Soldier Systems Center to be the next generation of protective combat helmets for use by the U.S. Army.</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Breezy.description>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Roach.label>MICH helmet Roach</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Roach.label>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Roach.description>The Modular Integrated Communications Helmet (MICH) is a U.S. combat helmet and one of several used by the U.S. military. It was developed by the United States Army Soldier Systems Center to be the next generation of protective combat helmets for use by the U.S. Army.</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Roach.description>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Scarecrow.label>MICH helmet Scarecrow</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Scarecrow.label>
  <RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Scarecrow.description>The Modular Integrated Communications Helmet (MICH) is a U.S. combat helmet and one of several used by the U.S. military. It was developed by the United States Army Soldier Systems Center to be the next generation of protective combat helmets for use by the U.S. Army.</RNApparel_MICHHelmet_141Scarecrow.description>
  <RNApparel_Backpack_Tactical_DCU.label>asssault pack DCU</RNApparel_Backpack_Tactical_DCU.label>
  <RNApparel_Backpack_Tactical_DCU.description>A backpack for carrying things.. Tactically. Perfect for occassions where you can't help but show off the new kit to the third world tribals. 
	
Look, who cares if everyone is staring at the backpack? It's what you want. Being the "Gray man" is for nancies who can't afford this overpriced backpack, even if for some reason the military grade ones are cheaper.</RNApparel_Backpack_Tactical_DCU.description>
  <RNApparel_Harness_ALICE_DCU.label>webbing ALICE DCU</RNApparel_Harness_ALICE_DCU.label>
  <RNApparel_Harness_ALICE_DCU.description>The All-Purpose Lightweight Individual Carrying Equipment (ALICE) was a load bearing system adopted as United States Army Standard A on 17 January 1973 to replace the M-1956 Load-Carrying Equipment (LCE) and M-1967 Modernized Load-Carrying Equipment (MLCE).
	
ALICE gear has since been used in training only by the U.S. Military.</RNApparel_Harness_ALICE_DCU.description>
  <RNApparel_DCUBoonie.label>boonie hat DCU</RNApparel_DCUBoonie.label>
  <RNApparel_DCUBoonie.description>A boonie hat, also known as giggle hat, is a form of wide-brim hat commonly used by military forces. Its design is similar to a bucket hat but with a stiffer brim. Has DCU camo.</RNApparel_DCUBoonie.description>
  <RNApparel_Balaclava_Ghost.label>balaclava Ghost</RNApparel_Balaclava_Ghost.label>
  <RNApparel_Balaclava_Ghost.description>An artistically terrifying ghost balaclava. Hides the wearer's face and makes them more confident.</RNApparel_Balaclava_Ghost.description>
  <RNApparel_combats_141Fleece.description>Custom made combat fleece for Task Force 141 operators. Designed to be used for both Arctic and Desert conditions.
	
Has DCU combat trousers, it feels heavier than normal fleece jackets, and yet it's significantly lighter than a parka. Grey color fleece jacket.</RNApparel_combats_141Fleece.description>
  <RNApparel_combats_141Fleece.label>141 fleece</RNApparel_combats_141Fleece.label>
  <RNApparel_combats_141FleeceBlack.description>Custom made combat fleece for Task Force 141 operators. Designed to be used for both Arctic and Desert conditions. 
	
Has DCU combat trousers, it feels heavier than normal fleece jackets, and yet it's significantly lighter than a parka. Black color fleece jacket.</RNApparel_combats_141FleeceBlack.description>
  <RNApparel_combats_141FleeceBlack.label>141 fleece black</RNApparel_combats_141FleeceBlack.label>
  <RNApparel_combats_141FleeceOlive.description>Custom made combat fleece for Task Force 141 operators. Designed to be used for both Arctic and Desert conditions. 
	
Has DCU combat trousers, it feels heavier than normal fleece jackets, and yet it's significantly lighter than a parka. Olive color fleece jacket.</RNApparel_combats_141FleeceOlive.description>
  <RNApparel_combats_141FleeceOlive.label>141 fleece olive</RNApparel_combats_141FleeceOlive.label>
  <RN_BallisticKnife_Blade.label>ballistic knife blade</RN_BallisticKnife_Blade.label>
  <RNBullet_40SW_Pistol.label>.40 SW bullet</RNBullet_40SW_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45ACP_Pistol.label>.45 ACP bullet</RNBullet_45ACP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45ACPAP_Pistol.label>.45 ACP AP bullet</RNBullet_45ACPAP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MM_Pistol.label>9x19mm Parabellum bullet</RNBullet_9MM_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MMMakarov_Pistol.label>9x18mm Makarov bullet</RNBullet_9MMMakarov_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_9MMAP_Pistol.label>9x19mm Parabellum AP bullet</RNBullet_9MMAP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_46x30_Pistol.label>4.6x30mm bullet</RNBullet_46x30_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_57_Pistol.label>5.7x28mm bullet</RNBullet_57_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_50_Pistol.label>.50 bullet</RNBullet_50_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_762Tokarev_Pistol.label>7.62x25mm Tokarev Parabellum bullet</RNBullet_762Tokarev_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_762_Revolver.label>7.62x38mmR bullet</RNBullet_762_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_454_Revolver.label>.454 bullet</RNBullet_454_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_44Magnum_Pistol.label>.44 Magnum bullet</RNBullet_44Magnum_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_45Colt_Pistol.label>.45 Colt bullet</RNBullet_45Colt_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_38Special_Pistol.label>.38 bullet</RNBullet_38Special_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_357_Revolver.label>.357 bullet</RNBullet_357_Revolver.label>
  <RNBullet_545x39_Rifle.label>5.45x39mm bullet</RNBullet_545x39_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_AACBlackout_PDW.label>AAC blackout bullet</RNBullet_AACBlackout_PDW.label>
  <RNBullet_380_SMG.label>.380 bullet</RNBullet_380_SMG.label>
  <RNBullet_32ACP_Pistol.label>.32 ACP bullet</RNBullet_32ACP_Pistol.label>
  <RNBullet_12Gauge_Shotgun.label>shotgun blast</RNBullet_12Gauge_Shotgun.label>
  <RNBullet_23x75mmR_Shotgun.label>23x75mmR blast</RNBullet_23x75mmR_Shotgun.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_LMG.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_LMG.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_LMG.label>7.62x51mm NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_LMG.label>
  <RNBullet_762x39_Rifle.label>7.62x39R bullet</RNBullet_762x39_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_556x45_Rifle.label>5.56x45mm bullet</RNBullet_556x45_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_303British_Rifle.label> .303 British bullet</RNBullet_303British_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_Rifle.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_792x57Mauser_Rifle.label>8mm Mauser bullet</RNBullet_792x57Mauser_Rifle.label>
  <RNBullet_9x39mmSP6_DMR.label>9x39mm SP-6 bullet</RNBullet_9x39mmSP6_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_58x42mm_DMR.label>5.8x42mm bullet</RNBullet_58x42mm_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x39_DMR.label>7.62x39R bullet</RNBullet_762x39_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_DMR.label>7.62 NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_DMR.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_792x57Mauser_DMR.label>8mm Mauser bullet</RNBullet_792x57Mauser_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_308Winchester_DMR.label>.308 Winchester bullet</RNBullet_308Winchester_DMR.label>
  <RNBullet_762x51mm_Sniper.label>7.62 NATO bullet</RNBullet_762x51mm_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_308Winchester_Sniper.label>.308 Winchester bullet</RNBullet_308Winchester_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_338Lapua_Sniper.label>.338 Lapua Magnum bullet</RNBullet_338Lapua_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_762x54_Sniper.label>7.62x54mmR bullet</RNBullet_762x54_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_408Cheyenne_Sniper.label>.408 Cheyenne bullet</RNBullet_408Cheyenne_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_50BMG_Sniper.label>.50 BMG bullet</RNBullet_50BMG_Sniper.label>
  <RNBullet_127x108_Sniper.label>12.7x108mm bullet</RNBullet_127x108_Sniper.label>
  <RNEx_RPG7RL.label>RPG-7</RNEx_RPG7RL.label>
  <RNEx_RPG7RL.description>The RPG-7 (Russian: РПГ-7) is a portable, reusable, unguided, shoulder-launched, anti-tank rocket-propelled grenade launcher. Originally the RPG-7 (Ручной Противотанковый Гранатомёт – Ruchnoy Protivotankoviy Granatomyot – Hand-held anti-tank grenade launcher) and its predecessor, the RPG-2, were designed by the Soviet Union; it is now manufactured by the Russian company Bazalt. The weapon has the GRAU index (Russian armed forces index) 6G3.

The ruggedness, simplicity, low cost, and effectiveness of the RPG-7 has made it the most widely used anti-armor weapon in the world. It is re-usable.</RNEx_RPG7RL.description>
  <RNEx_RPG7RL.tools.0.label>barrel</RNEx_RPG7RL.tools.0.label>
  <RNBullet_RPG7Rocket.label>RPG-7 rocket</RNBullet_RPG7Rocket.label>
  <RNEx_M320GL.label>M320</RNEx_M320GL.label>
  <RNEx_M320GL.description>M320 Grenade Launcher Module (GLM) is the U.S. military's designation for a new single-shot 40 mm grenade launcher system to replace the M203 for the U.S. Army, while other services initially kept using the older M203. The M320 uses the same High-Low Propulsion System as the M203.</RNEx_M320GL.description>
  <RNEx_M320GL.tools.0.label>barrel</RNEx_M320GL.tools.0.label>
  <RNBullet_40mmGrenade.label>40x46mm grenade round</RNBullet_40mmGrenade.label>
  <RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.label>MP5A2 HRT</RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.label>
  <RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.description>The MP5 (German: Maschinenpistole 5) is a 9mm submachine gun, developed in the 1960s by a team of engineers from the German small arms manufacturer Heckler and Koch GmbH (HK) of Oberndorf am Neckar. There are over 100 variants of the MP5, including some semi-automatic versions.

The MP5 is one of the most widely used submachine guns in the world, having been adopted by 40 nations and numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence, and security organizations. It is widely used by SWAT teams in North America.

In 1999, Heckler and Koch developed the Heckler and Koch UMP, the MP5's successor</RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.description>
  <RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.tools.0.label>grip</RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_MP5A2SDHRT_PDW.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.label>UMP45 HRT</RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.label>
  <RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.description>The Heckler and Koch UMP (Universale Maschinenpistole, German for "Universal Submachine Gun") is a submachine gun developed and manufactured by Heckler and Koch. The UMP has been adopted by various agencies such as the U.S. Customs and Border Protection. Heckler and Koch developed the UMP as a lighter and cheaper successor to the MP5, though both remain in production.</RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.description>
  <RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.tools.0.label>grip</RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_UMP45HRT_PDW.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_G36CHRT.label>G36C HRT</RNGun_G36CHRT.label>
  <RNGun_G36CHRT.description>The G36 is a 5.56×45mm assault rifle, designed in the early 1990s by Heckler anf Koch in Germany as a replacement for the heavier 7.62mm G3 battle rifle.
	
It was accepted into service with the Bundeswehr in 1997, replacing the G3.</RNGun_G36CHRT.description>
  <RNGun_G36CHRT.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_G36CHRT.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_G36CHRT.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_G36CHRT.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M240B.label>M240B</RNGun_M240B.label>
  <RNGun_M240B.description>The M240, officially the Machine Gun, 7.62 mm, M240, is the US military designation for the FN MAG ("Mitrailleuse A Gaz" = Gas operated machine gun; alternatively, "Mitrailleuse d'Appui General" = machine gun, support, general) a family of belt-fed, gas-operated medium machine guns that chamber the 7.62×51mm NATO cartridge.</RNGun_M240B.description>
  <RNGun_M240B.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M240B.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M240B.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M240B.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_MK48LMG.label>Mk 48</RNGun_MK48LMG.label>
  <RNGun_MK48LMG.description>The Mark 48, or Mk 48 is a lightweight belt-fed machine gun, firing 7.62×51mm NATO cartridges from a disintegrating belt of ammunition.

It is manufactured by Fabrique Nationale Manufacturing, Inc., a division of FN Herstal based in the United States. The Mk 48 has been developed in conjunction with the U.S. Special Operations Command (USSOCOM), which has adopted the weapon and started its fielding process, beginning with special operations units.</RNGun_MK48LMG.description>
  <RNGun_MK48LMG.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_MK48LMG.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_MK48LMG.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_MK48LMG.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_RPD.label>RPD</RNGun_RPD.label>
  <RNGun_RPD.description>The RPD (Russian: ручной пулемёт Дегтярёва Ruchnoy Pulemyot Degtyaryova, English: Degtyaryov hand-held machine gun) is a 7.62mm light machine gun developed in the Soviet Union by Vasily Degtyaryov for the 7.62×39mm M43 intermediate cartridge.</RNGun_RPD.description>
  <RNGun_RPD.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_RPD.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_RPD.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_RPD.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_PKMLMG.label>PKM</RNGun_PKMLMG.label>
  <RNGun_PKMLMG.description>The PK (Russian: Пулемёт Калашникова, or "Kalashnikov's Machinegun"), is a 7.62x54mmR general-purpose machine gun designed in the Soviet Union and currently in production in Russia.

The original PK was a development of Kalashnikov's AKM assault rifle and the accompanying RPK light machine gun design that featured stamped receivers. The PK uses the 7.62x54mmR Eastern Bloc standard cartridge.</RNGun_PKMLMG.description>
  <RNGun_PKMLMG.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_PKMLMG.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_PKMLMG.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_PKMLMG.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_InterventionSn.label>Intervention</RNGun_InterventionSn.label>
  <RNGun_InterventionSn.description>The CheyTac Intervention is an American bolt-action sniper rifle manufactured by CheyTac LLC, which can also be classified as an anti-materiel rifle. It is fed by a 7-round detachable single-stack magazine (an optional 5-round magazine is also available). 
	
It is specifically chambered in either .408 Chey Tac or .375 Chey Tac ammunition.</RNGun_InterventionSn.description>
  <RNGun_InterventionSn.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_InterventionSn.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_InterventionSn.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_InterventionSn.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_TAC50Sn.label>TAC-50</RNGun_TAC50Sn.label>
  <RNGun_TAC50Sn.description>The McMillan TAC-50 is a long-range anti-materiel and anti-personnel sniper rifle. The TAC-50 is based on previous designs from the same company, which first appeared during the late 1980s. 
	
McMillan makes several versions of .50 caliber rifles, based on the same proprietary action, for military, law enforcement and civilian use.</RNGun_TAC50Sn.description>
  <RNGun_TAC50Sn.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_TAC50Sn.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_TAC50Sn.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_TAC50Sn.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M107AMR.label>M107</RNGun_M107AMR.label>
  <RNGun_M107AMR.description>The Barrett M82, standardized by the U.S. military as the M107, is a recoil-operated, semi-automatic anti-materiel sniper system developed by the American Barrett Firearms Manufacturing company. Despite its designation as an anti-materiel rifle, it is used by some armed forces as an anti-personnel system. 
	
It is also called the Light Fifty for its .50 BMG (12.7×99mm NATO) chambering and significantly lighter weight compared to previous applications.</RNGun_M107AMR.description>
  <RNGun_M107AMR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M107AMR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M107AMR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M107AMR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M14EBR.label>M14 EBR</RNGun_M14EBR.label>
  <RNGun_M14EBR.description>The M14 rifle, officially the United States Rifle, 7.62 mm, M14, is an American automatic rifle that fires 7.62×51mm NATO (.308 in) ammunition. 
	
It became the standard-issued rifle for the U.S. military in 1959 replacing the M1 Garand rifle in the U.S. Army by 1961 and the U.S. Marine Corps by 1965 until being replaced by the M16 rifle beginning in 1964.</RNGun_M14EBR.description>
  <RNGun_M14EBR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M14EBR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M14EBR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M14EBR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M39EMR.label>M39 EMR</RNGun_M39EMR.label>
  <RNGun_M39EMR.description>The M39 Enhanced Marksman Rifle is a semi-automatic, gas-operated designated marksman rifle chambered for the 7.62×51mm NATO cartridge. It is a modified and accurized version of the M14 rifle used by the United States military, in a similar vein to the Mk 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle. It is based on the United States Marine Corps Designated Marksman Rifle (DMR), which it replaced. 
	
It is manufactured by Sage International and maintained by the USMC's Precision Weapons Section.</RNGun_M39EMR.description>
  <RNGun_M39EMR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M39EMR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M39EMR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M39EMR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M110SASSDMR.label>M110 SASS</RNGun_M110SASSDMR.label>
  <RNGun_M110SASSDMR.description>The M110 Semi Automatic Sniper System (M110 SASS) is an American semi-automatic sniper rifle/designated marksman rifle that is chambered for the 7.62×51mm NATO round, developed by U.S. firearm manufacturer Knight's Armament Company.
	
The M110 Semi-Automatic Sniper System is intended to replace the M24 Sniper Weapon System used by snipers, spotters, designated marksman, or squad advanced marksmen in the United States Army. However, the U.S. Army still acquired M24s from Remington until February 2010.</RNGun_M110SASSDMR.description>
  <RNGun_M110SASSDMR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M110SASSDMR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M110SASSDMR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M110SASSDMR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_AK47ModernAR.label>AK47 Tactical</RNGun_AK47ModernAR.label>
  <RNGun_AK47ModernAR.description>The AK-47, AK, or as it is officially known (Russian: Автома́т Кала́шникова, tr. Avtomát Kaláshnikova, lit. Kalashnikov's Automatic Rifle), also known as the Kalashnikov, is a gas-operated, 7.62×39mm assault rifle, developed in the Soviet Union by Mikhail Kalashnikov. 
	
It is the originating firearm of the Kalashnikov rifle (or "AK") family.</RNGun_AK47ModernAR.description>
  <RNGun_AK47ModernAR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_AK47ModernAR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_AK47ModernAR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_AK47ModernAR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.label>AKM Tactical</RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.label>
  <RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.description>The AKM (Russian: модернизи́рованный Автома́т Кала́шникова, tr. modernizírovanny Avtomát Kaláshnikova, lit. Modernized Kalashnikov Automatic Rifle) is a 7.62mm assault rifle designed by Mikhail Kalashnikov. It is a common modernized variant of the AK-47 rifle developed in the 1940s.

Introduced into service with the Soviet Army in 1959, the AKM is the most ubiquitous variant of the entire AK series of firearms and it has found widespread use with most member states of the former Warsaw Pact and its African and Asian allies as well as being widely exported and produced in many other countries.

It was officially replaced in Soviet frontline service by the AK-74 in the late 1970s, but remains in use worldwide.</RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.description>
  <RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_AKMTacticalAR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.label>M4A1 MIL-SPEC</RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1MilSpec.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.label>M4A1 Benghazi</RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1Benghazi.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Ghost.label>M4A1 Ghost</RNGun_M4A1Ghost.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Ghost.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1Ghost.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1Ghost.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1Ghost.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Ghost.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1Ghost.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.label>M4A1 Fallujah</RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1Fallujah.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.label>M4A1 Warfighter</RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1Warfighter.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.label>M4A1 Roach</RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.description>The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock.

The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle.</RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.description>
  <RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M4A1RoachAR.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_AA12S.label>AA-12</RNGun_AA12S.label>
  <RNGun_AA12S.description>The Auto Assault-12 (AA-12), originally designed and known as the Atchisson Assault Shotgun, is a shotgun developed in 1972 by Maxwell Atchisson. The most prominent feature is reduced recoil. The current 2005 version has been developed over 18 years since the patent was sold to Military Police Systems, Inc. The original design was the basis of several later weapons, including the USAS-12 combat shotgun. The weapon is fully automatic only. However, it fires at a rate of 300 rounds per minute, allowing it to fire one round at a time with brief trigger pulls. It is fed from either an 8-shell box magazine, or a 20- or 32-shell drum magazine.</RNGun_AA12S.description>
  <RNGun_AA12S.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_AA12S.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_AA12S.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_AA12S.tools.1.label>
  <RNGun_M1014S.label>M1014</RNGun_M1014S.label>
  <RNGun_M1014S.description>The Benelli M4 Super 90 is an Italian semi-automatic shotgun manufactured by Benelli Armi SpA.

On May 4, 1998, the United States Army's Armaments Research, Development and Engineering Center (ARDEC) at Picatinny Arsenal, New Jersey issued Solicitation #DAAE30-98-R-0401, requesting submissions for a new 12 gauge, semi-automatic combat shotgun for the U.S. military. In response to the request, Benelli Armi SpA of Urbino, Italy designed and built the Benelli M4 Super 90 Combat Shotgun. On August 4, 1998, five samples of the M4 were delivered to Aberdeen Proving Ground, Maryland, and after intense testing, the M4 had beaten the competition. In early 1999, ARDEC awarded the M1014 Joint Service Combat Shotgun contract to Heckler and Koch, American subsidiary for importation of the Benelli M4 Combat Shotgun. The first units (count of 20,000) were delivered to the United States Marine Corps in 1999. During testing, the prototype was named XM1014, but after adoption, the 'X' was dropped, and the weapon was officially designated the M1014.

"Palms are sweaty, knees weak, mom's Benelli." - Spaghetti rapper</RNGun_M1014S.description>
  <RNGun_M1014S.tools.0.label>stock</RNGun_M1014S.tools.0.label>
  <RNGun_M1014S.tools.1.label>barrel</RNGun_M1014S.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>