<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AdvancedMedicalStation.label>advanced medical station</AdvancedMedicalStation.label>
  <AdvancedMedicalStation.description>A medical station equipped with cutting-edge precision tools and computers for the production of advanced bionics, synthetic organs and brain implants.</AdvancedMedicalStation.description>
  <BionicWorkbench.label>bionic workbench</BionicWorkbench.label>
  <BionicWorkbench.description>A workbench equipped with precision tools for the production of high tech bionic parts.</BionicWorkbench.description>
  <AdvancedPowerArm.label>advanced power arm</AdvancedPowerArm.label>
  <AdvancedPowerArm.description>An upgraded artificial power arm. Highly lethal and effective in combat.\n\nDo not install on an unstable subject, as this might cause unwanted death and destruction.</AdvancedPowerArm.description>
  <AdvancedBionicHand.label>advanced bionic hand</AdvancedBionicHand.label>
  <AdvancedBionicHand.description>An upgraded bionic hand. Some people would chop their own hands off just to get this gorgeous piece of tech.</AdvancedBionicHand.description>
  <AdvancedBionicArm.label>advanced bionic arm</AdvancedBionicArm.label>
  <AdvancedBionicArm.description>An upgraded bionic arm. Remember when you struggled with opening jars? Now you will struggle to not break them instantly.</AdvancedBionicArm.description>
  <AdvancedBionicLeg.label>advanced bionic leg</AdvancedBionicLeg.label>
  <AdvancedBionicLeg.description>An upgraded bionic leg. Impressive technology which allows the user to move around faster than ever.</AdvancedBionicLeg.description>
  <AdvancedBionicFoot.label>advanced bionic foot</AdvancedBionicFoot.label>
  <AdvancedBionicFoot.description>An upgraded bionic foot. Dozens of servomotors grant faster movement and ultimate comfort.</AdvancedBionicFoot.description>
  <AdvancedBionicEar.label>advanced bionic ear</AdvancedBionicEar.label>
  <AdvancedBionicEar.description>An upgraded bionic ear. This device allows the user to hear better than bats.</AdvancedBionicEar.description>
  <AdvancedBionicSpine.label>advanced bionic spine</AdvancedBionicSpine.label>
  <AdvancedBionicSpine.description>An upgraded bionic spine. This durable device makes the user extremely mobile and flexible.</AdvancedBionicSpine.description>
  <ExoskeletonSuit.label>exoskeleton suit</ExoskeletonSuit.label>
  <ExoskeletonSuit.description>A high tech device made out of two components: a light skeletal structure and servomotors to make the user faster and stronger.</ExoskeletonSuit.description>
  <AdvancedBionicEye.label>advanced bionic eye</AdvancedBionicEye.label>
  <AdvancedBionicEye.description>An upgraded bionic eye.This advanced piece of technology allows the user to see perfectly in the dark as well as to see through walls.</AdvancedBionicEye.description>
  <BionicEye.label>bionic eye</BionicEye.label>
  <BionicEye.description>An advanced artifical eye. With its biogel nerve-link, internal signal pre-processor, and wide-spectrum sensors, it is better than a biological eye in almost every way. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage.</BionicEye.description>
  <BionicEar.label>bionic ear</BionicEar.label>
  <BionicEar.description>An advanced artificial ear implant. A collection of invisible subdermal microphones capture sound and transmit it to a biogel nerve interface that links directly with the auditory nerve. It's sensitive enough to hear a cat before you see it, can't be damaged by loud noise, and automatically tunes itself to pick out meaningful sounds in noisy environments.</BionicEar.description>
  <BionicArm.label>bionic arm</BionicArm.label>
  <BionicArm.description>An advanced artificial arm. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological arm in almost every way.</BionicArm.description>
  <BionicLeg.label>bionic leg</BionicLeg.label>
  <BionicLeg.description>An advanced artificial leg. With its biogel nerve-link, powerful mini-servos, and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological leg in almost every way.</BionicLeg.description>
  <BionicSpine.label>bionic spine</BionicSpine.label>
  <BionicSpine.description>An advanced artificial spine. A biogel nerve bundle runs down an articulated plasteel core, surrounded by a lattice-dust healing system. Outperforms biological spines.</BionicSpine.description>
  <PowerArm.label>power arm</PowerArm.label>
  <PowerArm.description>An advanced artificial power arm. Lethal and effective in combat.\n\nDo not install on an unstable subject, as this might cause unwanted death and destruction.</PowerArm.description>
  <BionicHand.label>bionic hand</BionicHand.label>
  <BionicHand.description>Allows the user to perform tasks even faster than with regular hands.</BionicHand.description>
  <BionicFoot.label>bionic foot</BionicFoot.label>
  <BionicFoot.description>This prosthesis grants faster walking with little to no stumbling !.</BionicFoot.description>
  <BionicJaw.label>bionic jaw</BionicJaw.label>
  <BionicJaw.description>Aside from a strong set of teeth, this also comes with a voice modulator.</BionicJaw.description>
  <BionicHeart.label>n/a</BionicHeart.label>
  <BionicHeart.description>inactive</BionicHeart.description>
  <BionicStomach.label>n/a</BionicStomach.label>
  <BionicStomach.description>inactive</BionicStomach.description>
  <SimpleProstheticHeart.label>n/a</SimpleProstheticHeart.label>
  <SimpleProstheticHeart.description>inactive</SimpleProstheticHeart.description>
  <Stomach.label>stomach</Stomach.label>
  <Stomach.description>Digests food and turns it into energy and nutrients. Needs refrigeration.</Stomach.description>
  <Heart.label>heart</Heart.label>
  <Heart.description>Supplies blood and oxygen to all parts of the body. Ready to find a new owner. Needs refrigeration.</Heart.description>
  <Liver.label>liver</Liver.label>
  <Liver.description>Plays an important role in metabolism and filtration. Needs refrigeration.</Liver.description>
  <Lung.label>lung</Lung.label>
  <Lung.description>Essential part of the respiratory system. Needs refrigeration.</Lung.description>
  <Kidney.label>kidney</Kidney.label>
  <Kidney.description>Filters and removes waste products from the blood. Needs refrigeration.</Kidney.description>
  <ArtificialBone.label>artificial bone</ArtificialBone.label>
  <ArtificialBone.description>Replaces destroyed bones.</ArtificialBone.description>
  <ArtificialNose.label>artificial nose</ArtificialNose.label>
  <ArtificialNose.description>Replaces a missing nose. Covers the hole in the face.</ArtificialNose.description>
  <SimpleProstheticLeg.label>simple prosthetic leg</SimpleProstheticLeg.label>
  <SimpleProstheticLeg.description>A leg prosthesis. While it lacks a neutral interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real leg.</SimpleProstheticLeg.description>
  <SimpleProstheticArm.label>simple prosthetic arm</SimpleProstheticArm.label>
  <SimpleProstheticArm.description>An arm prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real arm.</SimpleProstheticArm.description>
  <CochlearImplant.label>cochlear implant</CochlearImplant.label>
  <CochlearImplant.description>An implant which replaces normal hearing. An external microphone transmits a sound signal to electrodes wrapped around the inner ear's auditory sensing nerves. The electrodes stimulate the nerves according to the sound, creating a sensation of hearing. It's not as good as a natural ear, but it's a lot better than being deaf.</CochlearImplant.description>
  <SimpleProstheticHand.label>simple prosthetic hand</SimpleProstheticHand.label>
  <SimpleProstheticHand.description>Replaces missing hands. Way more comfortable and less frightening than a hook hand.</SimpleProstheticHand.description>
  <SimpleProstheticFoot.label>simple prosthetic foot</SimpleProstheticFoot.label>
  <SimpleProstheticFoot.description>Replaces missing feet.</SimpleProstheticFoot.description>
  <ArtificialPelvis.label>artificial pelvis</ArtificialPelvis.label>
  <ArtificialPelvis.description>Replaces a missing pelvis. Pretty useful if crawling is not your favourite kind of moving around.</ArtificialPelvis.description>
  <Neurostimulator.label>neurostimulator</Neurostimulator.label>
  <Neurostimulator.description>Highly advanced brain implant that attempts to enhance the consciousness of the subject. Comes with numerous side effects like headaches and loss of language.\n\nSome personality changes may occur. Only recommended for brain damaged colonists.</Neurostimulator.description>
  <Hyporegulator.label>hyporegulator</Hyporegulator.label>
  <Hyporegulator.description>Highly advanced brain implant that attempts to enhance the mental and physical resilience of the subject. The implant is placed into the hypothalamus which increases the effectiveness of the HPA axis and the body's thermoregulation.</Hyporegulator.description>
  <Cortexaugmentor.label>cortexaugmentor</Cortexaugmentor.label>
  <Cortexaugmentor.description>Highly advanced brain implant that attempts to enhance the general intelligence of the subject. The implant is placed into the prefrontal cortex which increases cognitive abilities such as language and learning speed.</Cortexaugmentor.description>
  <SyntheticLung.label>synthetic lung</SyntheticLung.label>
  <SyntheticLung.description>An enhanced lung augmented with nanocells to increase organ efficiency and durability. Should be kept frozen outside of the body to avoid cell death and organ failure.\n\nDoes not trigger transplant rejection.\n\nStats:\nBreathing: 20%\nMoving: 5%</SyntheticLung.description>
  <SyntheticLiver.label>synthetic liver</SyntheticLiver.label>
  <SyntheticLiver.description>An enhanced liver augmented with nanocells to increase organ efficiency and durability. Should be kept frozen outside of the body to avoid cell death and organ failure.\n\nDoes not trigger transplant rejection.\n\nStats:\nBlood filtration: 20%</SyntheticLiver.description>
  <SyntheticKidney.label>synthetic kidney</SyntheticKidney.label>
  <SyntheticKidney.description>An enhanced kidney augmented with nanocells to increase organ efficiency and durability. Should be kept frozen outside of the body to avoid cell death and organ failure.\n\nDoes not trigger transplant rejection.\n\nStats:\nBlood filtration: 20%</SyntheticKidney.description>
  <SyntheticHeart.label>synthetic heart</SyntheticHeart.label>
  <SyntheticHeart.description>An enhanced heart augmented with nanocells to increase organ efficiency and durability. Should be kept frozen outside of the body to avoid cell death and organ failure.\n\nDoes not trigger transplant rejection.\n\nStats:\nBlood pumping: 20%\nMoving: 10%\nManipulation: 10%</SyntheticHeart.description>
  <SyntheticStomach.label>synthetic stomach</SyntheticStomach.label>
  <SyntheticStomach.description>An enhanced stomach augmented with nanocells to increase organ efficiency and durability. Should be kept frozen outside of the body to avoid cell death and organ failure.\n\nDoes not trigger transplant rejection.\n\nStats:\nMetabolism: 25%</SyntheticStomach.description>
  <Joywire.label>joywire</Joywire.label>
  <Joywire.description>This little brain implant will make you feel happy and relaxed. Requires neuroscience research before installing.</Joywire.description>
  <Painstopper.label>painstopper</Painstopper.label>
  <Painstopper.description>This brain implant will make you not feel pain. Requires neuroscience research before installing.</Painstopper.description>
  <ArchotechEye.label>archotech eye</ArchotechEye.label>
  <ArchotechEye.description>An artifical eye built by an archotech. It perceives every type of electromagnetic radiation, including radio waves, infrared, light, x-rays, and gamma rays. Its visual acuity is precise enough to read handwriting from twenty meters away. It can emit various wavelengths of radiation like a flashlight, and has an internal subpersona AI which helps highlight useful visual information. Externally, it looks like a natural human eye, except it can change color at will. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechEye.description>
  <ArchotechArm.label>archotech arm</ArchotechArm.label>
  <ArchotechArm.description>An artifical arm built by an archotech. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechArm.description>
  <ArchotechLeg.label>archotech leg</ArchotechLeg.label>
  <ArchotechLeg.description>An artifical leg built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but a pair of these can move the user as fast as a decent car, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLeg.description>
  <UnfinishedProsthesis.label>unfinished prosthesis</UnfinishedProsthesis.label>
</LanguageData>