<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Upgrade_TechprofAIModule.label>Techprof Module</Upgrade_TechprofAIModule.label>
  <Upgrade_TechprofAIModule.description>Installs a secondary AI which greatly increases the research capabilities of the Android.\n-- "Two brains is better than one."</Upgrade_TechprofAIModule.description>
  <Upgrade_ArchotechAIModule.label>Archotech Module</Upgrade_ArchotechAIModule.label>
  <Upgrade_ArchotechAIModule.description>Replaces the standard AI of the Android with a Archotech one. Considered dangerous by many this can be a boon though. With superior intellectual capabilities everything seem to come natural to the Android with this brain.\n-- "Ascension complete."</Upgrade_ArchotechAIModule.description>
  <Upgrade_DroneCore.label>Drone Mentality</Upgrade_DroneCore.label>
  <Upgrade_DroneCore.description>Turns the Android almost completely into a drone. Their capability to learn is greatly lowered and they are not affected by mood so much.\n-- "Ignorance is bliss."</Upgrade_DroneCore.description>
  <Upgrade_LoverCore.label>Lover Mentality</Upgrade_LoverCore.label>
  <Upgrade_LoverCore.description>Turns the Android into a love slave. They will spend the majority of their time looking for a relationship, and you can force them to love someone. Unfortunately this got the side effect that capability to work and learn suffers.\n-- "Re: Immortal Lover."</Upgrade_LoverCore.description>
  <Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.0>Pleasure model</Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.0>
  <Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.1>Bishojo android</Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.1>
  <Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.2>Courtesan</Upgrade_LoverCore.spawnInBackstories.2>
  <Upgrade_HulkPhysique.label>Hulk Physique</Upgrade_HulkPhysique.label>
  <Upgrade_HulkPhysique.description>Gives the Android an hulking and strong physique. The Android is now better at physically demanding tasks.\n-- "Hulk smash!"</Upgrade_HulkPhysique.description>
  <Upgrade_AgilePhysique.label>Agile Physique</Upgrade_AgilePhysique.label>
  <Upgrade_AgilePhysique.description>Gives the Android an thin and agile physique. The Android is now faster and better at dodging.\n-- "Orassan go nyoom!"</Upgrade_AgilePhysique.description>
  <Upgrade_SuperPhysique.label>Perfect Physique</Upgrade_SuperPhysique.label>
  <Upgrade_SuperPhysique.description>Gives the Android an perfect physique. Bringing the best of both the agile and hulking phyisque together. The Android is now superior at everything physical.\n-- "I am now perfect."</Upgrade_SuperPhysique.description>
  <Upgrade_FightingModule.label>Fighting Module</Upgrade_FightingModule.label>
  <Upgrade_FightingModule.description>This module is utilized mostly by soldier Androids on glitterworlds. It enhances the combat capabilities of the user way beyond human limits.\n-- "The way of the warrior."</Upgrade_FightingModule.description>
  <Upgrade_FightingModule.spawnInBackstories.0>Broken android</Upgrade_FightingModule.spawnInBackstories.0>
  <Upgrade_MedicalModule.label>Medical Module</Upgrade_MedicalModule.label>
  <Upgrade_MedicalModule.description>This module is designed for Androids who accompany glitterworld parties offworld. Contains the most cutting edge doctoring software and micro implants to help with first aid and surgery.\n-- "Hello nurse~"</Upgrade_MedicalModule.description>
  <Upgrade_ConstructionModule.label>Construction Module</Upgrade_ConstructionModule.label>
  <Upgrade_ConstructionModule.description>Designed for new colonies this module greatly help settlers to setup their new dwellings. Whether inside a mountain or atop a skyscraper this module helps.\n-- "Can we fix it?"</Upgrade_ConstructionModule.description>
  <Upgrade_CrafterModule.label>Craftmanship Module</Upgrade_CrafterModule.label>
  <Upgrade_CrafterModule.description>Helps the Android to craft and cook much faster than their unupgraded kin. Used in premium crafter Android models in artisan workshops.\n-- "Mine and craft."</Upgrade_CrafterModule.description>
  <Upgrade_AgriculturalModule.label>Agricultural Module</Upgrade_AgriculturalModule.label>
  <Upgrade_AgriculturalModule.description>Outfitted with the latest plant and animal farming software this module with the help of a few menial laborers can run a farm on their own. Widely utilized by new glitterworld colonies.\n-- "Old MacDonald had a farm~"</Upgrade_AgriculturalModule.description>
  <Upgrade_ScienceModule.label>Science Module</Upgrade_ScienceModule.label>
  <Upgrade_ScienceModule.description>Augments the Androids reasoning and problem solving abilities beyond human comprehension. Installed on assistant laboratory Androids on glitterworlds all over the galaxy.\n-- "Big day today, Freeman."</Upgrade_ScienceModule.description>
  <Upgrade_DiplomacyModule.label>Diplomacy Module</Upgrade_DiplomacyModule.label>
  <Upgrade_DiplomacyModule.description>Gives the Android diplomatic and trading capabilities that seem supernatural. Widely installed on Androids who work on defusing hostage situations.\n-- "My name is Connor. I’m the android sent by CyberLife."</Upgrade_DiplomacyModule.description>
  <Upgrade_HyperweaveSkin.label>Hyperweave Skin</Upgrade_HyperweaveSkin.label>
  <Upgrade_HyperweaveSkin.description>Gives the Android a skin made out of hyperweave supported by mechanites that help mend it. Grants increased resistances to physical damage.\n-- "The future is now."</Upgrade_HyperweaveSkin.description>
  <Upgrade_PlasteelSkin.label>Plasteel Skin</Upgrade_PlasteelSkin.label>
  <Upgrade_PlasteelSkin.description>Gives the Android a skin made out of plasteel supported by mechanites that help mend it. Grants greatly increased resistances to physical damage. Makes them less desirable socially though.\n-- "I'll be back."</Upgrade_PlasteelSkin.description>
  <Upgrade_DragonScales.label>Dragon scales</Upgrade_DragonScales.label>
  <Upgrade_DragonScales.description>Augments the Androids skin with fantastical scales, and a network under the skin with a highly sophisticated cooling system that keeps the Android cool even under the most extreme high temperatures. Makes the Android nigh immune to fire and burn damage on top of increased armor.\n-- "Fuck you I'm a dragon."</Upgrade_DragonScales.description>
  <Upgrade_VanometricCell.label>Vanometric Cell</Upgrade_VanometricCell.label>
  <Upgrade_VanometricCell.description>Miniature version of the Vanometric Powercell. When installed it frees the Android of the need for both energy and food. Truly the ultimate upgrade.\n-- "Power Overwhelming."</Upgrade_VanometricCell.description>
  <Upgrade_MechaniteHive.label>Mechanite Hive</Upgrade_MechaniteHive.label>
  <Upgrade_MechaniteHive.description>Thumb sized devices placed throughout the body containing self maintaining factories of mechanites. Acts much like human blood when its exposed to the air and plugs any holes it detects.\n-- "I feel nothing!"</Upgrade_MechaniteHive.description>
  <Upgrade_BlackBox.label>Black Box</Upgrade_BlackBox.label>
  <Upgrade_BlackBox.description>Usually installed in recon Androids which it is critical in that they do not get leave witnesses when critically wounded. Probably the ultimate retribution tool there is.\n-- "I'm taking you all with me!"</Upgrade_BlackBox.description>
  <Upgrade_BlackBox.spawnInBackstories.0>Undercover spy</Upgrade_BlackBox.spawnInBackstories.0>
  <Upgrade_PsychicAttunement.label>Psychic Attunement</Upgrade_PsychicAttunement.label>
  <Upgrade_PsychicAttunement.description>By utilizing a material which got the opposite effect of psychic foil so can the mind and body of the android become a attractor for psionic forces. Why you would want to do this without the presence of fantastical forces like Magic on the RimWorld is beyond many scientists.\n-- "I only need my mind to take you down."</Upgrade_PsychicAttunement.description>
</LanguageData>