<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <HomeworldChildAG.title>Homeworlder</HomeworldChildAG.title>
  <HomeworldChildAG.titleShort>Homeworlder</HomeworldChildAG.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildAG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on the Gerzee homeworld with the typical life of foraging for food, running from predators, and spending time with the family who survived those predators.</HomeworldChildAG.baseDescription>
  <HomeworldChildPlanterG.title>Homeworld Planter</HomeworldChildPlanterG.title>
  <HomeworldChildPlanterG.titleShort>Homeworld Planter</HomeworldChildPlanterG.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildPlanterG.baseDescription>While every child in the Gerzee homeworld forages for food to survive, [PAWN_nameDef] always had a special talent for finding the plants with the sweetest fruit. [PAWN_pronoun] even grew a few plant outside their [PAWN_objective] burrow, something most Gerzee don't figure out until adulthood.</HomeworldChildPlanterG.baseDescription>
  <HomeworldChildSentryG.title>Homeworlder Sentry</HomeworldChildSentryG.title>
  <HomeworldChildSentryG.titleShort>Homeworlder Sentry</HomeworldChildSentryG.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildSentryG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was usually a sentry whenever [PAWN_possessive] family foraged for food. [PAWN_pronoun] may not have learned as much about plants as the other children, but it did give [PAWN_objective] some unique opportunities to learn about the animals around them.</HomeworldChildSentryG.baseDescription>
  <HomeworldChildKind.title>Kind Homeworlder</HomeworldChildKind.title>
  <HomeworldChildKind.titleShort>Kind Homeworlder</HomeworldChildKind.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildKind.baseDescription>While Gerzee don't focus too much on the individual, [PAWN_nameDef] stood out for being an especially caring child. This made them very likeable to the entire herd.</HomeworldChildKind.baseDescription>
  <HaulerChildSlaveG.title>Hauler Child Slave</HaulerChildSlaveG.title>
  <HaulerChildSlaveG.titleShort>Hauler Child</HaulerChildSlaveG.titleShort>
  <HaulerChildSlaveG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured by slavers as a young child and put to work with carrying smaller cargo, as they were still too small for most other jobs.</HaulerChildSlaveG.baseDescription>
  <TransportChildG.title>Transport Child</TransportChildG.title>
  <TransportChildG.titleShort>Transport Child</TransportChildG.titleShort>
  <TransportChildG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured by slavers as a child, left to grow into adult size on the ship as the slavers crypto-slept through the long journey. Not having much to do but talk to the other young Gerzee, [PAWN_nameDef] never really learned the ways of their people.</TransportChildG.baseDescription>
  <LonelyTransportChildG.title>Lonely Transport Child</LonelyTransportChildG.title>
  <LonelyTransportChildG.titleShort>Lonely Child</LonelyTransportChildG.titleShort>
  <LonelyTransportChildG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured by slavers as a child, left alone to grow into adult size on the ship as the slavers slept in their cryptosleep caskets. The lack of social interaction for so long left [PAWN_nameDef] a little... odd.</LonelyTransportChildG.baseDescription>
  <AggressiveChildG.title>Aggressive Child</AggressiveChildG.title>
  <AggressiveChildG.titleShort>Aggressive Child</AggressiveChildG.titleShort>
  <AggressiveChildG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was one of the rare Gerzee to have aggressive tendencies. Normally such Gerzee children die off quickly, as the great beasts of the Gerzee homeworld tend to catch the ones not running away in complete fear. Both fortunately and unfortunately for [PAWN_nameDef], they were caught by slavers, who wouldn't waste money by killing off their slave inventory.</AggressiveChildG.baseDescription>
  <GiftedChildG.title>Gifted Child</GiftedChildG.title>
  <GiftedChildG.titleShort>Gifted Child</GiftedChildG.titleShort>
  <GiftedChildG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was unusually intelligent for their species, having the potential to learn things most Gerzee simply couldn't grasp. This went unnoticed during their childhood, since most of their time was spent running from predators.</GiftedChildG.baseDescription>
  <FearfulChildG.title>Fearful Child</FearfulChildG.title>
  <FearfulChildG.titleShort>Fearful Child</FearfulChildG.titleShort>
  <FearfulChildG.baseDescription>While all Gerzee have the experience of running from their lives from massive predators, [PAWN_nameDef] always seemed to be the one to run into them first. This left [PAWN_nameDef] a bit edgy compared to most other Gerzee.</FearfulChildG.baseDescription>
  <HomeworldChildNightSentryG.title>Homeworlder Night Sentry</HomeworldChildNightSentryG.title>
  <HomeworldChildNightSentryG.titleShort>Night Sentry</HomeworldChildNightSentryG.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildNightSentryG.baseDescription>A Gerzee that sleeps better during the day is considered quite important to a Gerzee herd, as they are best at watching over the herd while they sleep at night. [PAWN_nameDef] was discovered to be one of these night Gerzee, and spent most of their time helping the adults keep watch over the herd.</HomeworldChildNightSentryG.baseDescription>
  <HomeworldChildDumbG.title>Slow Homeworlder</HomeworldChildDumbG.title>
  <HomeworldChildDumbG.titleShort>Slow Homeworlder</HomeworldChildDumbG.titleShort>
  <HomeworldChildDumbG.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on the Gerzee homeworld with the typical life of foraging for food, running from predators, and spending time with the family who survived those predators. [PAWN_nameDef] is notable, however, for being one of the dumbest members of their entire herd.</HomeworldChildDumbG.baseDescription>
  <HaulSlave.title>Hauler Slave</HaulSlave.title>
  <HaulSlave.titleShort>Hauler Slave</HaulSlave.titleShort>
  <HaulSlave.baseDescription>As what happens with many Gerzee who are torn from their homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was mainly used by slavers for hauling large objects, since the Gerzee can carry much more weight and bulk than most other races.</HaulSlave.baseDescription>
  <DearmedHaulSlave.title>Dearmed Hauler Slave</DearmedHaulSlave.title>
  <DearmedHaulSlave.titleShort>Dearmed Hauler</DearmedHaulSlave.titleShort>
  <DearmedHaulSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to mine slavers, a task fitting for the burrowing Gerzee. Unfortunately for [PAWN_objective], these were particularly brutal slavers. To help prevent mine workers from fighting their way out, the slavers would take an arm or two of their hauling slaves and replace them with simple prosthetics. This didn’t slow down the work since a hauler’s job was to carry large backpacks of broken rock, but it did make helping their fellow slaves in a fight nearly impossible.</DearmedHaulSlave.baseDescription>
  <PlanterSlave.title>Planter Slave</PlanterSlave.title>
  <PlanterSlave.titleShort>Planter Slave</PlanterSlave.titleShort>
  <PlanterSlave.baseDescription>Considering the Gerzee lifestyle of constantly foraging for plants, slavers had captured [PAWN_nameDef] and used [PAWN_objective] as farm labor for the corn fields of the slaver base. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend all day working the fields, being given little time to do anything else.</PlanterSlave.baseDescription>
  <FarmSlave.title>Farm Slave</FarmSlave.title>
  <FarmSlave.titleShort>Farm Slave</FarmSlave.titleShort>
  <FarmSlave.baseDescription>Considering the Gerzee lifestyle of constantly foraging for plants, slavers had captured [PAWN_nameDef] and sold [PAWN_objective] as farm labor. [PAWN_pronoun] would be used mainly be used to plant crops and haul heavy things, and occasionally to help tend the animals.</FarmSlave.baseDescription>
  <MineSlave.title>Mine Slave</MineSlave.title>
  <MineSlave.titleShort>Mine Slave</MineSlave.titleShort>
  <MineSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to mining slavers, who used [PAWN_possessive] strength to quickly smash through rock.</MineSlave.baseDescription>
  <PegMineSlave.title>Pegleg Mine Slave</PegMineSlave.title>
  <PegMineSlave.titleShort>Pegleg Slave</PegMineSlave.titleShort>
  <PegMineSlave.baseDescription>Mining slavers used [PAWN_nameDef] use their Gerzee strength to quickly smash through rock. Unfortunately for [PAWN_nameDef], these were particularly brutal slavers. Knowing that Gerzee miners were some of the few Gerzee who try to break out of slavery, these slavers usually replaced their miners’ legs with a wooden peg leg or two. [PAWN_nameDef] did not escape this fate.</PegMineSlave.baseDescription>
  <HandlerSlave.title>Handler Slave</HandlerSlave.title>
  <HandlerSlave.titleShort>Handler Slave</HandlerSlave.titleShort>
  <HandlerSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was a slave. Being considered just a “smarter” animal by the slavers, [PAWN_pronoun] was assigned to dealing with simple animal chores, such as milking and patching up muffalo.</HandlerSlave.baseDescription>
  <TortureSlave.title>Tortured Slave</TortureSlave.title>
  <TortureSlave.titleShort>Tortured Slave</TortureSlave.titleShort>
  <TortureSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was already unlucky enough to be a slave. Unfortunately, they eventually wre purchased by some particularly brutal slavers, and took joy in torturing [PAWN_objective] for years. [PAWN_nameDef] managed to survive long enough to be sold off to someone else, though by then a good amount of damage had already been done to [PAWN_possessive] body and mind.</TortureSlave.baseDescription>
  <BelovedSlave.title>Beloved Slave</BelovedSlave.title>
  <BelovedSlave.titleShort>Beloved Slave</BelovedSlave.titleShort>
  <BelovedSlave.baseDescription>While [PAWN_nameDef] was unlucky enough to be sold into slavery, [PAWN_pronoun] was lucky enough to have been first sold to a family to act as a caretaker for a kind old man. The old man treated [PAWN_nameDef] well for years and did their best to teach [PAWN_nameDef] some skills that might help [PAWN_objective] survive later on, knowing that [PAWN_nameDef] would be sold off by the family once he died. The old man eventually did die and [PAWN_nameDef] was sold, though now having a few skills the average Gerzee does not possess.</BelovedSlave.baseDescription>
  <ChemSlave.title>Chem Storage Slave</ChemSlave.title>
  <ChemSlave.titleShort>Chem Storage Slave </ChemSlave.titleShort>
  <ChemSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to a chemical waste-disposal company as  a slave worker. The company would deposit the waste while the workers were still digging out bigger storage spaces, as the money they made from promising such quick project times was more than the costs for buying replacement slaves. [PAWN_nameDef] only survived because cancerous body parts were chopped off early enough to avoid spreading to the rest of the body.</ChemSlave.baseDescription>
  <ResearchSlave.title>Research Slave</ResearchSlave.title>
  <ResearchSlave.titleShort>Research Slave</ResearchSlave.titleShort>
  <ResearchSlave.baseDescription>Mining slavers captured [PAWN_nameDef] from the Gerzee homeworld and sold them to a chemical waste-disposal company. Luckily for [PAWN_objective], a researcher at the site took [PAWN_objective] as their personal worker. [PAWN_nameDef] spent  most of [PAWN_objective] time moving heavy objects, but overheard enough scientific conversations to learn a couple of things.</ResearchSlave.baseDescription>
  <CookSlave.title>Cook Slave</CookSlave.title>
  <CookSlave.titleShort>Cook Slave</CookSlave.titleShort>
  <CookSlave.baseDescription>The slavers that owned [PAWN_nameDef] entertained themselves with the somewhat uncommon practice of making [PAWN_objective] the "chef" of the slave food supply. Seeing as how Gerzee can't even try to eat cooked foods without becoming violently ill, this meant [PAWN_nameDef] could only try to learn by experimenting and seeing the results of what [PAWN_pronoun] had made. After quite a few slaves died, the slavers stopped their game. However, the experience still left [PAWN_nameDef] a little broken.</CookSlave.baseDescription>
  <MineRevoltSlave.title>Mine Revolter</MineRevoltSlave.title>
  <MineRevoltSlave.titleShort>Mine Revolter</MineRevoltSlave.titleShort>
  <MineRevoltSlave.baseDescription>Mining slavers used [PAWN_objective]’s strength to quickly smash through rock. Being one of the few slave types who get to practice hitting things, the rare Gerzee that manage to overpower their slavers tend to be miners. [PAWN_nameDef] was a part of a group of such miners, who managed to break themselves out.</MineRevoltSlave.baseDescription>
  <FarmEscapeSlave.title>Farm Escapee</FarmEscapeSlave.title>
  <FarmEscapeSlave.titleShort>Farm Escapee</FarmEscapeSlave.titleShort>
  <FarmEscapeSlave.baseDescription>Considering the Gerzee lifestyle of constantly foraging for plants, slavers had used [PAWN_nameDef] as farm labor for the slaver base. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend all day working the fields, being given little time to do anything else. What [PAWN_objective] captors didn’t notice was that [PAWN_pronoun] was using [PAWN_objective] woodcutting and land-breaking chores as practice for fighting. Eventually [PAWN_pronoun] knocked out the field guard watching [PAWN_objective], and escaped into the wild.</FarmEscapeSlave.baseDescription>
  <VolunteerGuardSlave.title>Volunteer Guard</VolunteerGuardSlave.title>
  <VolunteerGuardSlave.titleShort>Volunteer Guard</VolunteerGuardSlave.titleShort>
  <VolunteerGuardSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was broken out of a slave camp by fellow slaves. Despite not having much experience with fighting, [PAWN_pronoun] quickly volunteered to become a defender of their newly formed tribe, knowing that the tribe would not survive this rimworld using the old ways of survival from the Gerzee homeworld.</VolunteerGuardSlave.baseDescription>
  <ExElder.title>Ex-Elder</ExElder.title>
  <ExElder.titleShort>Ex-Elder</ExElder.titleShort>
  <ExElder.baseDescription>The heads of Gerzee family packs are chosen based purely on age. Whichever member of the group is oldest at the time becomes the leader until they die, as their skills to survive all the predators of their world for so long makes them revered. [PAWN_nameDef] was one such elder, though sadly [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually caught by slavers. As Gerzee not on their homeworld are all there due to having failed to escape slavers (aka predators), the leadership system no longer applies to rimworld Gerzee.</ExElder.baseDescription>
  <PitFighterSlave.title>Pit Fighter</PitFighterSlave.title>
  <PitFighterSlave.titleShort>Pit Fighter</PitFighterSlave.titleShort>
  <PitFighterSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to an entertainment company to be used as an easy sacrifice in gladiator fights. Unlike most Gerzee who easily die off in such exhibitions, [PAWN_nameDef] turned out to be decent at fighting. And so [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to fight for years, being transported all over the galaxy as a special treat for gladiator audiences.</PitFighterSlave.baseDescription>
  <MineVengSlave.title>Mine Slayer</MineVengSlave.title>
  <MineVengSlave.titleShort>Mine Slayer </MineVengSlave.titleShort>
  <MineVengSlave.baseDescription>Mining slavers used [PAWN_nameDef]’s strength to quickly smash through rock for many years. Being one of the few slave types who get to practice hitting things, the rare Gerzee that manage to overpower their slavers tend to be miners. [PAWN_nameDef] was one such example, breaking themselves out and killing a couple of captors along the way. [PAWN_pronoun] decided [PAWN_pronoun] quite liked killing slavers, and made it [PAWN_objective] mission to kill as many as possible.</MineVengSlave.baseDescription>
  <FarmVengSlave.title>Farm Slayer</FarmVengSlave.title>
  <FarmVengSlave.titleShort>Farm Slayer</FarmVengSlave.titleShort>
  <FarmVengSlave.baseDescription>Considering the Gerzee lifestyle of constantly foraging for plants, slavers had captured [PAWN_nameDef] and used [PAWN_objective] as farm labor for the slaver base. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend all day working the fields, being given little time to do anything else. What [PAWN_objective] captors didn’t notice was that [PAWN_pronoun] was using [PAWN_objective] woodcutting and land-breaking chores as practice for cutting and breaking people. Eventually [PAWN_pronoun] killed the field guard watching [PAWN_objective], and escaped into the wild.</FarmVengSlave.baseDescription>
  <TortureVengSlave.title>Tortured Slayer</TortureVengSlave.title>
  <TortureVengSlave.titleShort>Tortured Slayer </TortureVengSlave.titleShort>
  <TortureVengSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was already unlucky enough to have been captured by a small group of slavers and taken from [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. Unfortunately, those slavers were particularly brutal as well, and took joy from torturing [PAWN_objective]. During one particular day of torture something in [PAWN_nameDef] snapped and, against the very passive Gerzee nature, [PAWN_pronoun] beat all of [PAWN_objective] captors to death.  Upon discovering [PAWN_pronoun] was stranded far from their homeworld, [PAWN_pronoun] decided to spend [PAWN_possessive] time hunting down potential slavers.</TortureVengSlave.baseDescription>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperiment.title>Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperiment.title>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperiment.titleShort>Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperiment.titleShort>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperiment.baseDescription>With Gerzee being of considerable size and strength, they are often experimented on by shady military corporations as potential soldiers. [PAWN_nameDef] was a part of one such secret program, having received combat training and new body parts to make them combat-ready. Unfortunately for the scientists, the experiment worked a little too well. [PAWN_nameDef] and a few other soldier experiments managed to wipe out the entire compound and escape.</GerzeeSoldierExperiment.baseDescription>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.title>Heavily Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.title>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.titleShort>Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.titleShort>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.baseDescription>With Gerzee being of considerable size and strength, they are often experimented on by shady military corporations as potential soldiers. [PAWN_nameDef] was a part of one such secret program, having received combat training and new body parts to make them combat-ready. Unfortunately for the scientists, the experiment worked a little too well. After being freed by fellow soldier experiments, [PAWN_nameDef] helped wipe out the entire facility and escape.</GerzeeSoldierExperimentHeavy.baseDescription>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.title>Recently Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.title>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.titleShort>Altered Gerzee</GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.titleShort>
  <GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.baseDescription>With Gerzee being of considerable size and strength, they are often experimented on by shady military corporations as potential soldiers. [PAWN_nameDef] was recently part of one such secret program, having received combat training and some new body parts to make them combat-ready. Unfortunately for the scientists, the experiment worked a little too well. After being freed by fellow soldier experiments, [PAWN_nameDef] helped wipe out the entire facility and escape.</GerzeeSoldierExperimentRecent.baseDescription>
  <SnappedChemSlave.title>Snapped Chem Storage Slave</SnappedChemSlave.title>
  <SnappedChemSlave.titleShort>Snapped Chem </SnappedChemSlave.titleShort>
  <SnappedChemSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to a chemical waste-disposal company as  a slave worker. The company would deposit the waste while the workers were still digging out bigger storage spaces, as the money they made from promising such quick project times was more than the costs for buying replacement slaves.	After watching most of their herd die from chemical poisoning, [PAWN_nameDef] eventually snapped and fought their way out. Far from home and most of their family dead, [PAWN_pronoun] has decided to try and destroy any potential slavers.</SnappedChemSlave.baseDescription>
  <GerzeeNewSlave.title>New Slave</GerzeeNewSlave.title>
  <GerzeeNewSlave.titleShort>New Slave</GerzeeNewSlave.titleShort>
  <GerzeeNewSlave.baseDescription>[PAWN_nameDef] is a recent capture by slavers. [PAWN_pronoun] hasn’t gone through much hardship, but [PAWN_pronoun] also hasn’t learned any particular skills. Though since [PAWN_pronoun] just recently came from a typical Gerzee life of foraging for food (and running from predators), [PAWN_pronoun] hasn’t lost any of [PAWN_objective] skill with plants yet.</GerzeeNewSlave.baseDescription>
</LanguageData>