<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Autobong.label>autobong</Autobong.label>
  <Autobong.description>An automatic smokeleaf-burning device which generates a smoke cloud around itself. Anyone in the cloud will become high on smokeleaf over time.</Autobong.description>
  
  <Drum.label>drum</Drum.label>
  <Drum.description>A large wooden drum used as a music source for tribal rituals and parties.</Drum.description>
  
  <DryadCocoon.label>dryad cocoon</DryadCocoon.label>
  <DryadCocoon.description>A sphere of fibrous plant matter. A dryad inside is slowly morphing into a new form. Gauranlen trees grow these spheres to help protect the dryads as they morph.</DryadCocoon.description>
  
  <DryadHealingPod.label>dryad healing pod</DryadHealingPod.label>
  <DryadHealingPod.description>A sphere of fibrous plant matter. A dryad inside is slowly healing its wounds.</DryadHealingPod.description>
  
  <GaumakerCocoon.label>gaumaker pod</GaumakerCocoon.label>
  <GaumakerCocoon.description>The result of the merging of several Gaumaker dryads, this symbiotic plant/animal pod is an essential part of the Gauranlen life cycle. After some time, it will flower into a mature Gauranlen pod which can be harvested to plant a new Gauranlen tree.</GaumakerCocoon.description>
  
  <GibbetCage.label>gibbet cage</GibbetCage.label>
  <GibbetCage.description>A steel cage for holding and displaying corpses. This horrifying sight inspires terror and disgust in observers. It is an especially brutal and effective way to terrorize slaves.</GibbetCage.description>
  
  <KneelPillow.label>kneel pillow</KneelPillow.label>
  <KneelPillow.description>A pillow on which believers kneel while observing rituals, praying, or discussing.</KneelPillow.description>
  
  <KneelSheet.label>kneel sheet</KneelSheet.label>
  <KneelSheet.description>A sheet on which believers kneel while observing rituals, praying, or discussing.</KneelSheet.description>
  
  <Lectern.label>lectern</Lectern.label>
  <Lectern.description>A slanted platform that holds a text in front of a speaker. Place it near the focus of rituals and speeches to extend the duration of their positive effects.</Lectern.description>
  
  <LightBall.label>lightball</LightBall.label>
  <LightBall.description>A decorative light that rotates and changes colors. Used as a focus for dance parties.</LightBall.description>
  
  <Loudspeaker.label>loudspeaker</Loudspeaker.label>
  <Loudspeaker.description>A large loudspeaker for playing music. At least one is necessary to hold a dance party, and more loudspeakers will enhance the effect.</Loudspeaker.description>
  
  <Pew.label>pew</Pew.label>
  <Pew.description>A long bench where ritual participants can sit while listening to a speaker. Place it facing rituals and speeches to extend the duration of their positive effects.</Pew.description>
  
  <PlantPot_Bonsai.label>bonsai pot</PlantPot_Bonsai.label>
  <PlantPot_Bonsai.description>This special pot is suitable for planting bonsai trees, which can improve the mood of people nearby and satisfy ideoligious requirements.</PlantPot_Bonsai.description>
  
  <Reliquary.label>reliquary</Reliquary.label>
  <Reliquary.description>A ceremonial building that protects and displays a relic. Relics are ancient objects venerated by some cultures, belief systems, or religions.</Reliquary.description>
  
  <Skullspike.label>skullspike</Skullspike.label>
  <Skullspike.description>A spike mounted upright for the purpose of piercing and displaying a human skull. To some, displayed skulls are a symbol of power. To others, they represent barbaric evil. Skullspikes are an especially brutal and effective way to terrorize slaves.</Skullspike.description>
  <Skullspike.comps.CompHasSources.inspectStringLabel>skull of</Skullspike.comps.CompHasSources.inspectStringLabel>
  
  <SlabBed.label>slab bed</SlabBed.label>
  <SlabBed.description>A slab of hard material made to sleep on. Slab beds are uncomfortable, but some see their use as a demonstration of moral good.</SlabBed.description>
  
  <SlabDoubleBed.label>slab double bed</SlabDoubleBed.label>
  <SlabDoubleBed.description>A slab of hard material made to sleep on. Slab beds are uncomfortable, but some see their use as a demonstration of moral good. This one is wide enough to fit two people.</SlabDoubleBed.description>
  
  <StylingStation.label>styling station</StylingStation.label>
  <StylingStation.description>A table with a mirror and styling tools. People can use this to change their look.</StylingStation.description>
</LanguageData>