<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Chemical_Amita.label>amita</Chemical_Amita.label>
  <Chemical_Amita.description>Because of a amita addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Amita.description>
  <Chemical_Andomorphine.label>Andomorphine</Chemical_Andomorphine.label>
  <Chemical_Andomorphine.description>Because of a Andomorphine, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.\n\nThis addiction never goes away.</Chemical_Andomorphine.description>
  <Chemical_AshesWater.label>Ashes water</Chemical_AshesWater.label>
  <Chemical_AshesWater.description>Because of a ashes water addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_AshesWater.description>
  <Chemical_Dextromitaine.label>Dextromitaine</Chemical_Dextromitaine.label>
  <Chemical_Dextromitaine.description>Because of a Dextromitaine addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Dextromitaine.description>
  <Chemical_Entotizin.label>Entotizin</Chemical_Entotizin.label>
  <Chemical_Entotizin.description>Because of a Entotizin addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Entotizin.description>
  <Chemical_Extratisinum.label>Extratisinum</Chemical_Extratisinum.label>
  <Chemical_Extratisinum.description>Because of a Extratisinum addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Extratisinum.description>
  <Chemical_Joycstasy.label>Joycstasy</Chemical_Joycstasy.label>
  <Chemical_Joycstasy.description>Because of a joycstasy addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Joycstasy.description>
  <Chemical_Likombinat.label>Likombinat</Chemical_Likombinat.label>
  <Chemical_Likombinat.description>Because of a Likombinat addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Likombinat.description>
  <Chemical_MaxBrain.label>Drug 'boost your brain'</Chemical_MaxBrain.label>
  <Chemical_MaxBrain.description>Because of a 'boost your brain' addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_MaxBrain.description>
  <Chemical_Metocarbine.label>Metocarbine</Chemical_Metocarbine.label>
  <Chemical_Metocarbine.description>Because of a Metocarbine addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Metocarbine.description>
  <Chemical_Mirotofinil.label>Mirotofinil</Chemical_Mirotofinil.label>
  <Chemical_Mirotofinil.description>Because of a Mirotofinil addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Mirotofinil.description>
  <Chemical_Narkoata.label>Narkoata</Chemical_Narkoata.label>
  <Chemical_Narkoata.description>Because of a Narkoata addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Narkoata.description>
  <Chemical_Pemotilan.label>Pemotilan</Chemical_Pemotilan.label>
  <Chemical_Pemotilan.description>Because of a Pemotilan addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Pemotilan.description>
  <Chemical_Spasmonitis.label>Spasmonitis</Chemical_Spasmonitis.label>
  <Chemical_Spasmonitis.description>Because of a spasmonitis addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Spasmonitis.description>
  <Chemical_Tetrodicline.label>Tetrodicline</Chemical_Tetrodicline.label>
  <Chemical_Tetrodicline.description>Because of a Tetrodicline addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Tetrodicline.description>
  <Chemical_Zero.label>Zero</Chemical_Zero.label>
  <Chemical_Zero.description>Because of a Zero addiction, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</Chemical_Zero.description>
</LanguageData>