<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RB_BasicBeekeeping.label>basic beekeeping</RB_BasicBeekeeping.label>
  <RB_BasicBeekeeping.description>Research the basics of beekeeping. With this research you can begin experimenting on the most basic breeds of bees, mild and temperate (tier 1), which are extracted from wild hives. To get new breeds of bees, you will need to research further.</RB_BasicBeekeeping.description>
  <RB_BeeBreeding.label>bee breeding</RB_BeeBreeding.label>
  <RB_BeeBreeding.description>Research bee breeding to get new members of the bee breeds you already have. When attached to a beehouse, the Brood Chamber produces random drones and queens of one of the breeds present in the beehouse. This is super useful to increase your total number of bees!</RB_BeeBreeding.description>
  <RB_BeeHybridizing.label>bee hybridizing</RB_BeeHybridizing.label>
  <RB_BeeHybridizing.description>Research bee hybridizing to get new breeds of bees. When attached to a beehouse, the Hybridization Chamber produces queens of a new, hybrid species by mixing the genes of those present in the beehouse. The beehouse will alert you if the combination of bees in the beehouse produces no hybrids, or if it produces more than one hybrid at random!</RB_BeeHybridizing.description>
  <RB_MeadBrewing.label>mead brewing</RB_MeadBrewing.label>
  <RB_MeadBrewing.description>Research mead brewing to be able to ferment a mixture of honey and water into mead. Mead is a mild alcoholic bewerage.</RB_MeadBrewing.description>
  <RB_BeeswaxLighting.label>beeswax lighting</RB_BeeswaxLighting.label>
  <RB_BeeswaxLighting.description>Research beeswax lighting to build candles. A cheap, quaint alternative to electric lights. Candles last several days without needing to be recharged by adding new beeswax, and they produce a small amount of heat as well as light.</RB_BeeswaxLighting.description>
  <RB_ClimatizedBeehouses.label>climatized beehouses</RB_ClimatizedBeehouses.label>
  <RB_ClimatizedBeehouses.description>Are you trying to breed bees in a biome with extreme temperatures? You'll notice that they are inactive most of the year. With a climatized beehouse you can make them work no matter what temperature is outside. It is slow, though, so your best bet is to breed new bees of the biome branch to modify the temperatures in a regular beehouse.</RB_ClimatizedBeehouses.description>
  <RB_AdvancedBeehouses.label>advanced beehouses</RB_AdvancedBeehouses.label>
  <RB_AdvancedBeehouses.description>Advanced beehouses consume a small amount of electricity, but provide a 25% boost to bee production speed. Useful!</RB_AdvancedBeehouses.description>
  <RB_AdvancedClimatization.label>advanced climatization</RB_AdvancedClimatization.label>
  <RB_AdvancedClimatization.description>Advanced climatized beehouses allow you to breed bees without caring for outside temperatures, and without carrying the penalty of regular climatized beehouses.</RB_AdvancedClimatization.description>
  <RB_AdvancedCentrifugation.label>advanced honey centrifugation</RB_AdvancedCentrifugation.label>
  <RB_AdvancedCentrifugation.description>The Advanced Honey Centrifuge semi-automates the process of centrifugating combs to get resources, allowing your colonists to extract them in bulk. This machine though doesn't do "extract from any available comb" tasks.</RB_AdvancedCentrifugation.description>
</LanguageData>