<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <IV_Nutrition_Research_Normal.label>Nutrition IV</IV_Nutrition_Research_Normal.label>
  <IV_Nutrition_Research_Normal.description>Provides nutrition via tube to bed-ridden colonists. Needs to be fueled with any item that provides nutritional value. Being fed liquid food isn't the best but it's cheaper, easier and better than starving...</IV_Nutrition_Research_Normal.description>
  <IV_Painkiller_Research_Normal.label>Painkiller IV</IV_Painkiller_Research_Normal.label>
  <IV_Painkiller_Research_Normal.description>Injects painkiller straight into the veins for increased effectiveness. Much more potent than taking tablets orally but only works when applied constantly.</IV_Painkiller_Research_Normal.description>
  <IV_Antibiotic_Research_Normal.label>Antibiotic IV</IV_Antibiotic_Research_Normal.label>
  <IV_Antibiotic_Research_Normal.description>Speeds up recovery from illness by directly injecting antibiotics into the bloodstream. Significantly more potent than just taking the tablets.</IV_Antibiotic_Research_Normal.description>
  <IV_Blood_Research_Normal.label>Blood IV</IV_Blood_Research_Normal.label>
  <IV_Blood_Research_Normal.description>A drip for realtime blood transfusions and coagulation. Slows down the rate a colonist bleeds out by thinning blood vessels, clotting wounds and reintroducing blood into the body. Requires blood bags as fuel, which can be retreived from drawing blood from Pawns or synthesizing them with bloodstem at a drug lab/crafting spot.</IV_Blood_Research_Normal.description>
  <IV_Anesthetic_Research_Normal.label>Anesthetic IV</IV_Anesthetic_Research_Normal.label>
  <IV_Anesthetic_Research_Normal.description>Keeps a pawn in a medically-induced coma permanently -- or until it's switched off. Monitors the vitals of the patient to ensure the exact dose of anesthetic administered maintains the coma without concern of death or brain damage.</IV_Anesthetic_Research_Normal.description>
  <BloodStemMK2.label>Bloodstem Infusion</BloodStemMK2.label>
  <BloodStemMK2.description>Using mechanites, enzymes and some good ol' bloodstem, you can synthesize blood and siphon it into bags as a near-limitless source of fuel for intraveneous therapy.</BloodStemMK2.description>
  <IV_Electrical_Research.label>Powered Medical Drips</IV_Electrical_Research.label>
  <IV_Electrical_Research.description>Using the hyper-conductivity of plasteel and the radioactivity of uranium, decaying neutrons can be positively charged and captured in liquid molecules. When injected into the body, the Pawn receives the benefits of the liquid without any being absorbed and lost. The result? A closed-loop pump that never runs out of fuel whilst maintaining all the benefits of traditional intraveneous therapy!</IV_Electrical_Research.description>
  <IV_Nutrition_Research_Electric.label>Electrical Nutrition IV</IV_Nutrition_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Nutrition_Research_Electric.description>Provides nutrition via tube to bed-ridden colonists. Being fed liquid food isn't the best but it's cheaper, easier and better than starving... Incorporates closed-loop pump technology for limitless fuel.</IV_Nutrition_Research_Electric.description>
  <IV_Painkiller_Research_Electric.label>Electrical Painkiller IV</IV_Painkiller_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Painkiller_Research_Electric.description>Injects painkiller straight into the veins for increased effectiveness. Much more potent than taking tablets orally but only works when applied constantly. Incorporates closed-loop pump technology for limitless fuel.</IV_Painkiller_Research_Electric.description>
  <IV_Antibiotic_Research_Electric.label>Electrical Antibiotic IV</IV_Antibiotic_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Antibiotic_Research_Electric.description>Speeds up recovery from illness by directly injecting antibiotics into the bloodstream. Significantly more potent than just taking the tablets. Incorporates closed-loop pump technology for limitless fuel.</IV_Antibiotic_Research_Electric.description>
  <IV_Blood_Research_Electric.label>Electrical Blood IV</IV_Blood_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Blood_Research_Electric.description>A drip for realtime blood transfusions and coagulation. Slows down the rate a colonist bleeds out by thinning blood vessels, clotting wounds and reintroducing blood into the body. Incorporates closed-loop pump technology for limitless fuel.</IV_Blood_Research_Electric.description>
  <IV_Anesthetic_Research_Electric.label>Electrical Anesthetic IV</IV_Anesthetic_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Anesthetic_Research_Electric.description>Keeps a pawn in a medically-induced coma permanently -- or until it's switched off. Monitors the vitals of the patient to ensure the exact dose of anesthetic administered maintains the coma without concern of death or brain damage. Incorporates closed-loop pump technology for limitless fuel.</IV_Anesthetic_Research_Electric.description>
  <IV_Glitterworld_Research_Electric.label>Glitterworld IV</IV_Glitterworld_Research_Electric.label>
  <IV_Glitterworld_Research_Electric.description>By enriching the blood with painkillers and antibiotics before it gets injected into the bloodstream, you can combine the functionality of all three drips. With both the closed-loop pump technology and this new enrichment process, the Glitterworld drip's complexity is unlike that seen anywhere but on distant Glitterworlds. Draws a lot of electricity.</IV_Glitterworld_Research_Electric.description>
</LanguageData>