<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DrillArm.label>drill arm</DrillArm.label>
  <DrillArm.description>An installed drill arm. Allows the miner to rapidly find and exploit weak lines in the rock. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</DrillArm.description>
  <DrillArm.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.drill.label>drill</DrillArm.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.drill.label>
  <DrillArm.labelNoun>a drill arm</DrillArm.labelNoun>
  
  <ElbowBlade.label>elbow blade</ElbowBlade.label>
  <ElbowBlade.description>An installed elbow blade. Extends at will from a hidden opening at the end of the ulna. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating slice attacks.</ElbowBlade.description>
  <ElbowBlade.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.blade.label>blade</ElbowBlade.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.blade.label>
  <ElbowBlade.labelNoun>an elbow blade</ElbowBlade.labelNoun>
  
  <FieldHand.label>field hand</FieldHand.label>
  <FieldHand.description>An installed field hand. Made to speed up the sowing and harvesting tasks of a farmer. Multiple telescoping finger-like protrusions can simultaneously harvest from several points on the same plant, or precisely sow several holes at once. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</FieldHand.description>
  <FieldHand.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.knuckle.label>knuckle</FieldHand.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.knuckle.label>
  <FieldHand.labelNoun>a field hand</FieldHand.labelNoun>
  
  <HandTalon.label>hand talon</HandTalon.label>
  <HandTalon.description>An installed hand talon. Extends from a hidden opening between the middle and ring fingers. The talon is longer than the palm, but it becomes flexible upon retracting, allowing the user to curl it up and conceal it inside the hand. It can perform rapid slashing attacks, but is poor at penetrating armor.</HandTalon.description>
  <HandTalon.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.talon.label>talon</HandTalon.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.talon.label>
  <HandTalon.labelNoun>a hand talon</HandTalon.labelNoun>
  
  <KneeSpike.label>knee spike</KneeSpike.label>
  <KneeSpike.description>An installed knee spike. Extends at will from a hidden opening on the front of the knee. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating stabbing attacks which penetrate even thick armor.</KneeSpike.description>
  <KneeSpike.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.spike.label>spike</KneeSpike.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.spike.label>
  <KneeSpike.labelNoun>a knee spike</KneeSpike.labelNoun>
  
  <Mindscrew.label>mindscrew</Mindscrew.label>
  <Mindscrew.description>An installed mindscrew. Inflicts continuous pain on the user. Mindscrews are used by some authorities as a long-term punishment. Some even install them voluntarily as a demonstration of ideological or religious devotion.</Mindscrew.description>
  <Mindscrew.labelNoun>a mindscrew</Mindscrew.labelNoun>
  
  <VenomFangs.label>venom fangs</VenomFangs.label>
  <VenomFangs.description>An installed set of venom fangs. The user can bite an enemy, extend the injectors, and pump venom into the target.</VenomFangs.description>
  <VenomFangs.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.venom_fangs.label>venom fangs</VenomFangs.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.venom_fangs.label>
  <VenomFangs.labelNoun>a set of venom fangs</VenomFangs.labelNoun>
  
  <VenomTalon.label>venom talon</VenomTalon.label>
  <VenomTalon.description>An installed venom talon. The user can scratch an enemy while squirting venom into the wound. The talon is designed to be installed in the middle finger. It's fast, but poor at penetrating armor.</VenomTalon.description>
  <VenomTalon.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.venom_talon.label>venom talon</VenomTalon.comps.HediffComp_VerbGiver.tools.venom_talon.label>
  <VenomTalon.labelNoun>a venom talon</VenomTalon.labelNoun>
</LanguageData>