<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <IceAge.label>Ice Age</IceAge.label>
  <IceAge.description>Atmospheric composition of the planet drastically changed resulting in a significant drop in temperature.

Flora and Fauna is suffering from these changes as biomes shift into their colder counterparts. Resources become scarce, forcing factions into conflict.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</IceAge.description>
  <IceAge.endMessage>The ice age is ending</IceAge.endMessage>
  <GlobalWarming.label>Global Warming</GlobalWarming.label>
  <GlobalWarming.description>Global temperatures have suddenly risen to dangerous levels.

Flora and Fauna is suffering from these changes as biomes shift into their warmer counterparts. Resources become scarce, forcing factions into conflict.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</GlobalWarming.description>
  <GlobalWarming.endMessage>The global warming is ending</GlobalWarming.endMessage>
  <PsychicRain.label>Psychic Rain</PsychicRain.label>
  <PsychicRain.description>A dangerous psychic entity caused disturbance on subatomic levels, resonating across all particles of the atmosphere.

A seemingly endless supernatural rain has begun, altering the very composition of time. Any person or creature not under the roof will age significantly faster.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</PsychicRain.description>
  <PsychicRain.endMessage>The psychic rain is ending</PsychicRain.endMessage>
  <LongNight.label>Long Night</LongNight.label>
  <LongNight.description>A space entity of unimaginable size has covered a local star, resulting in a long lasting eclipse.

Terrified of this supernatural phenomenon, other factions will use this time to wage war and conflict across the surface.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</LongNight.description>
  <LongNight.endMessage>The long night is ending</LongNight.endMessage>
  <PsychicBloom.label>Psychic Bloom</PsychicBloom.label>
  <PsychicBloom.description>A strong psychic pulse emitted by a long forgotten entity changed the very genetical structure of local flora. Whilst the sky filled with a seemingly endless auroras, colourful flowers started sprouting everywhere. 

All pawns will gain a positive mood buff for the time of the event. The rapidly spreading flowers will overgrow everything, including your fields. 

It will last anywhere between a few days to a season.</PsychicBloom.description>
  <PsychicBloom.endMessage>The psychic bloom is ending</PsychicBloom.endMessage>
  <HailStorm.label>Hail Storm</HailStorm.label>
  <HailStorm.description>A freak, small scale hail storm is ravaging the local area. Any person or creature not hiding under the roof risks getting injured by ice pellets.</HailStorm.description>
  <HailStorm.endMessage>The hail storm is ending.</HailStorm.endMessage>
  <Drought.label>Drought</Drought.label>
  <Drought.description>An unusual drought has set in.

Drought is devastating for plant life and will quickly destroy all the crops not planted in the hydroponics. Be sure to quickly harvest any plants you can.</Drought.description>
  <Drought.endMessage>The drought is ending.</Drought.endMessage>
  <SpaceBattle.label>Space battle</SpaceBattle.label>
  <SpaceBattle.description>A space battle is raging in the sky, may last up to 1 day.</SpaceBattle.description>
  <SpaceBattle.endMessage>The space battle is ending.</SpaceBattle.endMessage>
</LanguageData>