<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FF_Antidepressant.label>antidepressant</FF_Antidepressant.label>
  <FF_Antidepressant.description>A drug that induces a mild euphoria without the risk of side effects. Effective at counteracting depression.</FF_Antidepressant.description>
  <FF_Ectostasis.label>ectostasis</FF_Ectostasis.label>
  <FF_Ectostasis.description>Homeostatic drug composed of medical mechanites programmed to maintain bodily functions at baseline levels, suppressing chronic conditions as long as the drug is taken.</FF_Ectostasis.description>
  <FF_Fibrodust.label>fibrodust</FF_Fibrodust.label>
  <FF_Fibrodust.description>A coagulant powder that stops bleeding on the spot, developed by midworld militaries. The clotting effect fades rapidly, serving only to buy time for proper treatment. Usage may induce serious cardiovascular issues.</FF_Fibrodust.description>
  <FF_Neoderm.label>neoderm</FF_Neoderm.label>
  <FF_Neoderm.description>An advanced regenerative ointment. Neoderm heals dermal scars over time through a mildly painful process. Has no effect on internal organs or eyes.

Takes 5-7 days to heal one scar. Must be taken everyday.</FF_Neoderm.description>
  <FF_Overclock.label>overclock</FF_Overclock.label>
  <FF_Overclock.description>A self-injected drug cocktail that overclocks the user's metabolism, increasing movement and productivity. The drug places a heavy strain on the body, rapidly wearing it out while active.</FF_Overclock.description>
  <FF_Painkiller.label>painkiller</FF_Painkiller.label>
  <FF_Painkiller.description>An analgesic that dulls sensation, providing relief from physical pain. Overuse may cause addiction and serious side effects.</FF_Painkiller.description>
  <FF_Scythe.label>scythe</FF_Scythe.label>
  <FF_Scythe.description>A powerful immunostimulant developed to fight a pre-spacer era pandemic. Scythe utilizes a chemotherapeutic mechanism to massively overstimulate the immune system. However, it is used only as a last resort - the resulting frenzy of immune activity stresses the body into a two-day coma.</FF_Scythe.description>
  <FF_Sorrow.label>sorrow</FF_Sorrow.label>
  <FF_Sorrow.description>An advanced depressant that causes a controlled surge of sadness, often allowing cathartic introspection.\n\nRecommended for those who suffered great losses to prevent more serious mental breaks.</FF_Sorrow.description>
  <FF_Plant_PoisonIvy.label>poison ivy plant</FF_Plant_PoisonIvy.label>
  <FF_Plant_PoisonIvy.description>A bushy, vining plant with distinctive leaves. Since poison ivy can cause irritating, itchy rashes on contact, it is widely regarded as a nuisance. However, its extract has valuable uses in medicine.</FF_Plant_PoisonIvy.description>
  <FF_PoisonIvyLeaves.label>poison ivy leaves</FF_PoisonIvyLeaves.label>
  <FF_PoisonIvyLeaves.description>Raw cut leaves of a poison ivy. Chemicals extracted from poison ivy cuttings can be used to produce strong drugs.</FF_PoisonIvyLeaves.description>
</LanguageData>