<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEV_Mead.label>mead</VFEV_Mead.label>
  <VFEV_Mead.description>A drink akin to wine, made of fermented honey and water, aged in a simple barrel. This sweet, crisp drink is known be nursed over time and has a reputation of being particularly comforting.</VFEV_Mead.description>
  <VFEV_Mead.ingestible.ingestCommandString>Drink {0}</VFEV_Mead.ingestible.ingestCommandString>
  <VFEV_Mead.ingestible.ingestReportString>Drinking {0}.</VFEV_Mead.ingestible.ingestReportString>
  <VFEV_Mead.tools.0.label>bottle</VFEV_Mead.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Mead.tools.1.label>neck</VFEV_Mead.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_FurBed.label>fur bed</VFEV_FurBed.label>
  <VFEV_FurBed.description>A wood-framed bed stuffed with dried grasses and covered in a variety of pelts and furs to provide extra insulation during frigid nights. The warmth of this bed counters hypothermia.</VFEV_FurBed.description>
  <VFEV_DoubleFurBed.label>double fur bed</VFEV_DoubleFurBed.label>
  <VFEV_DoubleFurBed.description>A two-person, wood-framed bed stuffed with dried grasses and covered in a variety of pelts and furs to provide extra insulation during frigid nights. The warmth of this bed counters hypothermia.</VFEV_DoubleFurBed.description>
  <VFEV_Hnefatafl.label>hnefatafl table</VFEV_Hnefatafl.label>
  <VFEV_Hnefatafl.description>An ancient board game played on a latticed board. Unlike its cousin Chess this game is asymmetrical, one player must safely retreat their Jarl to the edge of the board and the other player must capture the enemy Jarl before they escape. Notably more fights seem to break out over Hnefatafl compared to other games.</VFEV_Hnefatafl.description>
  <VFEV_TrainingDummy.label>training dummy</VFEV_TrainingDummy.label>
  <VFEV_TrainingDummy.description>A target dummy made out of wood, soil, and dried plant matter. Surprisingly durable, allows oneself to test their swordsmanship and train over time without risking fatal confrontation.</VFEV_TrainingDummy.description>
  <VFEV_MeadFermentingBarrel.label>mead fermenting barrel</VFEV_MeadFermentingBarrel.label>
  <VFEV_MeadFermentingBarrel.description>A very simple barrel, held together with a series of mortise and tenon joints.</VFEV_MeadFermentingBarrel.description>
  <VFEV_Apiary.label>apiary</VFEV_Apiary.label>
  <VFEV_Apiary.description>A wooden box-like structure with a series of shelves, lattices, and chambers. When placed near flowers the apiary will naturally attract wild bees which will make it their new home. Over time these bees will produce honey which can be harvested and eaten directly, or later fermented into mead.</VFEV_Apiary.description>
  <VFE_TableFacePaints.label>face painting table</VFE_TableFacePaints.label>
  <VFE_TableFacePaints.description>A table with a vast assortments of pigments and brushes for face painting.</VFE_TableFacePaints.description>
  <VFEV_RuneStone.label>rune stone</VFEV_RuneStone.label>
  <VFEV_RuneStone.description>A loosely carved and smoothed structure ascribed with ancient text and ornate patterns. Ancient northern tribes were known to pray at these shrines as well as keep them in their halls as aesthetic decorum.</VFEV_RuneStone.description>
  <VFEV_RunedColumn.label>runed column</VFEV_RunedColumn.label>
  <VFEV_RunedColumn.description>A column with ornate engravings in a supposedly mysterious language only legible by few. Quite pleasing to look at while also being a handy roof support.</VFEV_RunedColumn.description>
  <VFEV_Hearth.label>hearth</VFEV_Hearth.label>
  <VFEV_Hearth.description>A large, tightly packed fire pit capable of holding high amounts of wood at once. Provides hefty warmth and light to thronerooms and halls alike and acts as a gathering spot for idle colonists.</VFEV_Hearth.description>
  <VFEV_FuneralPyre.label>funeral pyre</VFEV_FuneralPyre.label>
  <VFEV_FuneralPyre.description>A ceremonial pile of wood, temporarily erected to perform honorable funerals.</VFEV_FuneralPyre.description>
  <VFEV_PlantGrowerArtifact.label>psychic cornucopia</VFEV_PlantGrowerArtifact.label>
  <VFEV_PlantGrowerArtifact.description>A mysterious, single-use artifact which grows all plants nearby to maturity when activated. Created by a superior AI, it served as a gift to humanity long ago.</VFEV_PlantGrowerArtifact.description>
  <VFEV_LothurrAntler.label>lothurr antler</VFEV_LothurrAntler.label>
  <VFEV_LothurrAntler.description>An antler of a Lothurr. Incredibly heavy and priceless in most markets. This is a true trophy, as well as a deadly blunt weapon.</VFEV_LothurrAntler.description>
  <VFEV_LothurrAntler.tools.0.label>edge</VFEV_LothurrAntler.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_LothurrAntler.tools.1.label>base</VFEV_LothurrAntler.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Sweetroll.label>sweetroll</VFEV_Sweetroll.label>
  <VFEV_Sweetroll.description>A baked treat made of an eggy bread base drizzled with a thick, sweetened glaze. Any trader selling these should be immediately concerned, as sweetrolls have a knack for being stolen.</VFEV_Sweetroll.description>
  <VFEV_Honey.label>raw honey</VFEV_Honey.label>
  <VFEV_Honey.description>Raw, unprocessed honey harvested from an apiary, very sugary and fun to eat while also extremely long-lasting, perfect for taking on caravan trips, fermenting into mead, or baking into desserts.</VFEV_Honey.description>
  <VFEV_Leather_Fenrir.label>fenrirskin</VFEV_Leather_Fenrir.label>
  <VFEV_Leather_Fenrir.description>A ragged, furry pelt harvested from a fenrir. It is extremely difficult to pierce and is quite long-lasting, perfect for armor. Fetches a high price on the market.</VFEV_Leather_Fenrir.description>
  <VFEV_Leather_Lothurr.label>lothurr leather</VFEV_Leather_Lothurr.label>
  <VFEV_Leather_Lothurr.description>The shiny pelt of a lothurr. Luxurious, smooth, and has a shimmering shine to it. Used in many crafts and furnishings, primarily for aesthetics.</VFEV_Leather_Lothurr.description>
  <VFEV_Leather_Njorun.label>njorunfur</VFEV_Leather_Njorun.label>
  <VFEV_Leather_Njorun.description>The thick pelt of njorun. Similar in colour to muffalo pelt, it is much softer and far rarer. Absurdly good at temperature regulation in cold climates.</VFEV_Leather_Njorun.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_GuardianHelmet.label>guardian helmet</VFEV_Apparel_GuardianHelmet.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_GuardianHelmet.description>A strong medieval helmet that provides full-head coverage. While it offers fantastic protection, ones vision is grealy obscured, thus it is only recommended for front line infantry, particularly those foregoing shields.</VFEV_Apparel_GuardianHelmet.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_LeatherHelmet.label>leather helmet</VFEV_Apparel_LeatherHelmet.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_LeatherHelmet.description>A lightweight medieval helmet meant for stropping bladed weapon and animal attacks, notably leaves ones chin and jaw exposed. Not effective against blunt weapons.</VFEV_Apparel_LeatherHelmet.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RavagerHelmet.label>ravager helmet</VFEV_Apparel_RavagerHelmet.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RavagerHelmet.description>A simple metallic helmet designed to not block ones communication during combat. Often worn by front line, shield-wielding infantry to soak damage.</VFEV_Apparel_RavagerHelmet.description>
  <VFEV_MooseHeaddress.label>moose headdress</VFEV_MooseHeaddress.label>
  <VFEV_MooseHeaddress.description>A very heavy, albeit fragile helmet stitched together from many hides and furs made to represent a hardy moose. This shamanistic headdress is believed to bring great durability and tenacity to it's wearer. Due to the simple design, this helmet does not offer defense or insulation.</VFEV_MooseHeaddress.description>
  <VFEV_BearHeaddress.label>bear headdress</VFEV_BearHeaddress.label>
  <VFEV_BearHeaddress.description>A very heavy, albeit fragile helmet stitched together from many hides and furs made to represent a ferocious bear. This shamanistic headdress is believed to bring great aggression and strength to it's wearer. Due to the simple design, this helmet does not offer defense or insulation.</VFEV_BearHeaddress.description>
  <VFEV_JarlCrown.label>jarl crown</VFEV_JarlCrown.label>
  <VFEV_JarlCrown.description>A grand crown worthy of nordic leaders. As a symbol of status, it requires the antlers of a legendary Lothurr.</VFEV_JarlCrown.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_GuardianArmor.label>guardian armor</VFEV_Apparel_GuardianArmor.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_GuardianArmor.description>A heavy, metallic breastplate meant to provide warmth and protection to heavy infantry during battles in frigid tundras. Unfortunately, this armor leaves one slowed and more vulnerable to melee attacks.</VFEV_Apparel_GuardianArmor.description>
  <VFEV_LeatherArmor.label>leather armor</VFEV_LeatherArmor.label>
  <VFEV_LeatherArmor.description>Flexible, medium-thickness leather armor made from squares of animal hide. Meant to be worn under a pelt cloak or parka, offers suitable protection for light combat without restricting movement, making it a favorite of archers and scouts.</VFEV_LeatherArmor.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RavagerArmor.label>ravager armor</VFEV_Apparel_RavagerArmor.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RavagerArmor.description>Much heavier than its leather armor cousin, this armor is made much more carefully and tightly out of processed leathers. Intended to be worn by front-line troops and often accompanied by a shield.</VFEV_Apparel_RavagerArmor.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_JarlCape.label>jarl cape</VFEV_Apparel_JarlCape.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_JarlCape.description>A painstakingly sewn cloak topped with a broad, furry mantle and ornate clasp. Satisfies even the highest ranks of royalty and offers surprising amounts of insulation, even down to the legs.</VFEV_Apparel_JarlCape.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RoyalFurCoat.label>noble fur coat</VFEV_Apparel_RoyalFurCoat.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_RoyalFurCoat.description>An intently woven series of pelts then strapped together tightly with cured animal sinew, quite pleasing to wear even for nobility.</VFEV_Apparel_RoyalFurCoat.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoArmor.label>crypto armor</VFEV_CryptoArmor.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoArmor.description>Low-powered plasteel carapace armor draped with an unknown but impossibly durable cloth sash affixed over one shoulder, the armor emits a low electrical hum and feels smooth to the touch. The power supply itself features embedded cryptocasket technology and will use a stasis effect to slow ones bleeding.</VFEV_CryptoArmor.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyArmor.label>crypto heavy armor</VFEV_CryptoHeavyArmor.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyArmor.description>Heavy, high-powered plasteel plate armor affixed with an unknown but impossibly durable cloth cowl, the armor emits a low electrical hum and feels smooth to the touch. The power supply itself features embedded cryptocasket technology and will use a stasis effect to slow ones bleeding.</VFEV_CryptoHeavyArmor.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_CryptoLightHelmet.label>crypto helmet</VFEV_Apparel_CryptoLightHelmet.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_CryptoLightHelmet.description>A lower-powered helmet with an unknown but impossibly durable cloth hood. It's theorized that either a long-lost or far-advanced civilizations scout troopers would adorn this helmet before recon missions during the mechanoid wars. The helmet itself features embedded cryptocasket technology and will use a stasis effect to slow ones bleeding.</VFEV_Apparel_CryptoLightHelmet.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_CryptoHeavyHelmet.label>heavy crypto helmet</VFEV_Apparel_CryptoHeavyHelmet.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_CryptoHeavyHelmet.description>A heavy, high-powered helmet complete with an embedded HUD system and diagnostics display. It's theorized that either a long-lost or far-advanced civilizations shock troopers would adorn this helmet before strike missions during the mechanoid wars. The helmet itself features embedded cryptocasket technology and will use a stasis effect to slow ones bleeding.</VFEV_Apparel_CryptoHeavyHelmet.description>
  <VFEV_Shield_Round.tools.0.label>base</VFEV_Shield_Round.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Round.tools.1.label>centre</VFEV_Shield_Round.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Round.label>round shield</VFEV_Shield_Round.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Round.description>A wooden shield held together with a metal band, finished off with a leather inset to protect from rain. A leather strap and metal handle are also present on the back to allow for easy one-handed maneuvering during combat.</VFEV_Shield_Round.description>
  <VFEV_Shield_Crypto.tools.0.label>base</VFEV_Shield_Crypto.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Crypto.tools.1.label>centre</VFEV_Shield_Crypto.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Crypto.label>crypto shield</VFEV_Shield_Crypto.label>
  <VFEV_Shield_Crypto.description>A stabilized crypto-tech field wrapped around an advanced frame, capable of slowing the speed of the atoms of incoming projectiles to a halt. Does nothing to protect against heat and blunt trauma.</VFEV_Shield_Crypto.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.label>throwable torch belt</VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.label>
  <VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.description>A belt with a number of wooden torches strapped to it. They can be lit up and thrown to set things ablaze. Can be refueled with wood.</VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.description>
  <VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.verbs.0.label>throw torch</VFEV_Apparel_TorchBelt.verbs.0.label>
  <VFEV_Proj_GrenadeTorch.label>thrown torch</VFEV_Proj_GrenadeTorch.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.label>seax</VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.description>A stout bladed weapon adapted for use among northern clans. Because it can be swung quite rapidly and easily, it is favored among those first learning swordsmanship.</VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.description>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.0.label>handle</VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.1.label>point</VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.1.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.2.label>edge</VFE_MeleeWeapon_Seax.tools.2.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.label>bearded axe</VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.description>A form of one of mankind's oldest weapons. The "beard" of the axe extends downwards, providing wider cutting edge.\n\nThis weapon has a chance to deal a critical strike, stunning the opponent.</VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.description>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.tools.0.label>handle</VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.tools.1.label>edge</VFE_MeleeWeapon_BeardedAxe.tools.1.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.label>dane axe</VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.description>A mighty weapon on the battlefield in the right kind of hands. Made to cut through flesh and bones alike. The axe edge extends into what's called horns, ideal for cutting through light armor and flesh alike.\n\nThis weapon has a chance to deal a critical strike, stunning the opponent.</VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.description>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.tools.0.label>handle</VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.tools.1.label>edge</VFE_MeleeWeapon_DaneAxe.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.label>heavy crypto axe</VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.description>A two-handed, high-tech axe of unknown origin with an icy cold alloy edge. Crypto weapons are laced with what appears to be a cryogenic coating along their blade, targets struck by them without proper insulation may feel themselves crippled by hypothermia.</VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.tools.0.label>pommel</VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.tools.1.label>blade</VFEV_CryptoHeavyAxe.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.label>crypto hatchet</VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.description>An easily swung, high-tech hatchet of unknown origin with an icy cold alloy edge. Crypto weapons are laced with what appears to be a cryogenic coating along their blade, targets struck by them without proper insulation may feel themselves crippled by hypothermia.</VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.tools.0.label>pommel</VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.tools.1.label>blade</VFEV_CryptoLightAxe.tools.1.label>
  <VFE_ThrowingAxe.label>throwing axe</VFE_ThrowingAxe.label>
  <VFE_ThrowingAxe.description>A single-handed axe made for throwing. Light enough to be thrown accurately at medium range, it's also a great melee weapon in the hands of a capable warrior.</VFE_ThrowingAxe.description>
  <VFE_ThrowingAxe.tools.0.label>handle</VFE_ThrowingAxe.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_ThrowingAxe.tools.1.label>blade</VFE_ThrowingAxe.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_ThrowingAxe_Thrown.label>thrown axe</VFEV_ThrowingAxe_Thrown.label>
  <VFE_Harpoon.label>harpoon</VFE_Harpoon.label>
  <VFE_Harpoon.description>A long spear-like weapon usually used in fishing and hunting. Can be thrown over a very long distance and has a significant stopping power. This weapon represents a bundle of harpoons and can be thrown over and over.</VFE_Harpoon.description>
  <VFE_Harpoon.tools.0.label>handle</VFE_Harpoon.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_Harpoon.tools.1.label>point</VFE_Harpoon.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Harpoon_Thrown.label>thrown harpoon</VFEV_Harpoon_Thrown.label>
  <VFEV_OrbitalTargeterMjollnir.label>mjollnir strike targeter</VFEV_OrbitalTargeterMjollnir.label>
  <VFEV_OrbitalTargeterMjollnir.description>An ancient targeting apparatus for long forgotten Mjollnir sattelite. This unit designates a target and transmits the coordinates to a targeting relay, which then generates localised electricity discharge around the target. This unit has been reprogrammed to accept unauthorized users, but once it is used, the network will detect the incursion and cut off the link permanently.</VFEV_OrbitalTargeterMjollnir.description>
  <VFEV_LightningStrike.label>lightning strike</VFEV_LightningStrike.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.label>crypto heavy crossbow</VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.description>Less of a crossbow and more of an experimental artillery piece, fires metal-cored bolts wrapped in unstable crypto technology, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both pierced by the bolt, as well as frozen by crypto coating. Due to its weight, it is unable to be fired at close range and will slightly slow down the wielder.</VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.tools.0.label>stock</VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.tools.1.label>barrel</VFEV_CryptoHeavyCrossbow.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_HeavyCryptoBolt.label>crypto bolt</VFEV_HeavyCryptoBolt.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.label>crypto crossbow</VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.description>An experimental small crossbow with metal-cored bolts wrapped in unstable crypto technology, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both pierced by the bolt, as well as frozen by crypto coating. Able to be fired single-handedly, extremely rare and powerful.</VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.tools.0.label>butt</VFEV_CryptoLightCrossbow.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoBolt.label>crypto bolt</VFEV_CryptoBolt.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoPistol.label>crypto pistol</VFEV_CryptoPistol.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoPistol.description>An experimental micro pistol with metal-cored projectiles wrapped in unstable crypto technology, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both pierced by the metal core, as well as frozen by crypto coating. Extremely rare and powerful.</VFEV_CryptoPistol.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoPistol.tools.0.label>grip</VFEV_CryptoPistol.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoPistolBullet.label>crypto bullet</VFEV_CryptoPistolBullet.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoRifle.label>crypto rifle</VFEV_CryptoRifle.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoRifle.description>An experimental rifle with metal-cored projectiles wrapped in unstable crypto technology, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both pierced by the metal core, as well as frozen by crypto coating. Extremely rare and powerful.</VFEV_CryptoRifle.description>
  <VFEV_CryptoRifle.tools.0.label>stock</VFEV_CryptoRifle.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoRifle.tools.1.label>barrel</VFEV_CryptoRifle.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_CryptoRifleBullet.label>crypto bullet</VFEV_CryptoRifleBullet.label>
  <VFEV_WoolyCow.label>wooly cow</VFEV_WoolyCow.label>
  <VFEV_WoolyCow.description>A large domesticated ungulate, cows have been bred for millennia to produce huge amounts of milk, meat, and leather. This breed originates in the hilly areas and can be differentiated by long horns and a shaggy coat. They are exceptionally gentle creatures and will never seek revenge, no matter how many times they are harmed. Most of them are so adapted to farm life that they cannot survive in the wild.</VFEV_WoolyCow.description>
  <VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.1.label>head</VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.2.label>left hoof</VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.2.label>
  <VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.3.label>right hoof</VFEV_WoolyCow.tools.3.label>
  <VFEV_WoolCow.label>cow wool</VFEV_WoolCow.label>
  <VFEV_WoolCow.description>Cow's wool. It provides a decent amount of insulation.</VFEV_WoolCow.description>
  <VFEV_Fenrir.label>fenrir</VFEV_Fenrir.label>
  <VFEV_Fenrir.description>A gigantic, deadly wolf of unknown origin. The fenrir is aggressive by nature and extremely dangerous when enraged. Its fur and hide is incredibly resistant to damage and cold, while it's razor-sharp teeths can pierce even the best armour.\n\nLegends say that fenrir were bioengineered in ancient times for war and only follow the bravest leader's into combat.</VFEV_Fenrir.description>
  <VFEV_Fenrir.tools.0.label>left claw</VFEV_Fenrir.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Fenrir.tools.1.label>right claw</VFEV_Fenrir.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Fenrir.tools.3.label>head</VFEV_Fenrir.tools.3.label>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.label>lothurr</VFEV_Lothurr.label>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.description>A gigantic, dragon-like creature of unknown origin. The lothurr is peaceful by nature, but extremely dangerous when enraged. Its fur and armour plates are incredibly resistant to damage and cold, while it's majestic antlers fetch a huge price.\n\nMany legends surround the lothurrs. Some say it is the manifestation of the old nordic gods while others claim they are a truly alien species, other tall tales claim the beast is able to vanish and rapidly reappear elsewhere at will.</VFEV_Lothurr.description>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.tools.0.label>horns</VFEV_Lothurr.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.tools.2.label>left foot</VFEV_Lothurr.tools.2.label>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.tools.3.label>right foot</VFEV_Lothurr.tools.3.label>
  <VFEV_Lothurr.tools.4.label>head</VFEV_Lothurr.tools.4.label>
  <VFEV_Njorun.label>njorun</VFEV_Njorun.label>
  <VFEV_Njorun.description>A gigantic, ox-like creature of unknown origin. The njorun is wary by nature, traveling the planet in small herds and staying hidden from anyone who might wish it harm. Though docile, the beast is far too skittish to be tamed and is likely to retaliate if attacked.\n\n Legends say the njoruns are the result of breeding by long gone corporations in an attempt to create the perfect animal to breed for profits.</VFEV_Njorun.description>
  <VFEV_Njorun.tools.0.label>horns</VFEV_Njorun.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Njorun.tools.2.label>left foot</VFEV_Njorun.tools.2.label>
  <VFEV_Njorun.tools.3.label>right foot</VFEV_Njorun.tools.3.label>
  <VFEV_Njorun.tools.4.label>head</VFEV_Njorun.tools.4.label>
  <VFEV_Wolfhound.label>wolfhound</VFEV_Wolfhound.label>
  <VFEV_Wolfhound.description>A large, energetic dog with a thick, brown fur coat for remaining comfortable in arctic environments. Thought to be an evolutionary hybrid of wolf and hound bred for hunting.</VFEV_Wolfhound.description>
  <VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.0.label>left claw</VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.1.label>right claw</VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.3.label>head</VFEV_Wolfhound.tools.3.label>
  <VFEV_Mech_Odin.label>odin</VFEV_Mech_Odin.label>
  <VFEV_Mech_Odin.description>A monolothic, fortified mechanoid theorized to have the ability to cause lightning strikes through envirionmental manipulation and static discharge. Serrated, bladed arms are paired alongside EMP pulse resonators capable of disabling nearby electronics. Those brave enough to fight this mechanoid at point blank range are swiftly dispatched by high-voltage lightning strikes.\n\nDuring the mechanoid wars, the Odin's very sighting is known to usher in demand for retreat. Very few have encountered it and survived long enough to report back.</VFEV_Mech_Odin.description>
  <VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.0.label>left fist</VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.0.label>
  <VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.1.label>right fist</VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.1.label>
  <VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.2.label>head</VFEV_Mech_Odin.tools.2.label>
</LanguageData>