<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PsychicSensitizer.label>psychic sensitizer</PsychicSensitizer.label>
  <PsychicSensitizer.description>This brain implant stimulates growth in the regions of the brain related to psychic interaction, thus increasing psychic sensitivity.</PsychicSensitizer.description>
  <PsychicHarmonizer.label>psychic harmonizer</PsychicHarmonizer.label>
  <PsychicHarmonizer.description>This brain implant projects the user's mood in a spherical psychic field, forcing others nearby to feel a blurred, simplified version of their emotions. It can be a powerful tool to keep morale high, but if the user becomes unhappy, it can lead to collective disaster.</PsychicHarmonizer.description>
  <PsychicReader.label>psychic reader</PsychicReader.label>
  <PsychicReader.description>Gives limited mind-reading ability, improving the user's ability to get the upper hand in negotiations and social situations. The effect is proportional to the user's psychic sensitivity.</PsychicReader.description>
  <Neurocalculator.label>neurocalculator</Neurocalculator.label>
  <Neurocalculator.description>A non-intelligent microcomputer controlled by a visual/tactile neural interface. It assists with memory and calculation, like a calculator and notepad embedded in the brain.</Neurocalculator.description>
  <LearningAssistant.label>learning assistant</LearningAssistant.label>
  <LearningAssistant.description>A sensory recording system that replays important experiences during sleep, strengthening the formation of new memories.</LearningAssistant.description>
  <GastroAnalyzer.label>gastro-analyzer</GastroAnalyzer.label>
  <GastroAnalyzer.description>This bionic nose implant enhances the sense of smell, with a focus towards food-related smells. A multi-layered ultrafine absorption mesh detects compounds in the air. A microprocessor formats the readings into an olfactory nerve signal to send to the brain through a nerve-link interface. The result is that the user can smell foods with a depth, richness, and precision unknown among unenhanced humans, allowing them to cook more effectively. The whole unit is small enough to be installed in the nose without affecting the user's appearance.</GastroAnalyzer.description>
  <Immunoenhancer.label>immunoenhancer</Immunoenhancer.label>
  <Immunoenhancer.description>An analysis computer inspects the bloodstream, classifies pathogens, and rapidly prompts the body's natural immune system to respond to them faster than it could alone. This speeds immunity gain significantly.</Immunoenhancer.description>
  <Coagulator.label>coagulator</Coagulator.label>
  <Coagulator.description>Releases coagulating factors in response to blood loss, reducing bleeding rates significantly.</Coagulator.description>
  <HealingEnhancer.label>healing enhancer</HealingEnhancer.label>
  <HealingEnhancer.description>Releases nanomachines and healing factors that speed up wound healing. This implant only helps with physical wounds, and does nothing to combat disease or other health problems.</HealingEnhancer.description>
  <ToughskinGland.label>toughskin gland</ToughskinGland.label>
  <ToughskinGland.description>This bionic gland releases chemicals and nanomachines that toughen the skin, making it somewhat more resistant to damage. While it doesn't add as much protection as some other skin-hardening glands, the toughskin gland has the advantage of not noticeably altering the user's appearance.</ToughskinGland.description>
  <ArmorskinGland.label>armorskin gland</ArmorskinGland.label>
  <ArmorskinGland.description>This bionic gland releases chemicals and nanomachines that toughen the skin and add flexible subdermal keratin plates at strategic points. This makes the user more resistant to damage across their whole body. Unfortunately, these changes make the skin appear leathery, with wrinkles across the whole body and face, which is generally considered ugly.</ArmorskinGland.description>
  <StoneskinGland.label>stoneskin gland</StoneskinGland.label>
  <StoneskinGland.description>This bionic gland releases chemical and nanomachines that transform the user's skin into a built-in suit of armor. The whole epidermis thickens and hardens to resist burns, while jointed exterior keratin plates form everywhere they can - including the head and face. While it's very difficult to physically hurt someone using this implant, the plates and hard skin significantly reduces the user's physical attractiveness.</StoneskinGland.description>
  <AestheticShaper.label>aesthetic shaper</AestheticShaper.label>
  <AestheticShaper.description>A sophisticated package of hormonal and mechanite influences shapes the muscles and fat on the body, adding non-functional aesthetic tissue where needed to achieve a desired appearance. This implant can be configured to form various body shapes according to the user's taste - or that of their partner.</AestheticShaper.description>
  <AestheticNose.label>aesthetic nose</AestheticNose.label>
  <AestheticNose.description>The nose is shaped to the user's desired form, matching prevalent beauty standards and enhancing physical impressions.</AestheticNose.description>
  <LoveEnhancer.label>love enhancer</LoveEnhancer.label>
  <LoveEnhancer.description>Humans have always tried to use every new technology to enhance sexual satisfaction. Bionics were no exception. This implant makes physical and chemical changes to the body which enhance the experience of lovin' for both partners - both physically and psychologically. The implant unit can adapt to enhance both men and women upon being implanted.</LoveEnhancer.description>
  <DetoxifierStomach.label>detoxifier stomach</DetoxifierStomach.label>
  <DetoxifierStomach.description>An artificial stomach replacement with a broad-spectrum toxin filter and neutralization system. It allows the user to eat almost anything without ever worrying about food poisoning.</DetoxifierStomach.description>
  <ReprocessorStomach.label>reprocessor stomach</ReprocessorStomach.label>
  <ReprocessorStomach.description>An advanced chemical processing system breaks down nutrients the body could normally never use, leading to increased efficiency.</ReprocessorStomach.description>
  <NuclearStomach.label>nuclear stomach</NuclearStomach.label>
  <NuclearStomach.description>A micro-nuclear reactor combined with complex chemical synthesis replaces the body's need for food energy. Food is required only to replace matter lost from the body, reducing the user's intake needs significantly. This artificial stomach cannot get food poisoning. However, there is little room to shield the reactor, so the radiation increases the risk of cancer.</NuclearStomach.description>
  <CircadianAssistant.label>circadian assistant</CircadianAssistant.label>
  <CircadianAssistant.description>An artificial gland. Produces chemicals and nanomachines that clear toxin buildup from the brain.</CircadianAssistant.description>
  <CircadianHalfCycler.label>circadian half-cycler</CircadianHalfCycler.label>
  <CircadianHalfCycler.description>A signal redirector which isolates half of the brain, allowing the other half to sleep while the user remains outwardly awake. By alternating brain halves, the user never needs to sleep. Unfortunately, two hemispheres are better than one - working with half a brain causes a reduction in consciousness.</CircadianHalfCycler.description>
  <Mindscrew.label>mindscrew</Mindscrew.label>
  <Mindscrew.description>Inflicts continuous pain on the user. Mindscrews are used by some authorities as a long-term punishment. Some even install them voluntarily as a demonstration of ideological or religious devotion.</Mindscrew.description>
  <DrillArm.label>drill arm</DrillArm.label>
  <DrillArm.description>A mechanical arm replacement for speeding up mining. It has a built-in snake drill, which allows the miner to rapidly find and exploit weak lines in the rock. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</DrillArm.description>
  <FieldHand.label>field hand</FieldHand.label>
  <FieldHand.description>This mechanical hand replacement is made to speed up the sowing and harvesting tasks of a farmer. Multiple telescoping finger-like protrusions can simultaneously harvest from several points on the same plant, or precisely sow several holes at once. It also has a general-purpose manipulator. It is somewhat ungainly, which slows down movement slightly.</FieldHand.description>
  <HandTalon.label>hand talon</HandTalon.label>
  <HandTalon.description>A razor-sharp talon which extends from a hidden opening between the middle and ring fingers. The talon is longer than the palm, but it becomes flexible upon retracting, allowing the user to curl it up and conceal it inside the hand. It can perform rapid slashing attacks, but is poor at penetrating armor.</HandTalon.description>
  <ElbowBlade.label>elbow blade</ElbowBlade.label>
  <ElbowBlade.description>A razor-sharp blade that extends at will from a hidden opening at the end of the ulna. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating slice attacks.</ElbowBlade.description>
  <KneeSpike.label>knee spike</KneeSpike.label>
  <KneeSpike.description>A spike that extends at will from a hidden opening on the front of the knee. Appearing without warning, it can be used for devastating stabbing attacks which penetrate even thick armor.</KneeSpike.description>
  <VenomFangs.label>venom fangs</VenomFangs.label>
  <VenomFangs.description>A pair of injectors implanted through the canine teeth, connected to a venom pump. The user can bite an enemy, extend the injectors, and pump venom into the target.</VenomFangs.description>
  <VenomTalon.label>venom talon</VenomTalon.label>
  <VenomTalon.description>A retractable finger talon connected to a venom pump in the lower arm. The user can scratch an enemy while squirting venom into the wound. The talon is designed to be installed in the middle finger. It's fast, but poor at penetrating armor.</VenomTalon.description>
  <PsychicAmplifier.label>psylink neuroformer</PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <PsychicAmplifier.description>A consumable archotech-created device that forms or upgrades a psylink in the user's mind.\n\nThe user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into worthless ash.</PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <PsychicAmplifier.comps.0.useLabel>Use neuroformer to form psylink</PsychicAmplifier.comps.0.useLabel>
  <SunBlocker.label>sun blocker</SunBlocker.label>
  <SunBlocker.description>An ultratech machine that generates a sheet of exotic fields at high altitude, turning the sky opaque and blocking the sun.</SunBlocker.description>
  <SmokeSpewer.label>smoke spewer</SmokeSpewer.label>
  <SmokeSpewer.description>An ultratech weapon of mass destruction designed for area denial. By harvesting available compounds and converting them into self-reproducing opaque molecules, it can spew enough smoke to block the sun in a whole region of the planet.</SmokeSpewer.description>
  <ToxicSpewer.label>toxic spewer</ToxicSpewer.label>
  <ToxicSpewer.description>An ultratech weapon of mass destruction designed for area denial. This device harvests available compounds and converts them into self-reproducing poisons. By spewing these into the atmosphere, it can poison a whole region of the planet.</ToxicSpewer.description>
  <WeatherController.label>weather controller</WeatherController.label>
  <WeatherController.description>An ultratech device for controlling weather. Using chemicals and exotic fields, it forces the weather into a particular configuration.</WeatherController.description>
  <ClimateAdjuster.label>climate adjuster</ClimateAdjuster.label>
  <ClimateAdjuster.description>An ultratech device for controlling climate. Using chemicals and exotic fields to manipulate the atmosphere, it shifts the temperature in this region of the world.</ClimateAdjuster.description>
  <PsychicDroner.label>psychic droner</PsychicDroner.label>
  <PsychicDroner.description>An archotech device transmitting the thoughts of a mad superintelligence. It generates a massive psychic drone tuned to one gender and affecting a whole region of the planet. People of that gender will be disturbed by the effect, reducing their mood and possibly driving them insane. The effect is modulated by an individual's psychic sensitivity.</PsychicDroner.description>
  <PsychicSuppressor.label>psychic suppressor</PsychicSuppressor.label>
  <PsychicSuppressor.description>An archotech device that generates a massive psychic suppression field tuned to a particular gender. People of that gender have their psychic activity suppressed, reducing their consciousness. The effect is modulated by an individual's psychic sensitivity.</PsychicSuppressor.description>
  <EMIDynamo.label>EMI dynamo</EMIDynamo.label>
  <EMIDynamo.description>A massive electromagnetic interference generator. It interferes with or shuts down electrical devices in nearby regions.</EMIDynamo.description>
  <Shuttle.label>shuttle</Shuttle.label>
  <Shuttle.description>A spacer-tech shuttle designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</Shuttle.description>
  <ShuttleCrashed.label>crashed shuttle</ShuttleCrashed.label>
  <ShuttleCrashed.description>A spacer-tech shuttle designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</ShuttleCrashed.description>
  <BroadshieldProjector.label>burnout low-shield</BroadshieldProjector.label>
  <BroadshieldProjector.description>A man-portable low-angle shield projector. Bullets can go out, but not in. Its compact power source burns out after a few seconds of use.</BroadshieldProjector.description>
  <BroadshieldProjector.comps.1.countdownLabel>Burnout in</BroadshieldProjector.comps.1.countdownLabel>
  <Drape.label>drape</Drape.label>
  <Drape.description>A decorative sheet hanging from a vertical wooden frame. Appropriate for royal rooms.</Drape.description>
  <Brazier.label>brazier</Brazier.label>
  <Brazier.description>A bowl-shaped furnishing used to hold a fire. Will light the surroundings and create heat.</Brazier.description>
  <Throne.label>meditation throne</Throne.label>
  <Throne.description>A large, ornate chair designed for a dignity-focused psycaster to sit and meditate. Reigning on a throne is a form of meditation that builds up psyfocus. For dignity psycasters, more impressive meditation thrones and thronerooms increase the rate of psyfocus gain.</Throne.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>grand meditation throne</GrandThrone.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>A massive, ornate chair, designed for a dignity-focused psycaster to sit and meditate. Reigning on a throne is a form of meditation that builds up psyfocus. For dignity psycasters, more impressive meditation thrones and thronerooms increase the rate of psyfocus gain.</GrandThrone.description>
  <UnstablePowerCell.label>unstable power cell</UnstablePowerCell.label>
  <UnstablePowerCell.description>A mechanoid power generation unit. The vanometric power core will run forever, extracting energy from quantum foam fluctuations.\n\nAn internal amplifier system makes it unstable. If damaged, the unit will generate a massive explosion.\n\nSome brave humans steal these from mechanoids for their own use as power plants or defensive bombs. However, an unintentional detonation can be devastating.</UnstablePowerCell.description>
  <Gloomlight.label>mech node</Gloomlight.label>
  <Gloomlight.description>A self-powered mechanoid node of unknown function. Mech nodes can be deconstructed to yield valuable resources - but only if they are captured intact. The internal micro power cell will flame out and ruin the materials if the unit takes too much damage.</Gloomlight.description>
  <Defoliator.label>defoliator</Defoliator.label>
  <Defoliator.description>An area-denial device which annihilates nearby plants without affecting animals.\n\nIn planetary wars, these weapons are scattered across farmlands or jungles to deny the enemy food or cover. They're usually associated with orbital-drop mechanoid swarms.</Defoliator.description>
  <ActivatorCountdown.label>count-down activator</ActivatorCountdown.label>
  <ActivatorCountdown.description>A timed mechanoid activation unit. After counting down, it will wake nearby dormant mechanoids and structures.</ActivatorCountdown.description>
  <ActivatorProximity.label>proximity activator</ActivatorProximity.label>
  <ActivatorProximity.description>A proximity alarm for dormant mechanoids. If it detects a human-like threat nearby, it will awaken any nearby dormant mechanoids or structures.</ActivatorProximity.description>
  <ShieldGeneratorMortar.label>mech high-shield</ShieldGeneratorMortar.label>
  <ShieldGeneratorMortar.description>A shielding device which projects a momentum repulsor field. Shots can go out, but not in.\n\nThis one is tuned to high angles, so it will block mortar rounds.\n\nThe unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield.</ShieldGeneratorMortar.description>
  <ShieldGeneratorBullets.label>mech low-shield</ShieldGeneratorBullets.label>
  <ShieldGeneratorBullets.description>A shielding device which projects a momentum repulsor field. Shots can go out, but not in.\n\nThis one is tuned to low angles, so it will block ground-level projectiles like bullets.\n\nThe unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield.</ShieldGeneratorBullets.description>
  <MechCapsule.label>mech capsule</MechCapsule.label>
  <MechCapsule.description>A mechanoid storage and deployment capsule. It can contain a number of mechanoids, ready to emerge and fight upon being awakened.</MechCapsule.description>
  <MechAssembler.label>mech assembler</MechAssembler.label>
  <MechAssembler.description>An automated mechanoid factory. It periodically assembles and deploys new mechanoids.</MechAssembler.description>
  <MechDropBeacon.label>mech drop beacon</MechDropBeacon.label>
  <MechDropBeacon.description>A mechanoid reinforcement drop beacon. When activated, it calls in a group of mechs to land in drop pods nearby.</MechDropBeacon.description>
  <Turret_AutoMiniTurret.label>mini-slugger turret</Turret_AutoMiniTurret.label>
  <Turret_AutoMiniTurret.description>A self-powered defense turret mounted with a weak but long-ranged slug-thrower. May explode when damaged.</Turret_AutoMiniTurret.description>
  <Gun_MiniTurretMech.label>mini-slugger</Gun_MiniTurretMech.label>
  <Gun_MiniTurretMech.description>An automatic turret-mounted slug-thrower.</Gun_MiniTurretMech.description>
  <Bullet_MiniSlug.label>mini-slug</Bullet_MiniSlug.label>
  <Turret_AutoChargeBlaster.label>auto charge turret</Turret_AutoChargeBlaster.label>
  <Turret_AutoChargeBlaster.description>A self-powered turret mounted with a charge blaster. It cannot sense targets at very short ranges.</Turret_AutoChargeBlaster.description>
  <Gun_ChargeBlasterHeavyTurret.label>light charge blaster</Gun_ChargeBlasterHeavyTurret.label>
  <Gun_ChargeBlasterHeavyTurret.description>A pulse-charged rapid-fire blaster for area fire.</Gun_ChargeBlasterHeavyTurret.description>
  <Turret_AutoInferno.label>auto inferno turret</Turret_AutoInferno.label>
  <Turret_AutoInferno.description>A self-powered turret mounted with an inferno cannon. It cannot sense targets at very short ranges.</Turret_AutoInferno.description>
  <Turret_AutoMortar.label>auto mortar</Turret_AutoMortar.label>
  <Turret_AutoMortar.description>A self-powered, self-loading, automatic mortar. It can hit targets at any distance, over walls, but is quite inaccurate.</Turret_AutoMortar.description>
  <Artillery_AutoMortar.label>auto-mortar</Artillery_AutoMortar.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>ship landing beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.description>Marks the corner of a landing area. Four of these placed at the corners of a clear area (minimum 9x9) create a landing pad. Spacecraft usually land on pads if possible.</ShipLandingBeacon.description>
  <MeditationSpot.label>meditation spot</MeditationSpot.label>
  <MeditationSpot.description>Designates a spot for meditation. Psycasters can meditate here to gain psyfocus. If a focus object like a sculpture is nearby, the psycaster will be able to focus on it to boost their psyfocus gain. However, different people are able to use different focus objects.</MeditationSpot.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small nature shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine for honoring spiritual beings. Tribal psycasters can focus on this shrine while meditating to increase psyfocus gain. Nature shrines lose their power if they are close to artificial structures, so they are always built in nature. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large nature shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring spiritual beings. Tribal psycasters can focus on this shrine while meditating to increase psyfocus gain. Nature shrines lose their power if they are close to artificial structures, so they are always built in nature. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>animus stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <AnimusStone.description>An ancient jade stone marked with sacred tribal carvings. Tribal psycasters can focus on these stones during meditation to increase their psyfocus gain more than a typical nature shrine.\n\nDifferent tribal cultures tell different stories about these stones, but most agree that they were crafted by an ancient world spirit during a time of great power. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</AnimusStone.description>
  <Harp.label>harp</Harp.label>
  <Harp.description>A simple stationary musical instrument. A row of strings are stretched over a frame and plucked directly by a musician's fingers.\n\nIt can be crafted at a crafting spot or smithy.</Harp.description>
  <Harpsichord.label>harpsichord</Harpsichord.label>
  <Harpsichord.description>A complex stationary musical instrument crafted at a smithy. A musician touches a row of keys on the front of the instrument. Each key is attached to an internal mechanism which plucks one of a row of strings stretched over a wooden frame. While it permits more complex composition than the harp, its wooden construction and plucking mechanism limit its output volume and expressiveness.</Harpsichord.description>
  <UnfinishedPiano.label>unfinished piano</UnfinishedPiano.label>
  <UnfinishedPiano.description>An unfinished piano.</UnfinishedPiano.description>
  <Piano.label>piano</Piano.label>
  <Piano.description>An advanced stationary musical instrument. It is played by pressing a row of keys, which causes hammers to strike internal strings stretched over a steel frame. The hammer mechanism and high-tension strings allow the musician to play both very soft and very loud, making the piano a very expressive instrument.\n\nIt can be crafted at a smithy.</Piano.description>
  <BroadshieldCore.label>shield core</BroadshieldCore.label>
  <BroadshieldCore.description>A piece of ultratechnology that can generate a momentum-repulsor shield. This can't do anything on its own, but it is necessary to craft some other usable shield items.\n\nShield cores can be obtained by deconstructing mechanoid shield generators.</BroadshieldCore.description>
  <Apparel_PackJump.label>jump pack</Apparel_PackJump.label>
  <Apparel_PackJump.description>A single-person burst rocket for short-ranged flight. With its integrated harness and guidance assistant, the jump pack allows anyone to leap long distances at high speed, even over obstacles. It must be recharged after several uses.\n\nSome spacer tech militaries have melee combat specialists who use jump packs to bypass obstacles and rapidly close with the enemy.</Apparel_PackJump.description>
  <Apparel_PackJump.verbs.0.label>jump</Apparel_PackJump.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_PackBroadshield.label>low-shield pack</Apparel_PackBroadshield.label>
  <Apparel_PackBroadshield.description>A single-use man-portable low-shield projector. Deployed on the ground, it generates a circular shield that allows bullets out but not in. The unit is designed to last only a short time before burning out.\n\nMany ultratech combat squads owe their lives to a shield pack deployed at just the right time.</Apparel_PackBroadshield.description>
  <Apparel_PackBroadshield.verbs.0.label>deploy low-shield</Apparel_PackBroadshield.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>eltex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for psychic focusing. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>eltex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for psychic focusing. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>eltex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special psychic focusing materials. These enhance psychic sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>eltex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.description>A thin vest embedded with special psychic focusing materials. These enhance psychic sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.description>A long robe embedded with special psychic focusing materials. These enhance psychic sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>eltex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_ShirtRuffle.label>formal shirt</Apparel_ShirtRuffle.label>
  <Apparel_ShirtRuffle.description>A decorated formal shirt with buttons.</Apparel_ShirtRuffle.description>
  <Apparel_Corset.label>corset</Apparel_Corset.label>
  <Apparel_Corset.description>An embroidered corset with strong wire support to maintain a ladylike shape.</Apparel_Corset.description>
  <Apparel_VestRoyal.label>formal vest</Apparel_VestRoyal.label>
  <Apparel_VestRoyal.description>A vest embroidered with complex decorative designs.</Apparel_VestRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>prestige robe</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, flowing robe embroidered with complex decorative designs.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_HatLadies.label>ladies hat</Apparel_HatLadies.label>
  <Apparel_HatLadies.description>A decorative traditional hat with complex embroidery.</Apparel_HatLadies.description>
  <Apparel_HatTop.label>top hat</Apparel_HatTop.label>
  <Apparel_HatTop.description>A tall, stiff, shiny hat.</Apparel_HatTop.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>coronet</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A small crown-like piece of headwear made of metal.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>crown</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A crown of metal with an elaborate design.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_CrownStellic.label>stellic crown</Apparel_CrownStellic.label>
  <Apparel_CrownStellic.description>A grand crown of metal with an elaborate, overbearing design.</Apparel_CrownStellic.description>
  <Apparel_Cape.label>cape</Apparel_Cape.label>
  <Apparel_Cape.description>A long cape of elegant design. It hangs over one side of the torso.</Apparel_Cape.description>
  <Apparel_Beret.label>beret</Apparel_Beret.label>
  <Apparel_Beret.description>A soft, round, flat-crowned hat.</Apparel_Beret.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.label>prestige recon armor</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light partially-powered armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.label>prestige recon helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>prestige marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of powered armor. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>prestige marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>cataphract armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy powered armor, built for maximum protection at the cost of mobility. Heavy layered plasteel-weave plates with solid ablative coatings stop all but the most well-aimed or powerful attacks. Neuro-memetic assistors prevent the suit's massive weight from immobilizing the wearer entirely, but the suit is still quite cumbersome.\n\nArmor like this is used by imperial cataphracts to break heavily fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphract.label>cataphract helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphract.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.\n\nArmor like this is used by imperial cataphracts to break heavily fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>prestige cataphract armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>A suit of heavy powered armor, built for maximum protection at the cost of mobility. Heavy layered plasteel-weave plates with solid ablative coatings stop all but the most well-aimed or powerful attacks. Neuro-memetic assistors prevent the suit's massive weight from immobilizing the wearer entirely, but the suit is still quite cumbersome.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>prestige cataphract helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.\n\nExpensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded eltex threads also enhance the wearer's psychic sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>locust armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with an integrated burst rocket for short-ranged flight. Locust armor is slightly less protective than standard recon armor. Each jump consumes a burst of fuel, so the armor must be reloaded after several uses.\n\nUnlike most ultratech military units, locusts train primarily with melee weapons. They usually avoid static shootouts, preferring to jump straight into enemy fortifications and fight hand-to-hand. They do poorly in static defense or confined quarters, but excel in mixed cover or shipcracking operations.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.verbs.0.label>jump</Apparel_ArmorLocust.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>grenadier armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor with an integrated frag launcher on the shoulder. The armor is slightly less protective than standard marine armor. The launcher can only hold a limited amount of ammo and must be reloaded after use.\n\nGrenadiers usually specialize in breaching buildings or internal ship bulkheads. While not effective at very long range, grenadiers can be surprisingly deadly in confined quarters.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.verbs.0.label>launch frag grenade</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.verbs.0.label>
  <Proj_GrenadierGrenade.label>frag grenade</Proj_GrenadierGrenade.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.label>phoenix armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.description>A variant of cataphract armor with a shoulder-mounted flamebolt launcher. This armor is slightly less protective than standard cataphract armor against normal damage, but is especially flame-resistant. The flamebolt launcher has very limited ammo and must be reloaded after use.\n\nPhoenixes specialize in clearing out very confined spaces full of enemies, as in underground or shipborne operations. They can absorb hits while moving down a corridor, fill rooms with flame, and emerge from the smoke unscathed.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.verbs.0.label>launch incendiary</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPhoenix.verbs.0.label>
  <Proj_GrenadePhoenixFire.label>incendiary grenade</Proj_GrenadePhoenixFire.label>
  <Apparel_Gunlink.label>gunlink</Apparel_Gunlink.label>
  <Apparel_Gunlink.description>A targeting computer that helps the user aim. It detects and analyzes targets using infrared, visible, and millimeter-wave electromagnetic sensors. An onboard targeting computer displays firing solutions on a retinal projection. It offers no protection at all.</Apparel_Gunlink.description>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>shuttle (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>shuttle (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
  <ShuttleCrashing.label>shuttle (crashing)</ShuttleCrashing.label>
  <MonumentMarker.label>monument marker</MonumentMarker.label>
  <MonumentMarker.description>Marks the place where you intend to build a monument. Once placed, this cannot be moved.</MonumentMarker.description>
  <BulletShieldPsychic.label>skipshield</BulletShieldPsychic.label>
  <Flashstorm.label>flashstorm</Flashstorm.label>
  <SolarPinhole.label>solar pinhole</SolarPinhole.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>persona monosword</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword infused with mechanites that maintain a mono-molecular cutting edge. It cuts through even thick armor with ease, while its light weight and onboard persona permit extremely fast attacks.
\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.1.label>point</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.2.label>edge</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.tools.2.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>persona zeushammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. Upon impact, it blasts the target with an EMP burst in addition to the physical damage.
\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.tools.1.label>head</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>persona plasmasword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored sword with a cutting edge. Plasma is wrapped around the core, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both sliced by the metal core, as well as burned or ignited by the plasma sheath.
\nThis weapon has an onboard persona that can bond to only a single person. The wielder and intelligent weapon can synchronize their reflexes and attack with frightening speed, accuracy, and creativity. Once bonded to a wielder, the weapon's persona will refuse to be wielded by anyone else.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.1.label>point</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.2.label>edge</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.tools.2.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Axe.label>axe</MeleeWeapon_Axe.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Axe.description>An advanced form of one of mankind's oldest weapons, the war axe is a short blade attached to a shaft. The simple, ancient design concentrates cutting power generated from strong overhand swings.</MeleeWeapon_Axe.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_Axe.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_Axe.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Axe.tools.1.label>edge</MeleeWeapon_Axe.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.label>warhammer</MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.description>A long polearm topped with a brutal hammer. The powerful blunt impacts can pulverize an enemy's insides, even through armor.</MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.tools.1.label>head</MeleeWeapon_Warhammer.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.label>monosword</MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.description>A crystal-metallic longsword infused with mechanites that maintain a mono-molecular cutting edge. It cuts through even thick armor with ease, and its light weight permits fast attacks.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.1.label>point</MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.2.label>edge</MeleeWeapon_MonoSword.tools.2.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.label>zeushammer</MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.description>A warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. Upon impact, it blasts the target with an EMP burst in addition to the physical damage.</MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.tools.1.label>head</MeleeWeapon_Zeushammer.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.label>plasmasword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.description>A metal-cored sword with a cutting edge. Plasma is wrapped around the core, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both sliced by the metal core, as well as burned or ignited by the plasma sheath.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.0.label>handle</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.0.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.1.label>point</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.1.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.2.label>edge</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSword.tools.2.label>
  <OrbitalTargeterMechCluster.label>orbital mech cluster targeter</OrbitalTargeterMechCluster.label>
  <OrbitalTargeterMechCluster.description>An ancient military targeting device. It signals an orbital platform to drop a mechanoid combat cluster at the targeted point. The cluster may include any mixture of mechanoids and mech defense structures.
\nThough they may have once had some allegiance to the ancient army that created this unit, any mechs dropped now will indiscriminately attack any human they see - including the one that summoned them.
\nThe unit only contains one usage code, so it can only be used once.</OrbitalTargeterMechCluster.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.label>eltex staff</MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.description>An ultratech staff threaded with psychic focusing materials. While it is a solid melee weapon, its main purpose is to enhance the wielder's psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation, allowing more use of psychic powers.</MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.tools.0.label>head</MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaff.tools.0.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.label>anima tree</Plant_TreeAnima.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.description>A rare tree with warm, skin-smooth bark and long iridescent leaves. Infused with bioluminescent micro-organisms, anima trees develop a unique form of psychic symbiosis with surrounding lifeforms, allowing them to grow in a wide variety of biomes.\n\nIf a person (psycaster or not) meditates near an anima tree, it will grow anima grass around its base. Once enough grass is grown, it becomes possible to carry out a psychic linking ritual with the tree and upgrade a person's psychic powers. Only tribal peoples know the secret of this ritual. Tribal psycasters are also able to draw psyfocus from anima trees while meditating to them.\n\nAnima trees' psychic properties are weakened if artificial structures are placed nearby. They refuse to be caged or studied, and must remain part of nature.\n\nMost tribes believe that anima trees are not simply trees, but are rather the physical extremities of a single world spirit.</Plant_TreeAnima.description>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.comps.3.enoughPlantsLetterLabel>About: Anima tree linking</Plant_TreeAnima.comps.3.enoughPlantsLetterLabel>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.comps.3.enoughPlantsLetterText>The anima tree now has {0} anima grass around it. This is enough for a tribal person to begin their first linking ritual!\n\nThe linking ritual gives a level of psylink and the ability to use psychic powers. Upgrading to a higher level requires more grass at each level.\n\nThe anima grass requirements for linking rituals to upgrade psycasters are:\n\n{1}\n\nNote: Only those with the nature focus type can meditate to or link with anima trees. You can see a person's focus types by looking at their info card with the 'i' button.</Plant_TreeAnima.comps.3.enoughPlantsLetterText>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.label>anima grass</Plant_GrassAnima.label>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.description>A grass infused with luminous microorganisms. Tribal peoples find that anima grass grows around the base of an anima tree as they meditate. It seems to reflect some kind of strengthening of the tree's psychic power.\n\nOffworld scientists have tried to study the phenomenon, but the grass degenerates into normal plant matter when observed too closely.\n\nAnimals refuse eat anima grass. Tribal stories say this is done out of respect and fear.</Plant_GrassAnima.description>
  <WakeUp.description.description>A synthetic stimulant. Wake-up fills the user's need for rest, allowing them to work for extended periods without getting tired. Psycasters on wake-up gain more psyfocus from meditation than they otherwise would. However, taking wake-up runs the risk of developing an addiction.\n\nIn the most competitive universities and companies of many worlds, high-achievers are sometimes called 'wake-ups' because of the association with this drug.</WakeUp.description.description>
  <GoJuice.description.description>A synthetic performance-enhancing drug developed for space marines during the early days of interplanetary warfare. Go-juice blocks pain, increases movement speed, and improves the user's melee and shooting abilities. For psycasters, the drug also instantly increases psyfocus without meditation.\n\nThe military chemists who created it were never able to remove its addictiveness. Some saw this as a downside; others saw it as a benefit.</GoJuice.description.description>
</LanguageData>