<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEI_InsectoidLeg.label>insectoid leg</VFEI_InsectoidLeg.label>
  <VFEI_InsectoidLeg.description>A jointed appendage of an insectoid, consisting of several chitin covered segments. Whilst it’s an extremely painful mutation, this leg has much higher resistance to damage.</VFEI_InsectoidLeg.description>
  <VFEI_InsectoidArm.label>insectoid arm</VFEI_InsectoidArm.label>
  <VFEI_InsectoidArm.description>A jointed appendage of an insectoid, consisting of several chitin covered segments. Whilst it’s an extremely painful mutation, this arm has much higher resistance to damage.</VFEI_InsectoidArm.description>
  <VFEI_CompoundEye.label>compound eye</VFEI_CompoundEye.label>
  <VFEI_CompoundEye.description>An eye consisting of thousands of individual photoreceptor units, compound eyes have a large field of view and help with detecting fast movement, however its visibility range is significantly reduced. Whilst it’s an extremely painful mutation, this eye has a higher resistance to damage.</VFEI_CompoundEye.description>
  <VFEI_Mandibles.label>mandibles</VFEI_Mandibles.label>
  <VFEI_Mandibles.description>A pair of appendages situated on the sides of the mouth, Helping to crush and cut the food. Whilst it’s significantly less comfortable than normal jaw, insectoid mandibles significantly increase eating speed.</VFEI_Mandibles.description>
  <VFEI_JellySac.label>jelly sac</VFEI_JellySac.label>
  <VFEI_JellySac.description>A tube-like organ grown within the body. It allows humans to produce low quantities of insect jelly over time. It’s an extremely painful mutation, in some cases requiring medical enhancement for the person to actually live with it.</VFEI_JellySac.description>
  <VFEI_VenomGland.label>venom gland</VFEI_VenomGland.label>
  <VFEI_VenomGland.description>A sack-like gland tucked under the tongue that secretes acid, liquifying and allowing to safely consume even the most dangerous foods. The overstimulation of this gland enables the user to throw a short range acid spitting attack, effective at going through armor.</VFEI_VenomGland.description>
  <VFEI_PneumaticClaw.label>pneumatic claw</VFEI_PneumaticClaw.label>
  <VFEI_PneumaticClaw.description>A powerful pneumatic pincer arm, capable of repeatedly exerting great pressure on the target at the cost of refined motor skills.</VFEI_PneumaticClaw.description>
  <VFEI_Antenna.label>antenna</VFEI_Antenna.label>
  <VFEI_Antenna.description>A slender, mobile sensory organ that serves to compliment vision and locational awareness. A subject with this mutation will no longer suffer from darkness penalties, however sensory overload makes it very difficult to socialize.</VFEI_Antenna.description>
  <VFEI_PredatorStomach.label>predator stomach</VFEI_PredatorStomach.label>
  <VFEI_PredatorStomach.description>A highly efficient, although basic stomach alternative. Subjects with this mutation will be able to live longer with less food.</VFEI_PredatorStomach.description>
  <VFEI_PheromoneSecretor.label>pheromone secretor</VFEI_PheromoneSecretor.label>
  <VFEI_PheromoneSecretor.description>Insectoid glands that slowly leak colorless, odorless, but sticky pheromone, notable for inducing a mild euphoria in those nearby.</VFEI_PheromoneSecretor.description>
  <VFEI_VentricularSleeve.label>ventricular sleeve</VFEI_VentricularSleeve.label>
  <VFEI_VentricularSleeve.description>A barely understood heart and artery mutation, causes blood to coagulate into oxygen-rich gel-like material. Upon laceration or even loss of limbs, the gel will cauterize the wound immediately. Unfortunately puts heavy strain on human cardiovascular biology.</VFEI_VentricularSleeve.description>
  <VFEI_SynapticCerebellum.label>synaptic cerebellum</VFEI_SynapticCerebellum.label>
  <VFEI_SynapticCerebellum.description>An insectoid brain particularly sensitive to residual psychic synapse. A creature with this mutation possesses profound collective thought and psychic sensitivity, however is barely able to form cohesive sentences.</VFEI_SynapticCerebellum.description>
  <VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipModule.label>infested crashed ship module</VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipModule.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipModule.description>A mysterious segment of a long destroyed spaceship. It may contain exotic materials, computers, even AI personas. It seems to be completely covered in biomass and lumps of insectoid jelly. It is fairly certain that this old wreckage may contain great dangers.</VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipModule.description>
  <VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipPart.label>infested crashed ship part</VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipPart.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipPart.description>A mysterious crashed piece of a spaceship. It may contain exotic materials, computers, even AI personas. This one seems to be covered in biomass and insect jelly. Bizarre insect chittering can be heard within the hull.</VFEI_InfestedCrashedShipPart.description>
  <VFEI_InfestedShipChunk.label>infested ship chunk</VFEI_InfestedShipChunk.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedShipChunk.description>A chunk of a spacecraft covered in biomass and insect jelly. Bizarre insect chittering can be heard within the hull. Can be deconstructed to yield useful steel and components.</VFEI_InfestedShipChunk.description>
  <VFEI_InsectMeteoriteIncoming.label>meteorite (incoming)</VFEI_InsectMeteoriteIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_BioengineeringIncubator.label>bio-engineering incubator</VFEI_BioengineeringIncubator.label>
  <VFEI_BioengineeringIncubator.description>An ultra-tech vat tank connected to advanced life support systems. Often used on urbworlds and rimworlds for less than legal experiments, incubator is capable of mixing genomes and creating genetic modifications in the form of living subjects.</VFEI_BioengineeringIncubator.description>
  <VFEI_Mote.label>mote</VFEI_Mote.label>
  <VFEI_Mote.description>Don't mind me, i'm useless for you</VFEI_Mote.description>
  <VFEI_TunnelHiveSpawner.label>tunnel</VFEI_TunnelHiveSpawner.label>
  <VFEI_LargeHive.label>large hive</VFEI_LargeHive.label>
  <VFEI_LargeHive.description>An enourmous hive of insectoid creatures. If activated, it will spawn additional insect types and hives over time, as well as delicious and valuable insect jelly.</VFEI_LargeHive.description>
  <VFEI_InsectoidLarvaeCocoon.label>cocoon</VFEI_InsectoidLarvaeCocoon.label>
  <VFEI_InsectoidLarvaeCocoon.description>A larve cocoon of giant insects.</VFEI_InsectoidLarvaeCocoon.description>
  <VFEI_BurrowSmall.label>small burrow</VFEI_BurrowSmall.label>
  <VFEI_BurrowSmall.description>A burrow leading to a web of insectoid tunnels. It will periodically spawn waves of lower castes of insects until destroyed.</VFEI_BurrowSmall.description>
  <VFEI_BurrowMedium.label>medium burrow</VFEI_BurrowMedium.label>
  <VFEI_BurrowMedium.description>A burrow leading to a web of insectoid tunnels. It will periodically spawn waves of higher castes of insects until destroyed.</VFEI_BurrowMedium.description>
  <VFEI_BurrowRoyal.label>royal burrow</VFEI_BurrowRoyal.label>
  <VFEI_BurrowRoyal.description>A burrow leading to a web of insectoid tunnels. It will periodically spawn the highest caste of insects - the royal offspring of the queen until destroyed.</VFEI_BurrowRoyal.description>
  <VFEI_SonicInfestationRepeller.label>sonic infestation repeller</VFEI_SonicInfestationRepeller.label>
  <VFEI_SonicInfestationRepeller.description>A large ultratech device capable of emitting a sonic pulse every hour, repelling any insectoid movement underneath. Whilst it significantly removes the infestation risk, it enrages the insectoid empress and can lead to more powerful insectoid herds arriving at the colony.</VFEI_SonicInfestationRepeller.description>
  <VFEI_TeleporterTraveler.label>teleporter</VFEI_TeleporterTraveler.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_RiotArmor.label>riot armor</VFE_Apparel_RiotArmor.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_RiotArmor.description>A thick jacket with armor plates inserted on chests, arms, legs and back. Very effective at protecting against blunt trauma, this kind of armor is often used by riot police and heavy infantry alike.</VFE_Apparel_RiotArmor.description>
  <VFE_Apparel_RiotHelmet.label>riot helmet</VFE_Apparel_RiotHelmet.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_RiotHelmet.description>A heavy combat helmet with a face covering plate. Often used by riot police units due to its effectiveness at protecting against blunt trauma.</VFE_Apparel_RiotHelmet.description>
  <VFEI_Shield_Riot.tools.0.label>centre</VFEI_Shield_Riot.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Shield_Riot.label>riot shield</VFEI_Shield_Riot.label>
  <VFEI_Shield_Riot.description>An industrial heavy shield made out of reinforced steel. Provides a lot of protection against blunt damage, which makes it ideal for urbworld riot police.</VFEI_Shield_Riot.description>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicPacifier.label>psychic pacifier</VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicPacifier.label>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicPacifier.description>One-use artifact that directs psychic pacifying blast towards a character, making them join your faction. There is a large risk of brain damage. It works at long distances, and through walls.</VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicPacifier.description>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicAnimalTamer.label>psychic animal tamer</VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicAnimalTamer.label>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicAnimalTamer.description>A one-use psychic animal tamer. It overwhelms the target's mind with terrifying mental persuasion, dropping it into a transcendental state, in which it gets trusting and keen with you. There is a risk of brain damage. It works at long distances, and through walls.</VFEI_Artifacts_PsychicAnimalTamer.description>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechEraser.label>archotech eraser</VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechEraser.label>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechEraser.description>One-use artifact that utilises a vanometric core to erase everything in a radius of 10 from existence. Needs to be manually triggered.</VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechEraser.description>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechTeleporter.label>archotech teleporter</VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechTeleporter.label>
  <VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechTeleporter.description>One-use artifact which allows to transport up to 500 kg of mass from one place to any other place on the planet. Can't be used to give gift or raid other faction.</VFEI_Artifacts_ArchotechTeleporter.description>
  <VFEI_RoyalInsectJelly.label>royal insect jelly</VFEI_RoyalInsectJelly.label>
  <VFEI_RoyalInsectJelly.description>A golden, shining jelly used by the queens to create new spawn. It is smooth, rich, and brings joy to those who consume it. Because of its unique biological composition, it boosts immunity and nourishes anyone who has a taste of it.</VFEI_RoyalInsectJelly.description>
  <VFEI_InsectMilk.label>insect milk</VFEI_InsectMilk.label>
  <VFEI_InsectMilk.description>Milk from an insectoid.</VFEI_InsectMilk.description>
  <VFEI_EggInsectoidUnfertilized.label>insectoid egg (unfert.)</VFEI_EggInsectoidUnfertilized.label>
  <VFEI_EggInsectoidUnfertilized.description>An unfertilized insectoid egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</VFEI_EggInsectoidUnfertilized.description>
  <VFEI_DroneGenome.label>drone genetic material</VFEI_DroneGenome.label>
  <VFEI_DroneGenome.description>Genetic material of several different species of working animals and drones, mixed into one payload of DNA.\n\nWhen administered to a human being, this genome can have a random effect.</VFEI_DroneGenome.description>
  <VFEI_WarriorGenome.label>warrior genetic material</VFEI_WarriorGenome.label>
  <VFEI_WarriorGenome.description>Genetic material of several different species of warrior caste insects and predators, mixed into one payload of DNA.\n\nWhen administered to a human being, this genome can have a random effect.</VFEI_WarriorGenome.description>
  <VFEI_RoyalGenome.label>royal genetic material</VFEI_RoyalGenome.label>
  <VFEI_RoyalGenome.description>Genetic material of several different species of royal insectoids and queens, mixed into one payload of DNA.\n\nWhen administered to a human being, this genome can have a random effect.</VFEI_RoyalGenome.description>
  <VFEI_Chitin.label>chitin</VFEI_Chitin.label>
  <VFEI_Chitin.description>An extremely thick composition of rare minerals and biomass, commonly found in a form of insect exoskeletons.</VFEI_Chitin.description>
  <VFEI_Spidersilk.label>spidersilk</VFEI_Spidersilk.label>
  <VFEI_Spidersilk.description>A very delicate fabric that seems to shine due to the unique way it reflects light rays. It’s very flammable and provides little protection, but its beauty makes it extremely valuable.</VFEI_Spidersilk.description>
  <VFEI_Shell_PsychicWarhead.label>psychic warhead</VFEI_Shell_PsychicWarhead.label>
  <VFEI_Shell_PsychicWarhead.description>An archotech warhead from a long forgotten era. Upon detonation, it releases a strong psychic drone, sending all animals and humanoids in its reach into a berserk rage. Can be fired from mortars. Explodes when damaged.</VFEI_Shell_PsychicWarhead.description>
  <VFEI_Bullet_Shell_PsychicWarhead.label>archotech warhead shell</VFEI_Bullet_Shell_PsychicWarhead.label>
  <VFEI_Apparel_ArchotechShieldBelt.label>archotech shield belt</VFEI_Apparel_ArchotechShieldBelt.label>
  <VFEI_Apparel_ArchotechShieldBelt.description>A single-person psychic shield device made by a superior AI, that covers the user with an impenetrable shield bubble. It will attempt to stop any rapidly-moving projectile or energy attack. It does nothing against melee attacks or shots from point-blank range. This advanced version has a larger capacity, but lacks any recharge mechanism. The incomparable shield strength makes it a valuable good for any type of soldier.</VFEI_Apparel_ArchotechShieldBelt.description>
  <VFEI_Filth_Slime.label>royal slime</VFEI_Filth_Slime.label>
  <VFEI_GigalocustIncoming.label>gigalocust (incoming)</VFEI_GigalocustIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedShipChunkIncoming.label>infested ship part (incoming)</VFEI_InfestedShipChunkIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedShipPartIncoming.label>infested ship part (incoming)</VFEI_InfestedShipPartIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_InfestedShipModuleIncoming.label>infested ship part (incoming)</VFEI_InfestedShipModuleIncoming.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.label>plasmacutter</VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.description>A mining pistol with metal-cored projectiles wrapped in plasma, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both sliced by the metal core, as well as burned or ignited by plasma coating. This weapon has a chance to deal critical hits, with a chance to cut the limb straight off.</VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.description>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.tools.0.label>stock</VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.tools.1.label>barrel</VFE_Gun_Plasmacutter.tools.1.label>
  <Bullet_Plasmacutter.label>plasmacutter shot</Bullet_Plasmacutter.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.label>plasmapiercer</VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.description>A heavy rifle capable of shooting metal-cored nails covered in plasma and held in place by an energy field. These bolts are excellent at stopping larger targets, capable of knocking most human-sized enemies to the ground.</VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.description>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.tools.0.label>stock</VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.tools.1.label>barrel</VFE_Gun_Plasmapiercer.tools.1.label>
  <Bullet_Plasmapiercer.label>plasmapiercer shot</Bullet_Plasmapiercer.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.label>plasmabeam rifle</VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.description>A long range rifle using metal-cored pellets covered in superheated gas, held in place by an energy field. Shots fired from this rifle burn everything they hit, but due to how unstable they are, it’s very difficult to fire it accurately over long distances.</VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.description>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.tools.0.label>stock</VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.tools.1.label>barrel</VFE_Gun_PlasmabeamRifle.tools.1.label>
  <Bullet_PlasmaBeam.label>plasma beam</Bullet_PlasmaBeam.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.label>plasma scattergun</VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.description>A close-quarters scattergun firing shards of molten metal, kept in this state thanks to superheated gas wrapped around their cores. Inflicts a large number of burn wounds to enemies, most often eliminating threats with a single shot. Due to the unstable nature of the projectiles, it has a very short range.</VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.description>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.tools.0.label>stock</VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.tools.0.label>
  <VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.tools.1.label>barrel</VFE_Gun_PlasmaScattergun.tools.1.label>
  <Bullet_PlasmaScatter.label>plasma scatter shot</Bullet_PlasmaScatter.label>
  <VFE_Plasmasaw.label>plasmasaw</VFE_Plasmasaw.label>
  <VFE_Plasmasaw.description>A neo-industrial metal-cored saw with a cutting edge made out of plasma, held in place by an energy field. Targets are both sliced by the metal core, as well as burned or ignited by the plasma chain.</VFE_Plasmasaw.description>
  <VFE_Plasmasaw.tools.0.label>plasma chain</VFE_Plasmasaw.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Plant_Armillarix.label>armillarix</VFEI_Plant_Armillarix.label>
  <VFEI_Plant_Armillarix.description>A medium sized mushroom. When fully matured, its cap spreads open to release an inner bulb that emits very hard light, bright enough to grow other crops around it.</VFEI_Plant_Armillarix.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.label>insectoid queen</VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.description>A giant, genetically-engineered insectoid responsible for creating new spawn. A mother to the insects in her hive, a queen doesn’t do heavy work, and tries to avoid combat if possible. As massive as an adult thrumbo, the queen instills fear in most opponents. Her thick chitinous armor makes her hard to kill, whilst long, deadly blades can tear through plasteel shielding in seconds. Despite being quite slow in open terrain, an insectoid queen is capable of creating new larvae at a rapid pace, and should never be allowed to settle down.</VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_Insectoid_Queen.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.label>royal megaspider</VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.description>Not actually a spider, the royal megaspider is a rhino-sized natural spawn of the insectoid queen herself, serving not only as her bodyguard but also as a primary mate. Designed not for work, but for combat only, its thick chitinous armor makes it hard to kill, while its long deadly ripper-blades allow it to slay intruders in the name of his queen.</VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_Insectoid_RoyalMegaspider.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.label>gigalocust</VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.description>A genetically-engineered hunter drone the size of an elephant. It can fly over long distances, dropping down on unsuspecting targets, ripping them to shreds with its several sets of ripper-blades and sharp mandibles. Serving as special servants of the insectoid queen, these monstrosities are deadly, fast and nigh indestructible.</VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_Insectoid_Gigalocust.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.label>megapede</VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.description>A giant, heavy insectoid that glides on dozens of tiny legs. Its thick chitin armor and sharp mandibles the size of an elephant’s tusk make it an excellent siege machine. Due to being extremely slow, they are somewhat vulnerable to hit-and-run tactics.</VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.1.label>mandibles</VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.2.label>head</VFEI_Insectoid_Megapede.tools.2.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.label>larvae</VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.label>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.description>The juvenile form of an insectoid, larvae are harmless, slow and easy to kill. After some time has passed, it undergoes a metamorphosis, turning into an adult insectoid. There is no way to tell what kind of insect will crawl out of its cocoon.</VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.description>
  <VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_Insectoid_Larvae.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.label>Vat-grown boomtick</VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.description>A small genetically-engineered tick carrying a sack of exploding chemicals. Its speed and sharp mandibles are enough to scare off most predators, and the fact that it explodes upon death is a final blow to those not afraid. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.description>
  <VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatgrownBoomtick.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.label>Vat-grown cuterpillar</VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.description>A small insectoid made almost entirely of royal insectoid jelly. Its soft and beautiful appearance is enough for humans to want to spend every minute around it. Cuterpillars are quite valuable on the black market. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownCuterpillar.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.label>Vat-grown gigascorpion</VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.description>A car-sized creature consisting almost entirely of muscle, thick chitin plating, claws and a stinger. This insectoid is fast, agile, and capable of inflicting venomous stings to its foes. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.0.label>left pincer</VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.1.label>right pincer</VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.3.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownGigascorpion.tools.3.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.label>Vat-grown gigawig</VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.description>A huge insectoid consisting of several segments of hard chitin plates, with large claws that allow it to dig through the rock to unearth minerals and ore. Often used across the urbworld to work in quarries and mines, the gigawig regularly digs through the ground, consuming rocks and leaving valuable metals ready for picking. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownGigawig.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.label>Vat-grown megacricket</VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.description>A medium-sized bioengineered combination of a cricket and a woodworm, megacrickets  nourish themselves on trees and vegetation. They are also capable of supporting the hive by digging out crops for easier harvest. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.\n\nNOTE: The Megacricket needs to be trained in "Guard" to be able to help with harvests.</VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownMegacricket.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.label>Vat-grown milkbeetle</VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.description>A large bio-engineered livestock, milkbeetles produce thick insectoid milk in a large sac on its back. Whilst it is moderately armoured, the chitin plates can be safely removed as they quickly grow back. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownMilkbeetle.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.label>Vat-grown monstrosity</VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.description>A result of a failed experiment, this vat-grown monstrosity is a nigh indestructible insectoid with its entire body consisting of thick chitin and strong muscle, capable of regrowing limbs at a rapid pace. Because of underdeveloped organs, this vat-grown creature is unable to survive longer than a few hours at time, but its speed, strength and agility is enough to put an end to a number of research labs across the outer galaxy rim</VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.1.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.2.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownMonstrosity.tools.2.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.label>Vat-grown princess</VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.description>A giant, genetically-engineered insectoid responsible for creating large amounts of unfertilized insectoid eggs. A mere shadow of an actual insectoid queen, an insectoid princess is slow, quite incapable of handling herself in combat situations, and not as intimidating as the natural counterpart. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownPrincess.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.label>Vat-grown royal larva</VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.description>A large bio-engineered larva containing a sack of royal insectoid jelly. Its natural purpose is to become food for other insectoid castes, therefore, it doesn’t serve any important role in their society. When butchered, the royal jelly sack can be safely prepared for consumption. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.description>
  <VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatgrownRoyalLarva.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.label>Vat-grown royal maggot</VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.description>A long, slow and repugnant slug-like insectoid, with a large sac of royal insectoid jelly on its back. The royal maggot leaves a disgusting trail of insectoid ooze wherever it goes, but it regularly produces lumps of royal jelly, ready for consumption. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownRoyalMaggot.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.label>Vat-grown spiderweaver</VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.description>A bio-engineered spider insectoid the size of a bear. Designed for production of a beautiful insectoid spidersilk and sometimes employed in combat, its thick chitinous armor makes it hard to kill, whilst it’s sharp mandibles allow it to rip enemies into pieces. It is, however, quite slow in open terrain. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownSpiderweaver.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.label>Vat-grown titanbeetle</VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.description>A giant, beetle-like insectoid recognized for its ability to break down solid rocks into smaller, easier to carry, chunks. It’s heavily armoured to save it from eventual avalanches, whilst it’s deadly horn allows it to quickly eliminate potential predators with a single blow. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.\n\nNOTE: The Titanbeetle needs to be trained in "Guard" to be able to help with mining. Things mined by the beetle will always appear forbidden due to game constraints.</VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.1.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.2.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownTitanbeetle.tools.2.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.label>Vat-grown gigalocust</VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.description>A gigalocust is a genetically-engineered hunter drone the size of an elephant. It can quickly close distances to its enemies, ripping them to shreds with its several sets of ripper-blades and sharp mandibles. Serving as special servants of the insectoid queen, these monstrosities are deadly, fast and nigh indestructible. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownGigalocust.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.label>Vat-grown megapede</VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.description>A giant, heavy insectoid that glides on dozens of tiny legs. Its thick chitin armor and sharp mandibles the size of an elephant’s tusk make it an excellent siege machine. Due to being extremely slow, they are somewhat vulnerable to hit-and-run tactics. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.1.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.2.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownMegapede.tools.2.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.label>Vat-grown megascarab</VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.description>A large genetically-engineered beetle. Once the worker caste of an artificial ecosystem of insectoids designed to fight mechanoid invasions, it is now usually seen without its deadlier insectoid cousins. Still, its size and hard shell make it dangerous when it attacks. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownMegascarab.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.label>Vat-grown megaspider</VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.description>Not actually a spider, the megaspider is a genetically-engineered giant insectoid the size of a bear. Designed for heavy work and combat, its thick chitinous armor makes it hard to kill, while its long deadly ripper-blades make it deadly. It is, however, quite slow in open terrain. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.description>
  <VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatgrownMegaspider.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.label>Vat-grown spelopede</VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.description>A medium-sized bioengineered bug the size of a sheep. The spelopede is the middle caste of a hive, taking care of most work tasks as well as fighting with its digging claws. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.tools.0.label>head claw</VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownSpelopede.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWargling.label>Vat-grown wargling</VFEI_VatGrownWargling.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWargling.description>A dog-sized combat insectoid, usually tasked with defending property. It’s speed paired with strong jaws and several sharp appendages allow it to quickly tackle much larger assailants. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownWargling.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWargling.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownWargling.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWargling.tools.3.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownWargling.tools.3.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.label>Vat-grown worker ant</VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.description>A medium-sized, bioengineered ant the size of a large dog. It’s the middle caste of a hive, responsible for resource distribution and food delivery. Worker ants are capable of carrying large volumes of materials over long distances with ease. A vat-grown creature, it is unable to reproduce, and its lifespan is significantly decreased.</VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.description>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>mandibles</VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>
  <VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>head</VFEI_VatGrownWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>
  <VFEI_BlackHiveGenome.label>black hive genetic material</VFEI_BlackHiveGenome.label>
  <VFEI_BlackHiveGenome.description>A vial of genetic material extracted from an insectoid from the Black Hive.\n\nBlack hive genetic material is not viable in all combinations, and it won't combine with Royal Genome at all.</VFEI_BlackHiveGenome.description>
</LanguageData>