<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AB_FeraliskInfestedJungle.label>feralisk infested jungle</AB_FeraliskInfestedJungle.label>
  <AB_FeraliskInfestedJungle.description>An incredibly thick jungle, completely infested with spiders. Infested jungles such as these sometimes start expanding in a planet's biosphere, if the conditions are right. These worlds usually have to be bombarded from orbit with atomic weapons, to avoid the spiders being unwittingly (or worse, on purpose) transported to other inhabited planets.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>NOTES: this is a VERY hostile biome. Don't start your base here unless you know very well what you are doing. Build a walled compound, leave it as seldom as possible, and USE the spiders in your advantage.&lt;/color></AB_FeraliskInfestedJungle.description>
  <AB_GallatrossGraveyard.label>gallatross graveyard</AB_GallatrossGraveyard.label>
  <AB_GallatrossGraveyard.description>These parched mudflats are littered with the ancient bones of colossal Gallatrosses. Apparently the highly intelligent beasts are coming here to die, and to mourn their fallen relatives.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>NOTE: don't mess with the Gallatross unless you are very sure you are prepared.&lt;/color></AB_GallatrossGraveyard.description>
  <AB_GelatinousSuperorganism.label>gelatinous superorganism</AB_GelatinousSuperorganism.label>
  <AB_GelatinousSuperorganism.description>A huge mold-like organism has grown in this area, basically destroying the previous existing ecosystem, and replacing it with an alien landscape of its own creation. Its strange biology seems to be compatible with this planet's biosphere.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Expect to find no useable rocky materials to build here, and very little wood.&lt;/color></AB_GelatinousSuperorganism.description>
  <AB_MechanoidIntrusion.label>mechanoid intrusion</AB_MechanoidIntrusion.label>
  <AB_MechanoidIntrusion.description>A mechanoid hive was dismantling this biome, turning its mass into computronium, and hastily left it abandoned for unknown reasons. Almost no trace of its biological origins has been left untouched, with even the trees turned into mechanical contraptions destined for some nefarious purposes.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Animals rarely come to this biome, and thus finding food can be VERY difficult.&lt;/color></AB_MechanoidIntrusion.description>
  <AB_MycoticJungle.label>Mycotic Jungle</AB_MycoticJungle.label>
  <AB_MycoticJungle.description>The Mycotic Jungle is a super dense overgrowth of massive giant mushrooms, covered in a coat of mycelium. Giant mushrooms can be used as a poor substitute for wood, and the smaller ones will provide some sustenance. Beware of the bigger mushrooms, though, as they create a cloud of dangerous spores that can quickly suffocate any organic life.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Rains are VERY common in this biome. There is a plant that produces renewable wood, but most of the flora produces mushroom stalks.&lt;/color></AB_MycoticJungle.description>
  <AB_OcularForest.label>ocular forest</AB_OcularForest.label>
  <AB_OcularForest.description>This sickly looking forest seems to be completely alien, probably of an extra-dimensional origin. Natural plant life seems to be struggling to grow, and the very ground fights against the neighbouring lands. Strange lifeforms, perhaps not entirely alive, scurry around the sickening vegetation.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>There is a plant that produces renewable wood, but most of the flora produces red wood, a poor substitute.&lt;/color></AB_OcularForest.description>
  <AB_PropaneLakes.label>propane lakes</AB_PropaneLakes.label>
  <AB_PropaneLakes.description>Huge liquid propane lakes fill this desolate frozen landscape. As propane is a compound that doesn't occur naturally, this is probably the remnant of some weird ecological or industrial experiment gone awry.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Expect extremely cold temperatures, constant snowing, very little and non-renewable wood, and usually no rocks. Surprisingly some strange flora have adapted to these circumstances, attracting all kinds of unusual animals.&lt;/color></AB_PropaneLakes.description>
  <AB_PyroclasticConflagration.label>pyroclastic conflagration</AB_PyroclasticConflagration.label>
  <AB_PyroclasticConflagration.description>A desolate expanse of obsidian and solidified lava, with several active calderas bubbling menacingly. A few scraggy trees cling to the mostly unfertile soil.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>This is a HARD biome. Things will catch on fire. People will catch on fire, and maybe get stuck in the lava and burn to death if you don't restrict them properly. Acid rain will fall every few quadrums, which might be a welcome respite from the constant volcanic ash, if it weren't burning your colonists with acid. Ravenous exotic animals will set your stuff on fire. Fire, fire everywhere. You have been warned!&lt;/color></AB_PyroclasticConflagration.description>
  <AB_RockyCrags.label>forsaken crags</AB_RockyCrags.label>
  <AB_RockyCrags.description>This desertic landscape appears to be perpetually covered in an unnatural fog that seeps all light from the sun. In the ancient past it was partly terraformed by a mysterious humanoid alien race simply known as Forsakens. A plethora of nocturnal alien creatures roam the desert, feeding on bioluminescent plants and fungi that are the only available and reliable source of light.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>Luminosity in this biome doesn't reach high enough levels to grow plants, so you'll have to use the flora as natural sunlamps. Nights are DARK, and most creatures are nocturnal. Those which aren't, won't last long.&lt;/color></AB_RockyCrags.description>
  <AB_TarPits.label>tar pits</AB_TarPits.label>
  <AB_TarPits.description>Sun-baked mud, interspersed with patches of fertile grassy terrain. And, of course, the tar lakes themselves. Tar pits are usually infested with extensive subterranean bumbledrone hives.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733>This biome is arid, but rich in animal and vegetal life. Wood is not a problem, and neither are foreageable plants. Stone is scarce due to the pits being always a flat terrain. The greatest hazard is the incredibly hard to cross terrain, specially around the pits. Also, beware of aggressive bumbledrones surrounding their hive entrances!&lt;/color></AB_TarPits.description>
</LanguageData>