<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ROM_TheAgency.label>The Agency</ROM_TheAgency.label>
  <ROM_TheAgency.description>A clandestine organization of agents dedicated to keeping eldrich forces at bay.\n\nFashioned after ancient law enforcement organizations, The Agency can be found setting up outposts near disaster zones influenced by eldritch abominations most foul. Their goal is to research and investigate new strategies and relics to combat the monsters that have arisen from slumbers most ancient. They dress themselves in traditional police and detective attire from the old world they lost to the cosmic horrors, enjoy brandishing six-shooter revolvers, and are fond of trading their less secretive objects.\n\nThe Agency is structured like a military organization, with members ranking from Cadet up to Chief of the Agency. Those afflicted by cosmic machinations will need their help to survive, as the reinforcements they send tend to be well armed, and won't crack under pressure in the face of stygian monstrosities.</ROM_TheAgency.description>
  <ROM_TheAgency.pawnSingular>agent</ROM_TheAgency.pawnSingular>
  <ROM_TheAgency.pawnsPlural>agents</ROM_TheAgency.pawnsPlural>
  <ROM_TheAgency.leaderTitle>director</ROM_TheAgency.leaderTitle>
  <ROM_LostPlatoon.label>Lost Platoon</ROM_LostPlatoon.label>
  <ROM_LostPlatoon.description>This military unit has somehow appeared on the landscape due to mysterious circumstances. They have dug up new trenches in desperation, and through their fear, they only trade bullets instead of words. For whatever it is they have seen or where they have come from, it is clear that they do not belong here.</ROM_LostPlatoon.description>
  <ROM_LostPlatoon.pawnsPlural>lost soldiers</ROM_LostPlatoon.pawnsPlural>
  <ROM_LostPlatoon.leaderTitle>captain</ROM_LostPlatoon.leaderTitle>
  <ROM_Townsfolk.label>Coastal Fishing Towns</ROM_Townsfolk.label>
  <ROM_Townsfolk.description>Coastal communities of fishermen and tanners, with designated law enforcers.\n\nThese fishing villages seemingly come into existence overnight. A wild untamed forest can turn into a creaking assortment of docks and buildings. If one didn't know how they had mysteriously arrived, one would assume they had been there for decades. The weathered locals curiously ignore any questions as to how they arrived, or how they constructed a village so quickly and quietly.\n\nThe gruff citizens of these damp townships are slow to trust, but earning it can be worthwhile. The residents of these communities can be found wielding large hooks, branding irons, and the powerful harpoon gun. They are usually only willing to trade among their own people, but on the Rimworlds, these callused strangers will settle for anyone sane enough to barter.</ROM_Townsfolk.description>
  <ROM_Townsfolk.pawnSingular>townsfolk</ROM_Townsfolk.pawnSingular>
  <ROM_Townsfolk.pawnsPlural>townsfolk</ROM_Townsfolk.pawnsPlural>
  <ROM_Townsfolk.leaderTitle>governor</ROM_Townsfolk.leaderTitle>
</LanguageData>