<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AB_RedFog.label>red fog</AB_RedFog.label>
  <AB_RedFog.description>Red fog reduces the accuracy of ranged weapons.</AB_RedFog.description>
  <AB_VolcanicAsh.label>volcanic ash</AB_VolcanicAsh.label>
  <AB_VolcanicAsh.description>A mixture of rock, mineral, and glass particles expelled from a volcano during a volcanic eruption. This creates a thick atmospheric layer that reduces ranged accuracy.</AB_VolcanicAsh.description>
  <AB_VolcanicAshRain.label>volcanic ash with rain</AB_VolcanicAshRain.label>
  <AB_VolcanicAshRain.description>A mixture of rock, mineral, and glass particles expelled from a volcano during a volcanic eruption, precipitating with rain. This creates a thick atmospheric layer that reduces ranged accuracy.</AB_VolcanicAshRain.description>
  <AB_ForsakenNight.label>forsaken fog</AB_ForsakenNight.label>
  <AB_ForsakenNight.description>A preternatural darkness that seeps into your very soul. Even during the "day" brightness will be very low, so lighting is going to be absolutely essential. Nights are going to be REALLY dark.</AB_ForsakenNight.description>
  <AB_ForsakenRainyNight.label>forsaken rain</AB_ForsakenRainyNight.label>
  <AB_ForsakenRainyNight.description>A preternatural darkness that seeps into your very soul. A freezing rain of supercooled water has started to drop from the darkened sky.</AB_ForsakenRainyNight.description>
  <AB_ForsakenThunderstorm.label>forsaken thunderstorm</AB_ForsakenThunderstorm.label>
  <AB_ForsakenThunderstorm.description>A preternatural darkness that seeps into your very soul. Now with a dry thunderstorm! Isn't it great?</AB_ForsakenThunderstorm.description>
  <AB_AcidRainWeather.label>acid rain</AB_AcidRainWeather.label>
  <AB_AcidRainWeather.description>Toxic gas emissions from nearby volcanically active calderas are precipitating in the form of dangerous acid rain. Acid rain has an adverse impact on flora and fauna, killing insect and aquatic life-forms as well as having impacts on human health. Acid rain reduces the accuracy of ranged weapons, extinguishes fire, and slows people down.</AB_AcidRainWeather.description>
</LanguageData>