<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T1.label>Heretical Inclinations</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T1.description>Allows you to create basic Heretical technology</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T2.label>Heretical Tech</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T2.description>Allows you to create more Heretical technology</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T3.label>Grand Heresy</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T3.description>Allows you to create advanced warpspawned technology</OG_Chaos_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered.label>Power Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered.description>Allows the creation of basic Power Weapons.\nAttacks made by power weapons ignore all armour.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered_Special.label>Special Power Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered_Special.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered_Special.description>Allows the creation of Power Weapons with additional effects.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Powered_Special.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Force.label>Force Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Force.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Force.description>Force Weapons are advanced, psychically-attuned close combat weapons that are only effective in the hands of a psyker. Force Weapons effectively act as deadly, psychic extensions or amplifiers of the wielder's own Empyrean-spawned powers. They are designed to allow a psyker to channel deadly Warp energies into their victim, acting as a conduit between the wielder's mind and the flesh of his target. Large alien monstrosities and daemons that are resilient to conventional weapons can be slain outright by a single wound from a Force Weapon, as their bodies and minds are destroyed by the unearthly powers of the Immaterium.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Force.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Special.label>Special Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Special.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Special.description>Allows you to Research Special Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Special.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Heavy.label>Heavy Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Heavy.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Heavy.description>Allows you to create basic Heavy Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Heavy.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Flame.label>Flame Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Flame.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Flame.description>An age old principle Flamer Weapons are flamethrower weapons, capable of unleashing a liquid incendiary chemical that bursts into flames as it leaves the weapon.\nFlame-based weapons are used by several of the intelligent races and their militaries across the Milky Way Galaxy, and are valued for their ability to destroy many enemies at once with a burst of expanding flame, regardless of any protective cover they possess., some variety of Flame based weapons are used by most races in the galaxy, from Imperial Flamers to Orkish Burnaz, even the Tau and Eldar make use of similar weapons.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Flame.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Laser.label>Laser Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Laser.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Laser.description>Laser Weapons, or Las Weapons as they are known in the Imperium of Man, are a family of directed energy weapons that produce beams of high-intensity amplified light to produce heat damage on a target. Laser Weapons are relatively easy to produce and maintain. No solid ammunition is ever used -- only power cells which can be recharged and quickly swapped when depleted with another fully-charged power cell. This makes them ideal for large troop formations like the Astra Militarum.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Laser.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Haywire.label>Haywire Tech</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Haywire.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Haywire.description>When fired Haywire based weapons cause crackling blasts of electromagnetic energy leap from the projector with every shot. Capable of scrambling even the most robust electrical systems, a single hit from such a weapon can leave enemy tanks and aircraft powerles.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Haywire.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Plasma.label>Plasma Weapons</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Plasma.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Plasma.description>Plasma Weapons are highly potent and destructive directed energy weapons utilised in many forms by the advanced intelligent races of the Milky Way Galaxy. Most Plasma Weapons work by delivering pulses of searing energy and superheated matter that have been transmuted into a gaseous plasma state that carries an electrical charge. The plasma "bolts" fired by these weapons explode on impact and generate the destructive heat of a small sun, and the sheer amount of energy released by the impact of superheated plasma is often enough to completely vaporise the target.\n\nImperial Plasma weapons are prone to Overheating (Gets Hot!)</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Plasma.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Melta.label>Melta Tech</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Melta.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Melta.description>Melta Weapons are a type of thermal weapon that make use of a sub-atomic reaction in a chemical fuel source to produce a tightly-focused beam of intense, searing heat. The Imperial Meltagun and Multi-Melta (also known as "Cookers" or "Vape Guns"), as well as the grenade-like Melta Bomb, are formidable directed energy weapons. Melta Weapons have a short range but are very powerful and their thermal blast's intensity increases as the distance to the target decreases. A Meltagun works by inducing a minute, sub-molecular reaction within a highly-pressurised pyrum-petrol fuel mix located within an ammunition canister, and then projecting the resulting plasma through the canister and from the weapon's barrel as a blast of incredible heat.</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Melta.description>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Sonic.label>Sonic Weaponry</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Sonic.label>
  <OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Sonic.description>Allows you to create Sonic weaponry</OG_Common_Tech_Weapons_Sonic.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Base_T0.label>Imperial Subjects</OG_Imperial_Tech_Base_T0.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Base_T0.description>Grants you access to basic Imperial technology.</OG_Imperial_Tech_Base_T0.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel.label>Imperial Clothing</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel.description>Allows you to create basic Imperial Clothing</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>Flakk Armour</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>Allows you to create Imperial Flak Armour</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>Carapace Armour</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>Allows you to create Imperial Carapace Armour</OG_Imperial_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_Shield.label>Conversion Fields</OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_Shield.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_Shield.description>Allows you to create Conversion Field emitters</OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_Shield.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_ServoSkull.label>Servo Skulls</OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_ServoSkull.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_ServoSkull.description>Allows you to create basic Servo Skulls</OG_Imperial_Tech_Wargear_ServoSkull.description>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Weapons_Bolt.label>Bolt Weapons</OG_Imperial_Tech_Weapons_Bolt.label>
  <OG_Imperial_Tech_Weapons_Bolt.description>A brutally efficient weapon, the Bolter fires mass-reactive bolts at its targets, each one a self-propelled missile which explodes with devastating effectiveness after penetrating its target. The fear and awe that Bolter fire creates makes it a perfect weapon for shock troops, the hammering thunder of the guns mixing terrifyingly with the dull, wet explosions as flesh is blown apart.</OG_Imperial_Tech_Weapons_Bolt.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T1.label>Mechanicum Initiation</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T1.description>Allows access to basic Mechanicus technology</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T2.label>Tech Adepts of Mars</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T2.description>Allows access to improved Mechanicus technology</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T3.label>Scions of Mars</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T3.description>Allows access to advanced Mechanicus technology</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Radium.label>Radium Weapons</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Radium.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Radium.description>Teaches Imperial subjects how to create Radium weapons</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Radium.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Phosphor.label>Phosphor Tech</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Phosphor.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Phosphor.description>Teaches Imperial subjects how to create Adeptus Mechanicus Plasma weaponry</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Phosphor.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_AdvancedBallistics.label>Advanced Ballistics</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_AdvancedBallistics.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_AdvancedBallistics.description>Teaches Imperial subjects how to create a Stub Carbine</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_AdvancedBallistics.description>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Volkite.label>Volkite Tech</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Volkite.label>
  <OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Volkite.description>Volkite Weapons are an arcane term used by the Adeptus Mechanicus to refer to a class of powerful thermal ray weapons whose technology is pre-Imperial in origin and dates back to the Dark Age of Technology or the Age of Strife. These weapons possessed considerable killing power, surpassing most other armaments of their size.\n\nRequires Royalty</OG_Mechanicus_Tech_Weapons_Volkite.description>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T1.label>Adeptus Arbites</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T1.description>Grants you access to STC templates used by the Adeptus Arbites</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T2.label>Adeptus Militarum</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T2.description>Grants you access to STC templates used by the Adeptus Militarum</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T3.label>Militarum Tempestus</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T3.description>Grants you access to STC templates used to create finest weapons and wargear in the Departmento Munitorum's arsenal, Tempestus Scions are equipped to carry out missions beyond the capabilities of the rank-and-file Guardsman.</OG_Militarum_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Base.label>Officio Assassinorum</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Base.label>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Base.description>Grants you access to the Officio Assassinorum</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Base.description>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Vindicare.label>Vindicare Temple</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Vindicare.label>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Vindicare.description>Grants you access to STC templates for Weapons used by the Officio Assassinorum's Vindicare Temple.\n\nRequires Royalty</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Vindicare.description>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Callidus.label>Callidus Temple</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Callidus.label>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Callidus.description>Grants you access to STC templates for Weapons used by the Officio Assassinorum's Callidus Temple.\n\nRequires Royalty</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Callidus.description>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Culexus.label>Culexus Temple</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Culexus.label>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Culexus.description>Grants you access to STC templates for Weapons used by the Officio Assassinorum's Culexus Temple.\n\nRequires Royalty</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Culexus.description>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Eversor.label>Eversor Temple</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Eversor.label>
  <OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Eversor.description>Grants you access to STC templates for Weapons used by the Officio Assassinorum's Eversor Temple.\n\nRequires Royalty</OG_Assassinorum_Tech_Weapons_Eversor.description>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T1.label>The Dark Kin</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T1.description>The Drukhari were the malevolent faction of the ancient Aeldari who had chosen to remain within the Webway after the Fall and continued to pursue the decadent and hedonistic ways that nearly led to their extinction.

However, they were often referred to by outsiders as "Dark Eldar," a term which they rarely used for themselves and which was first coined by Asdrubael Vect from the Aeldari phrase "Eladrith Ynneas."</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T2.label>The Path of Damnation</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T2.description>Improved Dark Eldar Technology Concepts</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T3.label>The Damned</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T3.description>Advanced Dark Eldar Technology Concepts</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Weapons_Splinter.label>Splinter Technology</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Weapons_Splinter.label>
  <OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Weapons_Splinter.description>Splinter Weapons fire shards of splintered crystal using a powerful magno-electric pulse. These shards are covered in incredibly virulent and fast-acting toxins the better to ensure a painful death.</OG_DarkEldar_Tech_Weapons_Splinter.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T1.label>Craftworld Eldar</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T1.description>The Aeldari who fled their ancient empire in the Craftworlds eventually called themselves the "Asuryani" since their culture was redefined by their decision to pursue the Asuryani Path that they believed had been laid out for them by the chief Aeldari god, the Phoenix King Asuryan.</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T2.label>The Eldar Path</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T2.description>Basic Eldar Technology Concepts</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T3.label>Infinity Circuit</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T3.description>Allows you to construct Wraith weaponry</OG_Eldar_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Shuriken.label>Shuriken Technology</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Shuriken.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Shuriken.description>Shuriken Weapons are the primary type of anti-personnel weapons used by the Aeldari. Utilising gravitic pulses, a mono-molecular disc of plasti-crystal taken from the weapon's magazine is accelerated down the barrel of the weapon, hurling it at the target at incredible velocity. The accelerator creates a peristaltic shift from the front to the rear of the firing chamber, hurling the shuriken missiles forward at a tremendous velocity. A burst of several missiles can be fired in a fraction of a second in this way.</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Shuriken.description>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Weapons_Monofilament.label>Monofilament Weaponry</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Weapons_Monofilament.label>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Weapons_Monofilament.description>All Monofilament Weapons work on the same principle: a liquid form of the psycho-reactive substance known as Wraithbone is kept in stasis within the weapon's magazine. Once the weapon is activated, this substance will be forced by an electromagnetic propulsive field through an incredibly fine sift, and will solidify into a mass of threads, each one molecule thick, called mono-filaments which are razor sharp. This mass of threads, called a "spinner cloud," is then catapulted at the enemy with tremendous force. Being only one molecule in width, the filaments will have few difficulties in penetrating any armour through minute weaknesses in its molecular structure, and will wreak havoc on the body within, chopping it into a gory mess.</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Weapons_Monofilament.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Vortex.label>Vortex Tech</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Vortex.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Vortex.description>Vortex Weapons are some of the most deadly weapons available and, while coming in many shapes and sizes, operate on the same principle of creating a gaping hole in reality. Like a black hole anything that comes in contact with this rift, whether matter or energy, is effectively wiped from existence as it is sucked into the nightmare realm known as the Immaterium and turned into the very stuff of the Warp.</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Vortex.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Witchblade.label>Witchblades</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Witchblade.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Witchblade.description>A Witchblade is a psychically-attuned melee weapon that a Craftworld Aeldari walking the Path of the Seer, such as Warlocks and Farseers, often carry to battle. Essentially a potent Force Weapon, these swords resonate with their users, enhancing their physical strength to terrifying levels -- Farseers have been known to slash through the heaviest of Power Armour or cleave battle tanks clean in half with devastating blows from these weapons. Used to enhance and unleash the latent psychic power of the wielder, Witchblades are effective against all infantry targets; humanoid, xenos, beast or daemon. A Witch Blade contains a helix-shaped, crystalline psychic matrix embedded with runes to channel and focus a Seer's psychic energies.</OG_Eldar_Tech_Weapons_Witchblade.description>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel.label>Eldar Apparel</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel.label>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel.description>Allows you to create basic Eldar apparel</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel.description>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>Eldar Armour</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>
  <OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>Allows you to create basic Eldar armour</OG_Aeldari_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>Aspect Armour</OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>Allows you to create Eldar Aspect Warrior armours</OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.label>Rune Armour</OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.label>
  <OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.description>Allows you to create the most Advanced Eldar armours, such as those worn by Farseers, Warlocks and Exarchs</OG_Eldar_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T1.label>Orkish Kulture</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T1.description>Basic understanding of Orkish 'Kulture'.</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T2.label>Mek Tek</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T2.description>Allowz da mekz ta make some wargear an shootaz wiv even more Dakka!</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T3.label>Big Mek Brainz</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T3.description>Allowz da mekz ta make some fancy wargear an da best shootaz wiv da most Dakka!</OG_Ork_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T1.label>Brutality</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T1.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T1.description>Allowz da boyz ta make propa Choppaz!</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T1.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T2.label>Extreme Brutality</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T2.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T2.description>Allowz da boyz ta make bigga, betta Choppaz!</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Melee_T2.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Ranged_T2.label>More Dakka</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Ranged_T2.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Ranged_T2.description>Allowz da boyz ta make betta Shootaz!</OG_Ork_Tech_Weapons_Ranged_T2.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel.label>Clovin</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel.description>Allowz da boyz ta make Clovin and Leva Arma!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T1.label>Nob bitz</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T1.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T1.description>Allowz da boyz ta make stuff fer Nobz!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T1.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>Arma</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>Allowz da boyz ta make betta Arma!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>Eavy Arma</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>Allowz da mekz ta make Eavy Arma!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T2.label>Boss bitz</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T2.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T2.description>Allowz da boyz ta make stuff fer da Boss!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_T2.description>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.label>Mega Arma</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.label>
  <OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.description>Allowz da mekz ta make Mega Arma!</OG_Ork_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T3.description>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T1.label>Kroot Kindred</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T1.description>Basic understanding of Kroot Culture</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T2.label>Kroot Culture</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T2.description>Basic understanding of Kroot Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T3.label>Kroot Mercenaries</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T3.description>Basic understanding of Kroot Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Kroot_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T1.label>The Greater Good</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T1.description>Basic understanding of Tau Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T2.label>Caste System</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T2.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T2.description>Basic understanding of Tau Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T2.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T3.label>Etherals</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T3.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T3.description>Basic understanding of Tau Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Tau_Tech_Base_T3.description>
  <OG_Vespid_Tech_Base_T1.label>Vespid Strain</OG_Vespid_Tech_Base_T1.label>
  <OG_Vespid_Tech_Base_T1.description>Basic understanding of Vespid Culture and the Greater Good</OG_Vespid_Tech_Base_T1.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_PlasmaPulse.label>Pulse Weapons</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_PlasmaPulse.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_PlasmaPulse.description>The T'au, whilst a relatively young race in the grand scale of time, have advanced extraordinarily rapidly and have already perfected many different forms of Plasma Weapon technology and use it to a great extent on the battlefield. The T'au variant of Plasma Weapon technology, which they refer to as Pulse Weapons, is commonly utilised by the warriors of the T'au Empire's military Fire Caste. Pulse Weapons make use of micro-pulsed induction fields to propel a particle across a distance.</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_PlasmaPulse.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Railgun.label>Railgun Weaponry</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Railgun.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Railgun.description>Rail Weapons use a series of powerful electromagnets and super-conductive electrodes to accelerate small, solid and conductive projectiles to hypersonic speeds. The resulting high levels of kinetic force imparted to the weapon's projectile allows it to devastate and destroy the most heavily armoured vehicles on impact, even at extremely long ranges. Few vehicles are able to withstand a direct hit from a Rail Weapon without suffering critical damage.</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Railgun.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Ion.label>Ionic Projection</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Ion.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Ion.description>Ion Weapons are advanced directed energy weapons utilised by the Fire Caste of the Tau Empire. Ion Weapons typically are capable of engaging enemies at long range with high-energy streams of ionised subatomic particles, vaporising flesh and metal with equal ease. These high-energy ions containing an electric charge are accelerated by an electromagnetic field and react explosively with the target as a result of the direct transfer of energy at an atomic level.</OG_Tau_Tech_Weapons_Ion.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel.label>Tau Apparel</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel.description>Allows you to create basic Tau apparal</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>Pathfinder Armour</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>Allows you to create Pathfinder armour</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T1.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>Combat Armour</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>Allows you to create Combat armour</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Armour_T2.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Drone.label>Tau Drone Tech</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Drone.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Drone.description>Basic understanding of Tau Drone technology, allows you to build basic drones</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Drone.description>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Shield.label>Tau Shield Tech</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Shield.label>
  <OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Shield.description>Allows you to Shield drones</OG_Tau_Tech_Apparel_Wargear_Shield.description>
</LanguageData>