<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AirConditioning.label>air conditioning</AirConditioning.label>
  <AirConditioning.description>Build coolers to make people comfortable in hot weather, or to construct freezers for storing perishable goods.</AirConditioning.description>
  
  <Autodoors.label>autodoor</Autodoors.label>
  <Autodoors.description>Build autodoors which automatically open when someone approaches, without slowing anyone down.</Autodoors.description>
  
  <Batteries.label>battery</Batteries.label>
  <Batteries.description>Build batteries for storing electricity.</Batteries.description>
  
  <BiofuelRefining.label>biofuel refining</BiofuelRefining.label>
  <BiofuelRefining.description>Build biofuel refineries to make chemfuel from biological matter like wood or foodstuffs.</BiofuelRefining.description>
  
  <BlowbackOperation.label>blowback operation</BlowbackOperation.label>
  <BlowbackOperation.description>Craft low-power blowback-operated guns like autopistols and machine pistols.</BlowbackOperation.description>
  
  <ColoredLights.label>advanced lights</ColoredLights.label>
  <ColoredLights.description>Change the color of standard electric lamps, and reduce their power consumption by half. This does not affect sun lamps.</ColoredLights.description>
  
  <Electricity.label>electricity</Electricity.label>
  <Electricity.description>Harness the power of electricity for a hundred different tasks.</Electricity.description>
  <Electricity.discoveredLetterText>Your colony has harnessed the power which outsiders call "electricity". It has the potential to transform every aspect of your people's way of life.\n\nYou have now unlocked the Power tab in the Architect menu from which you may build electric generators, power conduits, and other mechanisms to control this new force. The Power tab also displays the electric grid which connects electric generators and appliances.</Electricity.discoveredLetterText>
  <Electricity.discoveredLetterTitle>About: Electricity</Electricity.discoveredLetterTitle>
  
  <Firefoam.label>firefoam</Firefoam.label>
  <Firefoam.description>Construct firefoam poppers, automatic fire-safety devices which spread fire-retardant foam in response to encroaching flames.</Firefoam.description>
  
  <FlakArmor.label>flak armor</FlakArmor.label>
  <FlakArmor.description>Craft clothing with metal armor sewn in to resist bullets and explosions. This weighty armor slows movement slightly.</FlakArmor.description>
  
  <FoamTurret.label>foam turret</FoamTurret.label>
  <FoamTurret.description>Produce a turret which can be activated to spray fire-extinguishing foam.</FoamTurret.description>
  
  <GasOperation.label>gas operation</GasOperation.label>
  <GasOperation.description>Craft high-power guns like chain shotguns, LMGs, and heavy SMGs.</GasOperation.description>
  
  <GeothermalPower.label>geothermal power</GeothermalPower.label>
  <GeothermalPower.description>Build geothermal power plants on top of steam geysers, for uninterrupted power.</GeothermalPower.description>
  
  <GunTurrets.label>gun turrets</GunTurrets.label>
  <GunTurrets.description>Produce simple automated gun turrets.</GunTurrets.description>
  
  <Gunsmithing.label>gunsmithing</Gunsmithing.label>
  <Gunsmithing.description>Craft simple manually-operated guns like revolvers, pump shotguns, bolt-action rifles, and incendiary launchers.</Gunsmithing.description>
  
  <Hydroponics.label>hydroponics</Hydroponics.label>
  <Hydroponics.description>Build hydroponics basins to rapidly grow crops indoors regardless of the terrain or weather outside.</Hydroponics.description>
  
  <IEDs.label>IEDs</IEDs.label>
  <IEDs.description>Build improvised traps from any kind of mortar shell.</IEDs.description>
  
  <Machining.label>machining</Machining.label>
  <Machining.description>Build machining tables to craft guns, grenades, flak armor, and to shred dead mechanoids for resources.</Machining.description>
  
  <Mortars.label>mortars</Mortars.label>
  <Mortars.description>Build mortars which can lob shells long distances - even over walls.</Mortars.description>
  
  <NutrientPaste.label>nutrient paste</NutrientPaste.label>
  <NutrientPaste.description>Build nutrient paste dispensers which efficiently produce edible meals from raw nutritive feedstocks, while requiring no labor at all.</NutrientPaste.description>
  
  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>packaged survival meal</PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>
  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>Produce packaged survival meals which never go bad. Great for traveling.</PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>
  
  <Prosthetics.label>prosthetics</Prosthetics.label>
  <Prosthetics.description>Build inexpensive prosthetic body parts to replace lost limbs. Requires a skilled doctor to attach.</Prosthetics.description>
  
  <SmokepopBelt.label>smokepop packs</SmokepopBelt.label>
  <SmokepopBelt.description>Build smokepop packs which allow the wearer to deploy a defensive smokescreen.</SmokepopBelt.description>
  
  <SolarPanels.label>solar panel</SolarPanels.label>
  <SolarPanels.description>Build solar panels for electricity generation.</SolarPanels.description>
  
  <SterileMaterials.label>sterile materials</SterileMaterials.label>
  <SterileMaterials.description>Construct sterile tiles to make cleanrooms for safer and more effective medical treatment, research, and cooking.</SterileMaterials.description>
  
  <TubeTelevision.label>tube television</TubeTelevision.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>Produce tube televisions for recreational watching.</TubeTelevision.description>
  
  <WatermillGenerator.label>watermill generator</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>Build watermill generators on rivers to generate a steady supply of power.</WatermillGenerator.description>
</LanguageData>