<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DeepDrilling.label>deep drilling</DeepDrilling.label>
  <DeepDrilling.description>Build deep drills for extracting resources from underground. You'll need a ground-penetrating scanner to find the resources.</DeepDrilling.description>
  
  <FlatscreenTelevision.label>flatscreen television</FlatscreenTelevision.label>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Produce high-resolution flatscreen televisions for greater enjoyment.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.label>ground-penetrating scanner</GroundPenetratingScanner.label>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.description>Build ground-penetrating scanners that can detect drillable resources under the surface. Requires an advanced component to construct.</GroundPenetratingScanner.description>
  
  <HeavyTurrets.label>autocannon turret</HeavyTurrets.label>
  <HeavyTurrets.description>Produce the heavy autocannon turret.</HeavyTurrets.description>
  
  <HospitalBed.label>hospital bed</HospitalBed.label>
  <HospitalBed.description>Construct hospital beds which improve medical outcomes.</HospitalBed.description>
  
  <LongRangeMineralScanner.label>long-range mineral scanner</LongRangeMineralScanner.label>
  <LongRangeMineralScanner.description>Construct long-range mineral scanners your researchers can use to detect precious minerals across the planet. Can be tuned to find a specific mineral. Requires advanced components to construct.</LongRangeMineralScanner.description>
  
  <MedicineProduction.label>medicine production</MedicineProduction.label>
  <MedicineProduction.description>Produce standard industrial-tech medicine by combining herbal medicine, neutroamine, and cloth.</MedicineProduction.description>
  
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.label>microelectronics</MicroelectronicsBasics.label>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>Work with complex microelectronics. This unlocks the hi-tech research bench and comms console.</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>
  
  <MoisturePump.label>moisture pump</MoisturePump.label>
  <MoisturePump.description>Construct moisture pumps, which very slowly normalize the moisture in the ground around them. They can turn wet ground dry and convert soft sand into normal sand.</MoisturePump.description>
  
  <MultibarrelWeapons.label>multibarrel weapons</MultibarrelWeapons.label>
  <MultibarrelWeapons.description>Assemble miniguns.</MultibarrelWeapons.description>
  
  <PrecisionRifling.label>precision rifling</PrecisionRifling.label>
  <PrecisionRifling.description>Craft precisely-machined guns like assault rifles and sniper rifles.</PrecisionRifling.description>
  
  <ShieldBelt.label>shields</ShieldBelt.label>
  <ShieldBelt.description>Build wearable shield gear. Shields use momentum-repulsion technology to prevent projectiles from traversing the field boundary.</ShieldBelt.description>
  
  <TransportPod.label>transport pod</TransportPod.label>
  <TransportPod.description>Construct launchable transport pods that you can use to send people and supplies long distances across the planet's surface. Can be used for raiding, travel, sending gifts, and more.</TransportPod.description>
</LanguageData>