<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AdvancedFabrication.label>advanced fabrication</AdvancedFabrication.label>
  <AdvancedFabrication.description>Fabricate advanced components from standard components and other materials.</AdvancedFabrication.description>
  
  <Bionics.label>bionic replacements</Bionics.label>
  <Bionics.description>Build high-tech bionic body parts to replace lost limbs and eyes. Requires a skilled doctor to attach.</Bionics.description>
  
  <ChargedShot.label>pulse-charged munitions</ChargedShot.label>
  <ChargedShot.description>Build weapons which fire pulse-charged munitions for extra damage. Note that these also require advanced components.</ChargedShot.description>
  
  <Cryptosleep.label>cryptosleep casket</Cryptosleep.label>
  <Cryptosleep.description>Construct cryptosleep caskets, which can put living beings in a state of indefinite suspended animation.</Cryptosleep.description>
  
  <Fabrication.label>fabrication</Fabrication.label>
  <Fabrication.description>Build fabrication benches, capable of high-tech projects ranging from component assembly to power armor construction.</Fabrication.description>
  <Fabrication.discoveredLetterText>You now have the technology to build a fabrication bench - but it also requires some advanced components to get started. You can collect advanced components several ways:\n\n  -All outlander settlements sell advanced components. Send a caravan to buy some.\n  -Some visiting traders sell advanced components. Invite or wait for them.\n  -Some quests are rewarded with advanced components.</Fabrication.discoveredLetterText>
  <Fabrication.discoveredLetterTitle>About: Getting advanced components</Fabrication.discoveredLetterTitle>
  
  <MultiAnalyzer.label>multi-analyzer</MultiAnalyzer.label>
  <MultiAnalyzer.description>Build multi-analyzers which increase research speed and allow higher-level research projects.</MultiAnalyzer.description>
  
  <PoweredArmor.label>marine armor</PoweredArmor.label>
  <PoweredArmor.description>Build marine armor, a general-use powered armor suit used by high-tech shock troops. Note that these also require advanced components.</PoweredArmor.description>
  
  <ReconArmor.label>recon armor</ReconArmor.label>
  <ReconArmor.description>Craft recon armor, a light powered armor suit used by scout troops who need protection on the move. Note that these also require advanced components.</ReconArmor.description>
  
  <RocketswarmLauncher.label>rocketswarm launcher</RocketswarmLauncher.label>
  <RocketswarmLauncher.description>Produce rocketswarm launchers, single-burst turrets which can devastate a wide area at a key moment in battle.</RocketswarmLauncher.description>
  
  <SniperTurret.label>uranium slug turret</SniperTurret.label>
  <SniperTurret.description>Produce the armor-penetrating uranium slug turret. It fires uranium slugs which tear through plasteel like paper, but it's less effective at close range.</SniperTurret.description>
  
  <VitalsMonitor.label>vitals monitor</VitalsMonitor.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Build vitals monitors which improve medical outcomes when placed next to hospital beds.</VitalsMonitor.description>
</LanguageData>