<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PTPsiDefence.label>Psi Defense</PTPsiDefence.label>
  <PTPsiDefence.description>Psi defense is a defensive technique that decreases a psion's susceptibility to psionic abilities, including friendly ones.</PTPsiDefence.description>
  <PTPsiTrance.label>Psi Trance</PTPsiTrance.label>
  <PTPsiTrance.description>Psi trance is a simple meditation technique allows a psion to rest more effectively than simple sleep, resulting in less time spent sleeping.</PTPsiTrance.description>
  <PTInsulation.label>Insulation</PTInsulation.label>
  <PTInsulation.description>Insulation is a technique that allows a psion's body to function normally in a wider temperature range than would otherwise be possible.</PTInsulation.description>
  <PTSerenity.label>Serenity</PTSerenity.label>
  <PTSerenity.description>Serenity is a technique that steels a psion's mind against the stresses of the world, lowering their chance to have a mental break.</PTSerenity.description>
  <PTWeaponSynchronicity.label>Weapon Synchronicity</PTWeaponSynchronicity.label>
  <PTWeaponSynchronicity.description>Weapon synchronicity is a technique developed to allow a psion to properly utilize the potential of a psychic weapon. Without any training, psychic weapons are no different from their normal couterparts. With weapon synchronicity, the psion can improve the performance of psychic weapons.</PTWeaponSynchronicity.description>
  <PTPsiForging.label>Psi Forging</PTPsiForging.label>
  <PTPsiForging.description>Psi forging is a technique that allows a psion to manipulate psychically resonant materials more easily. Psions trained in this ability can use it to create athenium from simpler materials.</PTPsiForging.description>
  <PTCombatPrecognition.label>Combat Precognition</PTCombatPrecognition.label>
  <PTCombatPrecognition.description>Combat precognition is a technique that allows a psion to predict an adversary's movement before it happens, making them better at dodging attacks.</PTCombatPrecognition.description>
  <PTCombatInsight.label>Combat Insight</PTCombatInsight.label>
  <PTCombatInsight.description>Combat insight is a technique that allows a psion to more easily see an adversary's weaknesses, making them more effective at penetrating armor.</PTCombatInsight.description>
  <PTCombatIntuition.label>Combat Intuition</PTCombatIntuition.label>
  <PTCombatIntuition.description>Combat intuition is a technique that gives a psion insight into an adversary's next moves, allowing them to more easily track and shoot targets, faster.</PTCombatIntuition.description>
  <PTCombatPrecision.label>Combat Precision</PTCombatPrecision.label>
  <PTCombatPrecision.description>Combat precision is a technique that helps a psion stay calm in the pressure of combat, improving their precision with shooting weapons.</PTCombatPrecision.description>
  <PTEmpatheticNegotiation.label>Empathetic Negotiation</PTEmpatheticNegotiation.label>
  <PTEmpatheticNegotiation.description>Empathetic negotiation is a technique that makes a psion more receptive to the needs of others, improving their negotiation abilities.</PTEmpatheticNegotiation.description>
  <PTEmpatheticBargaining.label>Empathetic Bargaining</PTEmpatheticBargaining.label>
  <PTEmpatheticBargaining.description>Empathetic bargaining is a technique that makes a psion more receptive to the wants of others, improving their bargaining abilities.</PTEmpatheticBargaining.description>
  <PTEmpatheticHandling.label>Empathetic Handling</PTEmpatheticHandling.label>
  <PTEmpatheticHandling.description>Empathetic handling is a technique that makes a psion more receptive to the feelings of animals, improving their ability to tame and train animals.</PTEmpatheticHandling.description>
  <PTPsiAttunement.label>Psi Attunement</PTPsiAttunement.label>
  <PTPsiAttunement.description>Psi attunement is a meditation technique increases a psion's synchronization with psychic phenomenon, increasing their psychic sensitivity by 40%.</PTPsiAttunement.description>
  <PTPsiFocus.label>Psi Focus</PTPsiFocus.label>
  <PTPsiFocus.description>Psi focus is a meditation technique that increases a psion's psi energy regeneration by 0.5, scaled by their ability modifier.\n\nPsi focus is not counted for the purposes of unlocking new ability slots.</PTPsiFocus.description>
  <PTPsiCapacitance.label>Psi Capacitance</PTPsiCapacitance.label>
  <PTPsiCapacitance.description>Psi capacitance is a meditation technique that increases a psion's maximum psi energy by 50, scaled by their ability modifier.\n\nPsi capacitance is not counted for the purposes of unlocking new ability slots.</PTPsiCapacitance.description>
  <PTTruesight.label>Truesight</PTTruesight.label>
  <PTTruesight.description>Truesight is a technique that unlocks a psion's metaphorical third eye, allowing them to visualize psychic phenomenon.</PTTruesight.description>
  <PTConversion.label>Conversion</PTConversion.label>
  <PTConversion.description>Conversion is a technique that quickens a psion's metabolism.</PTConversion.description>
  <PTPurity.label>Purity</PTPurity.label>
  <PTPurity.description>Purity is a technique that helps to purify a psion's body faster it than normally would.</PTPurity.description>
  <PTOverdrive.label>Overdrive</PTOverdrive.label>
  <PTOverdrive.description>Overdrive is a technique that pushes a psion's body to its physical limits, improving its overall function.</PTOverdrive.description>
  <PTAlacrity.label>Alacrity</PTAlacrity.label>
  <PTAlacrity.description>Alacrity is a technique that allows a psion to move faster than would normally be possible.</PTAlacrity.description>
  <PTPrecision.label>Precision</PTPrecision.label>
  <PTPrecision.description>Precision is a technique that makes it easier for a psion to precisely manipulate objects.</PTPrecision.description>
  <PTInfluence.label>Influence</PTInfluence.label>
  <PTInfluence.description>Influence is a technique that integrates the use of psionics in social interactions, making the psion more convincing.</PTInfluence.description>
  <PTInsight.label>Insight</PTInsight.label>
  <PTInsight.description>Insight is a technique that integrates the use of psionics in social interactions, making the psion more understanding.</PTInsight.description>
  <PTPerfectedDefence.label>Perfected Defense</PTPerfectedDefence.label>
  <PTPerfectedDefence.description>Perfected defense is an advanced defensive technique that decreases a psion's susceptibility to psionic abilities, including friendly ones.\n\nTo train perfected defense, the psion must already be trained in psi defence. Psi defence will be upgraded to its perfected variant upon training completion.</PTPerfectedDefence.description>
  <PTMindfray.label>Mindfray</PTMindfray.label>
  <PTMindfray.description>Mindfray is a targeted ability that can cause the target to momentarily lose touch with reality. It doesn't take much energy to use and has a short cooldown.</PTMindfray.description>
  <PTMindfray.GizmoDesc>Use mindfray on a target</PTMindfray.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindfray.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Mindfray</PTMindfray.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindfray.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Causes the target to lose touch with reality for a short time.</PTMindfray.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTMindSuppression.label>Mind Suppression</PTMindSuppression.label>
  <PTMindSuppression.description>Mind suppression is a targeted ability that decreases the psychic sensitivity of the target for some time.</PTMindSuppression.description>
  <PTMindSuppression.GizmoDesc>Use mind suppression on a target</PTMindSuppression.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Psychic Suppression</PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Decreases the psychic sensitivity of the target for some time.</PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.1.Title>Psychic Silence</PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.1.Title>
  <PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.1.Description>Massively decreases the psychic sensitivity of the target for some time.</PTMindSuppression.PossibleEffects.1.Description>
  <PTInspire.label>Inspire</PTInspire.label>
  <PTInspire.description>Inspire is a targeted ability that gives the target an inspiring thought, increasing their mood for a while.</PTInspire.description>
  <PTInspire.GizmoDesc>Use inspire on a target</PTInspire.GizmoDesc>
  <PTInspire.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Inspire</PTInspire.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTInspire.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Gives the target an inspiring thought, improving their mood significantly.</PTInspire.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTPerfectedSynchronicity.label>Perfected Synchronicity</PTPerfectedSynchronicity.label>
  <PTPerfectedSynchronicity.description>Perfected synchronicity is an advanced technique developed to allow a psion to properly utilize the potential of a psychic weapon. Without any training, psychic weapons are no different from their normal couterparts. With perfected synchronicity, the psion can significantly improve the performance of psychic weapons.\n\nTo train perfected synchronicity, the psion must already be trained in weapon synchronicity. Weapon synchronicity will be upgraded to its perfected variant upon training completion.</PTPerfectedSynchronicity.description>
  <PTPerfectedAttunement.label>Perfected Attunement</PTPerfectedAttunement.label>
  <PTPerfectedAttunement.description>Perfected attunement is an advanced meditation technique increases a psion's synchronization with psychic phenomenon, increasing their psychic sensitivity by 80%.\n\nTo train perfected attunement, the psion must already be trained in psi attunement. Psi attunement will be upgraded to its perfected variant upon training completion.</PTPerfectedAttunement.description>
  <PTPerfectedFocus.label>Perfected Focus</PTPerfectedFocus.label>
  <PTPerfectedFocus.description>Perfected focus is an advanced meditation technique that increases a psion's psi energy regeneration by 1, scaled by their ability modifier.\n\nTo train perfected focus, the psion must already be trained in psi focus. Psi focus will be upgraded to its perfected variant upon training completion.\n\nPerfected focus is not counted for the purposes of unlocking new ability slots.</PTPerfectedFocus.description>
  <PTPerfectedCapacitance.label>Perfected Capacitance</PTPerfectedCapacitance.label>
  <PTPerfectedCapacitance.description>Perfected capacitance is an advanced meditation technique that increases a psion's maximum psi energy by 100, scaled by their ability modifier.\n\nTo train perfected capacitance, the psion must already be trained in psi capacitance. Psi capacitance will be upgraded to its perfected variant upon training completion.\n\nPerfected capacitance is not counted for the purposes of unlocking new ability slots.</PTPerfectedCapacitance.description>
  <PTBattlefieldPrecognition.label>Battlefield Precognition</PTBattlefieldPrecognition.label>
  <PTBattlefieldPrecognition.description>Battlefield precognition is a powerful technique that gives a psion extended awareness of the battlefield, allowing them to periodically dodge damage from psychically active attackers.\n\nPsions using battlefield precognition can't dodge more than 60% of the time, ever. The chance to dodge is scaled by the attacker's psychic sensitivity, meaning that attacks from psions can be dodged easily, and attacks from psychically dead individuals are harder to dodge.</PTBattlefieldPrecognition.description>
  <PTBattlefieldPrecision.label>Battlefield Precision</PTBattlefieldPrecision.label>
  <PTBattlefieldPrecision.description>Battlefield precision is a powerful technique that gives a psion extended awareness of the battlefield, allowing them to place attacks better, increasing their damage dealt to psychically active targets.\n\nThe damage modifier is scaled by the target's psychic sensitivity, meaning that attacks against psions have significantly increased damage, and attacks from psychically dead individuals have a diminished damage increase.</PTBattlefieldPrecision.description>
  <PTMindlink.label>Mindlink</PTMindlink.label>
  <PTMindlink.description>Mindlink is a targeted ability that grants the target a portion of the user's skills while active. Consumes a lot of energy while active.</PTMindlink.description>
  <PTMindlink.GizmoDesc>Use mindlink on a target</PTMindlink.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindlink.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Mindlink</PTMindlink.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindlink.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Grants a portion of the user's skills to the target, but only for skills which the target is worse at. Unlike most abilities, the transfer is affected by both the user's and the target's ability modifiers.</PTMindlink.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTPsiHeal.label>Psi Heal</PTPsiHeal.label>
  <PTPsiHeal.description>Psi heal is a targeted ability that uses psychic energy to mend injuries in the target. It takes a lot of training to use effectively, as its base healing is quite low.</PTPsiHeal.description>
  <PTPsiHeal.GizmoDesc>Use psi heal on a target</PTPsiHeal.GizmoDesc>
  <PTPsiHeal.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Heal</PTPsiHeal.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTPsiHeal.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Heals the target using psychic energy.</PTPsiHeal.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTMindsoothe.label>Mindsoothe</PTMindsoothe.label>
  <PTMindsoothe.description>Mindsoothe is a targeted ability that attempts to bring the target out of a mental state. Beyond the typical success chance factors, it is additionally more difficult to bring a target out of a recently started mental state.</PTMindsoothe.description>
  <PTMindsoothe.GizmoDesc>Use mindsoothe on a target</PTMindsoothe.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindsoothe.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Soothe</PTMindsoothe.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindsoothe.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Breaks the target out of their current mental state.</PTMindsoothe.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTInsanity.label>Insanity</PTInsanity.label>
  <PTInsanity.description>Insanity is a targeted ability that can cause the target to go insane, attacking anything near them. It takes a lot of training to use properly, as it has a low base success chance.</PTInsanity.description>
  <PTInsanity.GizmoDesc>Use insanity on a target</PTInsanity.GizmoDesc>
  <PTInsanity.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Insanity</PTInsanity.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTInsanity.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Causes the target to go insane for some time, attacking anyone nearby.</PTInsanity.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTMindmelt.label>Mindmelt</PTMindmelt.label>
  <PTMindmelt.description>Mindmelt is a targeted ability that overloads the target with raw psychic energy, causing injuries. It takes a lot of training to use effectively, as its base damage is quite low.\n\nPsychic injuries take a variety of horrifying forms that are generally painful and impossible to treat. Often, the effects are as much psychosomatic as physical, resulting in far greater pain than one would expect for the damage caused.</PTMindmelt.description>
  <PTMindmelt.GizmoDesc>Use mindmelt on a target</PTMindmelt.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Psionic Damage</PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Inflicts psionic damage on the target, causing them extreme pain and some injury.</PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.1.Title>Mindmelt</PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.1.Title>
  <PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.1.Description>Inflicts psionic damage on the target, but inflicts all of it directly on the brain. Instantly kills the target most of the time.</PTMindmelt.PossibleEffects.1.Description>
  <PTMindlash.label>Mindlash</PTMindlash.label>
  <PTMindlash.description>Mindlash is an ability that stuns anyone who attacks the psion for a short time.\n\nMindlash is not an active ability, and is triggered when the psion is attacked.</PTMindlash.description>
  <PTMindlash.GizmoDesc>When the psion is attacked they will the attacker for a short time.</PTMindlash.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindlash.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Mindlash</PTMindlash.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindlash.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Stuns the attacker for a short time.</PTMindlash.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTTranscendentDefense.label>Transcendent Defense</PTTranscendentDefense.label>
  <PTTranscendentDefense.description>Transcendent defense is a highly advanced defensive technique that decreases a psion's susceptibility to psionic abilities, including friendly ones.\n\nTo train transcendent defense, the psion must already be trained in perfected defence. Perfected defence will be upgraded to its transcendent variant upon training completion.</PTTranscendentDefense.description>
  <PTMindDomination.label>Mind Domination</PTMindDomination.label>
  <PTMindDomination.description>Mind domination is a long-range targeted ability that overloads the target's brain with psychic energy, killing them instantly most of the time. Mind domination can only be used on other psions.</PTMindDomination.description>
  <PTMindDomination.GizmoDesc>Use mind domination on a target</PTMindDomination.GizmoDesc>
  <PTMindDomination.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Destroy Mind</PTMindDomination.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTMindDomination.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Inflicts massive psionic damage on the target's brain, killing them instantly most of the time.</PTMindDomination.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTPhoenix.label>Phoenix</PTPhoenix.label>
  <PTPhoenix.description>Phoenix is an ability that allows the psion to draw on the psychic energies around them to heal themselves when in need.\n\nPhoenix is not an active ability, and is triggered when the psion is close to death.</PTPhoenix.description>
  <PTPhoenix.GizmoDesc>When the psion takes damage that would down or kill them, phoenix heals them</PTPhoenix.GizmoDesc>
  <PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.0.Title>Resurgence</PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.0.Title>
  <PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.0.Description>Heals wounds on the user.</PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.0.Description>
  <PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.1.Title>Resurrection</PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.1.Title>
  <PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.1.Description>Heals the user for a massive amount.</PTPhoenix.PossibleEffectsOnUser.1.Description>
  <PTMindFortress.label>Mind Fortress</PTMindFortress.label>
  <PTMindFortress.description>Mind fortress is a powerful defensive technique that makes the psion immune to psionic abilities. Unfortunately, this technique also makes them unable to use active abilities.</PTMindFortress.description>
  <PTPsiRally.label>Psi Rally</PTPsiRally.label>
  <PTPsiRally.description>Psi rally is a powerful ability that can grant a variety of bonuses to friendly pawns around the psion.\n\nDue to the intense focus needed to channel psi rally, damage will interrupt casting.</PTPsiRally.description>
  <PTPsiRally.GizmoDesc>Channel psi rally</PTPsiRally.GizmoDesc>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Battle trance</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Puts the target into a battle trance, improving their combat efficiency.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.1.Title>Battlefield awakening</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.1.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.1.Description>Awakens latent battlefield abilities in the target, massively improving their combat efficiency.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.1.Description>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.2.Title>Melee mastery</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.2.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.2.Description>Grants the target melee mastery for a time, improving their melee weapon abilities.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.2.Description>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.3.Title>Ranged mastery</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.3.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.3.Description>Grants the target ranged mastery for a time, improving their ranged weapon abilities.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.3.Description>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.4.Title>Inspire</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.4.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.4.Description>Gives the target an inspiring thought, improving their mood significantly.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.4.Description>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.5.Title>Heal</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.5.Title>
  <PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.5.Description>Heals the target using psychic energy.</PTPsiRally.PossibleEffects.5.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.label>Psi Storm</PTPsiStorm.label>
  <PTPsiStorm.description>Psi storm is a powerful ability that can cause a variety of damaging effects to hostile pawns around the psion.\n\nDue to the intense focus needed to channel psi storm, damage will interrupt casting.</PTPsiStorm.description>
  <PTPsiStorm.GizmoDesc>Channel psi storm</PTPsiStorm.GizmoDesc>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.0.Title>Insanity</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.0.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.0.Description>Causes the target to go insane for some time, attacking anyone nearby.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.0.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.1.Title>Catatonia</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.1.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.1.Description>Causes the target to go catatonic for some time.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.1.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.2.Title>Panic</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.2.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.2.Description>Causes the target to panic and flee.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.2.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.3.Title>Mindfray</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.3.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.3.Description>Causes the target to lose touch with reality for a short time.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.3.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.4.Title>Psionic Damage</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.4.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.4.Description>Inflicts psionic damage on the target, causing them extreme pain and some injury.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.4.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.5.Title>Massive Psionic Damage</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.5.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.5.Description>Inflicts massive psionic damage on the target, causing excruciating pain and major injury.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.5.Description>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.6.Title>Mindmelt</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.6.Title>
  <PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.6.Description>Inflicts psionic damage on the target, but inflicts all of it directly on the brain. Instantly kills the target most of the time.</PTPsiStorm.PossibleEffects.6.Description>
</LanguageData>