<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <NobleApparel.label>noble apparel</NobleApparel.label>
  <NobleApparel.description>Tailor noble-specific apparel like formal shirts and royal robes.</NobleApparel.description>
  <RoyalApparel.label>royal apparel</RoyalApparel.label>
  <RoyalApparel.description>Tailor royal apparel of the highest tier, like royal robes and crowns.</RoyalApparel.description>
  <CataphractArmor.label>cataphract armor</CataphractArmor.label>
  <CataphractArmor.description>Craft cataphract armor, heavy powered armor that slows the user but which can absorb extreme punishment. Note that these also require advanced components.</CataphractArmor.description>
  <JumpPack.label>jump packs</JumpPack.label>
  <JumpPack.description>Build jump packs to perform aerial assaults during combat.</JumpPack.description>
  <Gunlink.label>gunlink</Gunlink.label>
  <Gunlink.description>Build wearable gunlinks to enhance your soldiers' shooting accuracy.</Gunlink.description>
  <BrainWiring.label>brain wiring</BrainWiring.label>
  <BrainWiring.description>Craft brain implants that induce or prevent blunt sensations like joy or pain.</BrainWiring.description>
  <SpecializedLimbs.label>specialized limbs</SpecializedLimbs.label>
  <SpecializedLimbs.description>Craft specialized bionic limbs built for specific purposes - both combat and labor.</SpecializedLimbs.description>
  <CompactWeaponry.label>compact weaponry</CompactWeaponry.label>
  <CompactWeaponry.description>Craft compact, concealable bionic weapons which can be embedded in various body parts.</CompactWeaponry.description>
  <VenomSynthesis.label>poison synthesis</VenomSynthesis.label>
  <VenomSynthesis.description>Craft bionics that synthesize venom from internal chemical reactors for use in toxifying attacks.</VenomSynthesis.description>
  <ArtificialMetabolism.label>artificial metabolism</ArtificialMetabolism.label>
  <ArtificialMetabolism.description>Craft bionics that process food more safely or efficiently than a biological stomach.</ArtificialMetabolism.description>
  <NeuralComputation.label>neural computation</NeuralComputation.label>
  <NeuralComputation.description>Craft brain implants that assist thought and learning by use of a direct, shallow brain-computer interface.</NeuralComputation.description>
  <SkinHardening.label>skin hardening</SkinHardening.label>
  <SkinHardening.description>Craft bionic implants which induce the toughening of natural skin, producing an armor-like effect.</SkinHardening.description>
  <HealingFactors.label>healing factors</HealingFactors.label>
  <HealingFactors.description>Craft bionics that enhance natural healing processes.</HealingFactors.description>
  <FleshShaping.label>flesh shaping</FleshShaping.label>
  <FleshShaping.description>Craft bionics which induce the reshaping of natural flesh, usually for the purposes of aesthetic enhancement or personal pleasure.</FleshShaping.description>
  <MolecularAnalysis.label>molecular analysis</MolecularAnalysis.label>
  <MolecularAnalysis.description>Craft bionics with molecular analyzers for assisting the immune system or analyzing food.</MolecularAnalysis.description>
  <CircadianInfluence.label>circadian influence</CircadianInfluence.label>
  <CircadianInfluence.description>Craft brain implants that chemically manipulate the circadian rhythm, reducing or altering the need to sleep.</CircadianInfluence.description>
  <Harp.label>harp</Harp.label>
  <Harp.description>Craft the harp, a simple stationary musical instrument popular among nobility in some cultures.</Harp.description>
  <Harpsichord.label>harpsichord</Harpsichord.label>
  <Harpsichord.description>Craft the harpsichord, a complex stationary musical instrument.</Harpsichord.description>
  <Piano.label>piano</Piano.label>
  <Piano.description>Craft the piano, an advanced stationary musical instrument.</Piano.description>
</LanguageData>